<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brian Hammons on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/brian-hammons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brian Hammons on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/brian-hammons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150921-the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150921-the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-2FRIs6Ct-Fc/VgDXNDwW06I/AAAAAAAACcY/NajCMB6v3Rc/s2048/DH17.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&amp;rsquo;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&amp;rsquo;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&amp;rsquo;t get caught! Cause you know, awkward.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noshing Tacos with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150322-noshing-tacos-with-review-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150322-noshing-tacos-with-review-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Once again we were proud to host buddy Brian Hammons of the food/candy/retro/life blog Review the World as he made his way down to Dallas for the big UFC 185 fight night. What a weekend! Among other things, I introduced Brian Hammons to some of the best tacos in the COUNTRY. Go see what resulted over on reviewtheworld.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150101-top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150101-top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2014/</guid>
      <description>One thing I love is end of year retrospectives. And in the grand tradition I started last year, I offer to you the top ten Review the World episodes of 2014. So clear your personal calendars, grab a bag of Rap Snacks, and settle in the for the show. These are all episodes I love, and I encourage you to watch every one in its entirety.&#xA;#10: Childhood Neighborhood Tour We begin with Brian&amp;rsquo;s most recent entry, one that was intended to cap all of his furious activity for 2014, and at one point, possibly forever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Mrgo_E1r37k/VGLpoDVtcfI/AAAAAAAABkU/2I7G8LsRERY/s2048/IMG_0676.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those of you paying &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-the-beginning/&#34;&gt;close attention&lt;/a&gt; will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog &lt;a href=&#34;http://reviewtheworld.com/&#34;&gt;reviewtheworld.com&lt;/a&gt;. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2013</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-top10-reviewtheworld-episodes-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-top10-reviewtheworld-episodes-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since Brian and Review the World were my main inspirations in starting my own blog, I figured it would be fitting to begin by introducing some of my favorite episodes from the past year. According to Brian, 2013 was one of the busiest years he&amp;rsquo;s ever had on the site, and it shows. He had a ton of great content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;10-the-brian-and-tim-show-episode-25-halloween-extra---ufo-and-ghost-discussionhttpwwwreviewtheworldcom201310b-show-25-ufo-ghost-discussionhtmlm0&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/2013/10/b-show-25-ufo-ghost-discussion.html?m=0&#34;&gt;#10: The Brian and Tim Show Episode #25: Halloween Extra - UFO and Ghost Discussion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sort of an extended special segment of the 2013 Halloween episode, Brian and Tim decide to talk about their own experiences with the paranormal. Basically this was how my cousins and I spent many a late night when I was younger, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure by the end of this you&amp;rsquo;ll be talking to your screen wanting to add your two cents. Who knows? Maybe some of mine will get featured on this blog one day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3nAdksT_dCw&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning.</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-the-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-the-beginning/</guid>
      <description>My name is Toby.&#xA;In the spring of 2013 I discovered Brian Hammons&amp;rsquo; blog Review the World, and something inside clicked. Here was a guy — just slightly my junior — getting out and enjoying life with his friends, exploring his local environment, and generally on fire with all the possibilities that an ordinary life offers to those who know how to look for them. I had spent the bulk of 2012 doing all of those things with my two older kids while my wife was, for the most part (and regrettably), stuck at home working and/or gestating.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
