<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reviewtheworld.com on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/reviewtheworld.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reviewtheworld.com on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 22:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/reviewtheworld.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2013</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-top10-reviewtheworld-episodes-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-top10-reviewtheworld-episodes-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>Since Brian and Review the World were my main inspirations in starting my own blog, I figured it would be fitting to begin by introducing some of my favorite episodes from the past year. According to Brian, 2013 was one of the busiest years he&amp;rsquo;s ever had on the site, and it shows. He had a ton of great content.
#10: The Brian and Tim Show Episode #25: Halloween Extra - UFO and Ghost Discussion Sort of an extended special segment of the 2013 Halloween episode, Brian and Tim decide to talk about their own experiences with the paranormal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning.</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-the-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-the-beginning/</guid>
      <description>My name is Toby.
In the spring of 2013 I discovered Brian Hammons&#39; blog Review the World, and something inside clicked. Here was a guy — just slightly my junior — getting out and enjoying life with his friends, exploring his local environment, and generally on fire with all the possibilities that an ordinary life offers to those who know how to look for them. I had spent the bulk of 2012 doing all of those things with my two older kids while my wife was, for the most part (and regrettably), stuck at home working and/or gestating.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
