<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thevcubesolver on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/thevcubesolver/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thevcubesolver on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 11:26:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/thevcubesolver/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Geocaching Lost Episodes</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/geocaching-lost-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/geocaching-lost-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Over the years I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated a ton of never-used footage from our various geocaching adventures. Here they all are, wrapped up a big ball of video for you, my Tobyblogging public.
Enjoy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Meganerd Fun Pack!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-meganerd-fun-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-meganerd-fun-pack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1507/26490173342_5105efd276_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Super Meganerd Fun Pack&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;The Super Meganerd Fun Pack — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/26490173342/&#34; title=&#34;The Super Meganerd Fun Pack&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What the pack?!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My cousin Carl, &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/&#34;&gt;as previously featured on Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt;, sent this to me for my birthday. Get a load. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like he knows me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Play Mario Party 10</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/we-play-mario-party-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/we-play-mario-party-10/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I play Mario Party 10, the most inexplicably hated Mario Party of them all!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversations 2 – Thoughts on the Wii U</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/conversations-2-thoughts-on-the-wii-u/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/conversations-2-thoughts-on-the-wii-u/</guid>
      <description>TheVCubeSolver and I talk about the things we love about the Nintendo Wii U on a long drive home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Play Wii Play Playthrough</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/we-play-wii-play-playthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/we-play-wii-play-playthrough/</guid>
      <description>TheVCubeSolver and I team up in this playthrough vid to reintroduce you to a seriously underrated classic on the Wii.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Hour&#39;s Wreck the Halls</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1695/23471270343_deab39ff5a_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Wreck the Halls — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/23471270343/&#34; title=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;2015 was the year I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tobyblog.com/2015/09/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever.html&#34;&gt;Dark Hour Haunted House&lt;/a&gt;, and you probably realize by now what a fan I am. We are very fortunate to live in an area with access to a year round haunt. To be able to be successful at that requires a level of quality and showmanship, frankly, above your average haunt. Not to detract from anyone else in the business (no one can do it all!), but I think it does hold true. In getting to know these guys and the haunt itself a little better over these past few months, it is becoming clear how much of an inspiration they are to other folks in the industry. And I&amp;rsquo;ve still not yet discovered all they have to offer!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tobyblog Thanksgiving Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-thanksgiving-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-thanksgiving-special/</guid>
      <description>After taking some time off to contemplate the overwhelming success of my Burger King poop tweet*, we now return to our regularly scheduled programming.
In truth October is always a busy month for us and I don&amp;rsquo;t have much spare time for blogging. This past Halloween was without a doubt the best yet, but I&amp;rsquo;ll save that retrospective for another day. For today we find ourselves at the end of November, as grand a month as any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</guid>
      <description>I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&#39;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&#39;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&#39;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&#39;t get caught!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprechers Root Beer Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating our third anniversary of Buddy Team reviews, TheVCubeSolver and I team up to tackle the legendary Sprechers Root Beer. It&amp;rsquo;s good stuff!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kranky Coffee</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Straight off a Dollar Store shelf at the lovely Grapevine Mills Mall in Grapevine, Texas, and stocked just a few bins over from the storied Orchard Skittles, comes Kranky Candy, the coffee dusted confection you will soon come to know and love. Is it an afternoon snack? A breakfast substitute? Repurposed industrial by-product? You decide.
Joining me in his first proper appearance* on Tobyblog is my good friend Brian Hammons of ReviewTheWorld.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversations Series: The Nintendo NX</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/conversations-series-the-nintendo-nx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/conversations-series-the-nintendo-nx/</guid>
      <description>Join TheVCubeSolver and I as we discuss the recently announced NX project from Nintendo, a new and novel system that could be the successor to the beleaguered Wii U. But what exactly is it? For the moment, all we can do is guess. But I think we have some good ideas.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March Cache Maintenance</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/march-cache-maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/march-cache-maintenance/</guid>
      <description>TheVCubeSolver and I hit the road on a pretty March morning to do some maintenance on a couple of our geocaches. The log for RtW #3 had filled up and Augie&amp;rsquo;s beaver cache had recently been reported missing. A little town, a little country. More geocaching goodness for you.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Night Cache</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/my-first-night-cache/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/my-first-night-cache/</guid>
      <description>Come along with the kids and I on our first night caching adventure. For the uninitiated among you, night caching is simply geocaching at night. Generally night caches are made so that you can&amp;rsquo;t find them during the daytime, by making use of trails of reflective tacks or tape or other forms of guidance visible only at night.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tobyblog Halloween Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-halloween-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-halloween-special/</guid>
      <description>I love Halloween. You do, too. This video is a tribute to that season, to every memory and every thrill. To cold autumn nights. To the warm glow of jack o&amp;rsquo; lanterns. To spooky stories and cozy evenings. To every bit of magic and adventure in our lives.
This is the story of Halloween 2013 as we experienced it; what has gone down in our lives and memories as THE BEST HALLOWEEN EVER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retropalooza</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/retropalooza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/retropalooza/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I took the kids to the amazing Retropalooza convention in Arlington, Texas, and boy did we have a blast! There were loads and loads of dealer tables with some very cool nostalgia items on display, classic and rare games galore, cosplayers, and even a few YouTube celebrities. Take a look at some of the fun things we discovered.
The owner of Tendril here was willing to let him go for a meagre forty dollars, making it the best deal I found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit To The Toy Store</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-the-toy-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-the-toy-store/</guid>
      <description>The great thing about being a dad to small kids is that you always have a built-in excuse to be in the toy aisle. And if you have your kids with you then nobody looks twice at you as you gawk at all the amazing stuff on the store shelves these days. We are living in a golden age for toys and board games. Sure, there were a lot of really cool toys that I miss from the seventies and eighties that I wish my kids had a chance to experience, but today&#39;s market offers a certain quality and vast variety of toys and other amusements that the old days could never touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wylie&#39;s Angel</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/wylies-angel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/wylies-angel/</guid>
      <description>I like geocaching for lots of reasons. I like to be outside. I like discovering new places. I like&amp;nbsp;walking and connecting with nature. But occasionally I learn something as well. Usually it&amp;rsquo;s just local historical trivia, or maybe a&amp;nbsp;geography&amp;nbsp;lesson. But sometimes the lesson is more personal, and as in this case, tragic.
The morning started out with a trip to the Trinity Trails in Wylie, Texas for some hiking and caching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kryptonite Kandy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kryptonite-kandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kryptonite-kandy/</guid>
      <description>Another bonus retro review! TheVCubeSolver hits up Popcorn Papa and takes a look at some very green rock candy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taki&#39;s, Cane Sugar Soda Pops</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</guid>
      <description>This is an older review from TheVCubeSolver and I very much inspired by the hijinks of Brian Hammons and the gang over at Review the World. In it we take a look at a couple of different varieties of Taki&amp;rsquo;s chips and some cane sugar soda pops we picked up at the local coffee shop.
Oh, and you&amp;rsquo;ll notice I&amp;rsquo;m calling myself &amp;ldquo;Meeks, the Pedestrian&amp;rdquo;. Cause we were trying to have code names or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Winter Open</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/houston-winter-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/houston-winter-open/</guid>
      <description>Footage from the Houston Winter Open speedcubing competition.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon! Houston Winter Open</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/coming-soon-houston-winter-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/coming-soon-houston-winter-open/</guid>
      <description>A teaser for my upcoming documentary on the Houston Winter Open 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</guid>
      <description>Back in the summer of 2013 TheVCubeSolver and I dropped by the local candy shop to review Blue Bunny&amp;rsquo;s Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes, a push-pop like product in three weird flavors. It turned out to be a complete and total sensory experience.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>