<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>restaurants on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/restaurants/</link>
    <description>Recent content in restaurants on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/restaurants/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Toe 2 Toe&#34; Review: Chili Cheese Fries</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2014 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</guid>
      <description>THE CONTENDERS:
Melter&amp;rsquo;s (Irving)
melty burgers and loaded baked potatoes14 year old native Dallas establishment2 locations, downtown Dallas &amp;amp; Irvinglow key atmosphere with an emphasis on the food&amp;nbsp;vs.Burger Fi (Garland)upscale burgers and hot dogsFlorida chain with scores of locations&amp;nbsp;around the country50s/60s diner aestheticthick, home-cut fries and real angus beef
MELTERS&amp;nbsp;
Melters&amp;rsquo; chili cheese fries were the first and, so far, only thing I&amp;rsquo;ve had off of their menu, but I&amp;rsquo;m already impressed with the place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Naan Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/</guid>
      <description>Go back, right now, and take a look at my Zyka India Food restaurant review. Notice anything suspicious about the Chicken 65? Take a closer look at those ingredients. 

Jalapenos. Onions. Cilantro. Sound familiar? 
If you&amp;rsquo;re from Texas or anywhere in the Southwest you would immediately associate that combination with Mexican or Tex-Mex cuisine. There are other similarities, too, like the general spiciness, the use of chilis, or the penchant for using circular flatbread at every meal to sandwich ingredients and sop up sauces.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>