<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>seasons on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/seasons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in seasons on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 15:54:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/seasons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Decorator&#39;s Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>The Decorator&#39;s Warehouse, located in Arlington, Texas, bills itself as Texas&#39;s largest Christmas store. And it is very large. But what really impresses you upon entering the place is just how jam-packed it is with holiday and seasonal baubles, as if despite its football-field size floor space they still did not have quite enough room to fit everything.&amp;nbsp;
As soon as you walk in the door you&#39;re assaulted with holiday cheer; the entrance is rather elaborately decorated and serves as both a picture station and portal of sorts into this alternate dimension that feels something like Santa&#39;s attic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aisles &amp; Aisles of Halloween at At Home </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/aisles-aisles-of-halloween-at-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/aisles-aisles-of-halloween-at-at-home/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re just under 100 days to Halloween now, but there are certain places you can always depend on to roll out the spooky stock a little early. I covered At Home last year and this year&#39;s selection looks bigger and better than ever. For 2015 our local store has literally doubled the floor space devoted to Halloween goods. And, well, just take a look for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Dias De Los Muertos at World Market</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</guid>
      <description>Already a great place to find exotic candies, foreign soda pop, and specialty food items at any time of the year (Brian Hammons, you know what I&#39;m talking about), World Market really comes alive for Halloween. If you&#39;ve got one in your area, get down there right now and check their selection. The stuff they carry is definitely outside of the Target/Big Lots/Dollar Store Halloween mold, but that&#39;s not to say it&#39;s super expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
