<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review the World on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/review-the-world/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review the World on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 15:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/review-the-world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucc-ees Beaver Nuggets with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bucc-ees-beaver-nuggets-with-review-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bucc-ees-beaver-nuggets-with-review-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Join Brian and I in downtown Garland, Texas as we dish on one of the state’s finest contributions to the culinary world, Beaver Nuggets.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cauldron Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:53:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Joined once again by nostalgia blogger and good friend Brian Hammons of reviewtheworld.com, Augie and I team up to complete our trilogy of Skittles reviews, this time looking at the legendary and rarely sighted Cauldron Skittles variety, now in its second year on store shelves. Does the candy itself live up to the promise of its bright orange bag? We find out, and the answer may just shock you. (It probably won&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brightside Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 15:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</guid>
      <description>Join me, Augie, and superpal Brian of Review the World for installment number two in this soon to be classic trilogy of Skittles candy reviews. This time we look at Brightside Skittles, the very flipside of the Darkside reviewed a couple of years back with Brian on his last visit to Dallas. A great theme for summer and sunny days, will Brightside warm your tummy as we slip into fall and all things pumpkin spice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Skittles Review with Brian</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 23:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, folks.
It has been a while now since I&amp;rsquo;ve been active on this site, but life has not held still for me and the family. Since the last time I posted anything of significance, quite a great deal has happened, actually, much of which was originally destined for publication here. Well, as it does, life got in the way, priorities shifted, my free time diminished, etc. etc. — and the gist of it all is that you folks were left unattended for many months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2015-2016</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again folks, that magical time between Christmas and New Year where thoughtful commentators like myself come out with their end of year retrospectives; and continuing a tradition I established a couple of years back on this site, I intend to give you my take on the best of my buddy Brian Hammons&amp;rsquo; output over on the internet&amp;rsquo;s most beloved nostalgia blog, ReviewTheWorld.com.
You can catch up on previous years&amp;rsquo; content by taking a look at my other lists:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</guid>
      <description>I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&#39;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&#39;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&#39;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&#39;t get caught!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprechers Root Beer Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating our third anniversary of Buddy Team reviews, TheVCubeSolver and I team up to tackle the legendary Sprechers Root Beer. It&amp;rsquo;s good stuff!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kranky Coffee</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Straight off a Dollar Store shelf at the lovely Grapevine Mills Mall in Grapevine, Texas, and stocked just a few bins over from the storied Orchard Skittles, comes Kranky Candy, the coffee dusted confection you will soon come to know and love. Is it an afternoon snack? A breakfast substitute? Repurposed industrial by-product? You decide.
Joining me in his first proper appearance* on Tobyblog is my good friend Brian Hammons of ReviewTheWorld.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noshing Tacos with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/noshing-tacos-with-review-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/noshing-tacos-with-review-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Once again we were proud to host buddy Brian Hammons of the food/candy/retro/life blog Review the World as he made his way down to Dallas for the big UFC 185 fight night. What a weekend! Among other things, I introduced Brian Hammons to some of the best tacos in the COUNTRY. Go see what resulted over on reviewtheworld.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2014/</guid>
      <description>One thing I love is end of year retrospectives. And in the grand tradition I started last year, I offer to you the top ten Review the World episodes of 2014. So clear your personal calendars, grab a bag of Rap Snacks, and settle in the for the show. These are all episodes I love, and I encourage you to watch every one in its entirety.
#10: Childhood Neighborhood Tour We begin with Brian&amp;rsquo;s most recent entry, one that was intended to cap all of his furious activity for 2014, and at one point, possibly forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2013</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>Since Brian and Review the World were my main inspirations in starting my own blog, I figured it would be fitting to begin by introducing some of my favorite episodes from the past year. According to Brian, 2013 was one of the busiest years he&amp;rsquo;s ever had on the site, and it shows. He had a ton of great content.
#10: The Brian and Tim Show Episode #25: Halloween Extra - UFO and Ghost Discussion Sort of an extended special segment of the 2013 Halloween episode, Brian and Tim decide to talk about their own experiences with the paranormal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>