<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>review the world on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/review-the-world/</link>
    <description>Recent content in review the world on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 15:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/review-the-world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bucc-ees Beaver Nuggets with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bucc-ees-beaver-nuggets-with-review-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bucc-ees-beaver-nuggets-with-review-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Join Brian and I in downtown Garland, Texas as we dish on one of the state’s finest contributions to the culinary world, Beaver Nuggets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cauldron Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:53:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Joined once again by nostalgia blogger and good friend Brian Hammons of reviewtheworld.com, Augie and I team up to complete our trilogy of Skittles reviews, this time looking at the legendary and rarely sighted Cauldron Skittles variety, now in its second year on store shelves. Does the candy itself live up to the promise of its bright orange bag? We find out, and the answer may just shock you. (It probably won&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brightside Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 15:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</guid>
      <description>Join me, Augie, and superpal Brian of Review the World for installment number two in this soon to be classic trilogy of Skittles candy reviews. This time we look at Brightside Skittles, the very flipside of the Darkside reviewed a couple of years back with Brian on his last visit to Dallas. A great theme for summer and sunny days, will Brightside warm your tummy as we slip into fall and all things pumpkin spice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Skittles Review with Brian</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 23:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, folks.
It has been a while now since I&amp;rsquo;ve been active on this site, but life has not held still for me and the family. Since the last time I posted anything of significance, quite a great deal has happened, actually, much of which was originally destined for publication here. Well, as it does, life got in the way, priorities shifted, my free time diminished, etc. etc. — and the gist of it all is that you folks were left unattended for many months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprechers Root Beer Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating our third anniversary of Buddy Team reviews, TheVCubeSolver and I team up to tackle the legendary Sprechers Root Beer. It&amp;rsquo;s good stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kranky Coffee</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Straight off a Dollar Store shelf at the lovely Grapevine Mills Mall in Grapevine, Texas, and stocked just a few bins over from the storied Orchard Skittles, comes Kranky Candy, the coffee dusted confection you will soon come to know and love. Is it an afternoon snack? A breakfast substitute? Repurposed industrial by-product? You decide.
Joining me in his first proper appearance* on Tobyblog is my good friend Brian Hammons of ReviewTheWorld.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
