<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</title>
    <link>https://tobyblog.com/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 16:30:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tobyblog.com/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dandelion Wine — Chapter One</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/dandelion-wine-chapter-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 16:30:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/dandelion-wine-chapter-one/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One night each week he was allowed to leave his father, his mother, and his younger brother Tom asleep in their small house next door and run here, up the dark spiral stairs to his grandparents&amp;rsquo; cupola, and in this sorcerer&amp;rsquo;s tower sleep with thunders and visions, to wake befor the crystal jingle of milk bottles and perform his ritual magic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dandelion Wine — A Book for Summer</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/dandelion-wine-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 16:19:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/dandelion-wine-01/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1589491164/img/dandelion-small.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What you have here in this book then is a gathering of dandelions from all those years. The wine metaphor which appears again and again in these pages is wonderfully apt. I was gathering images all of my life, storing them away, and forgetting them. Somehow I had to send myself back, with words as catalysts to open the memories out and see what they had to offer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ray Bradbury, Just This Side of Byzantium — An Introduction, Dandelion Wine&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Summer doesn&amp;rsquo;t officially arrive for a while, but after an hour out in the Texas sun on my quarantine walk, you can start to feel the sweat pooling around your neck and dripping down your scalp. I saw somebody on Twitter recommending this as a good time to start reading (or re-reading) Ray Bradbury&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Dandelion Wine.&lt;/em&gt; Why not?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live Forever</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/live-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 11:05:44 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/live-forever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1586966702/img/IMG_6769.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This popped up on my Twitter this morning from a unexpected and practically random source. The following story is told in Sam Weller&amp;rsquo;s biography of Ray Bradbury.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chef Roy Choi</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190507-chef-roy-choi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190507-chef-roy-choi/</guid>
      <description>Last night’s story time for the kid. I like to get into it, so I started to read it like I was spitting bars, street style. After a few pages he asked me to stop spitting on him. 🎤🔥</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lenten Meditation </title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190328-a-lenten-meditation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190328-a-lenten-meditation/</guid>
      <description>The soul has to make a choice, and the outcome will either break it into pieces or enable it to sail to its destination in God. And the choice comes down to this: Will the soul accept or reject suffering? Will it make this suffering its own, or struggle against it, seeing it as something alien to itself?&#xA;&amp;hellip;If he chooses to accept his suffering, he must embrace it with the wholeness of his life; he must discover and accept the proper relation to his suffering.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Love, She Weeps At Many Things</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190228-robot-mice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 01:41:02 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190228-robot-mice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/7896/46298054945_7fc2b02e2f_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Nightstand&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My love, she weeps at many things,&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I would not for the world stop up her tears;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;She came in many years of drought&lt;br&gt;&#xA;And taught me just how right was private rain&lt;br&gt;&#xA;To touch the dust with smallest storm &lt;br&gt;&#xA;With emerald droppings from her eyes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Death of Ivan Ilyich</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20181024-the-death-of-ivan-ilyich/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 02:11:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20181024-the-death-of-ivan-ilyich/</guid>
      <description>The Death of Ivan Ilyich, Leo Tolstoy. Chapter XII From that moment the screaming began that continued for three days, and was so terrible that one could not hear it through two closed doors without horror. At the moment he answered his wife he realized that he was lost, that there was no return, that the end had come, the very end, and his doubts were still unsolved and remained doubts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Air</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20181024-fresh-air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 02:03:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20181024-fresh-air/</guid>
      <description>Crime and Punishment, Fyodor Dostoyevsky. Part 6, Chapter 2. &amp;ldquo;You must fulfill the demands of justice. I know that you don&amp;rsquo;t believe it, but indeed, life will bring you through. You will live it down in time. What you need now is fresh air, fresh air, fresh air!&amp;rdquo;&amp;quot;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mask of the Red Death</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/the-mask-of-the-red-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/the-mask-of-the-red-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-LG5tJUTc_xU/VEJuvEURinI/AAAAAAAABis/MisjKk3frhA/s2048/IMG_2405.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &amp;lsquo;Red Death&amp;rsquo; had long devastated the country. No pestilence had ever been so fatal, or so hideous. Blood was its Avatar and its seal — the redness and the horror of blood. There were sharp pains, and sudden dizziness, and then profuse bleeding at the pores, with dissolution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
