<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christmas on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/christmas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christmas on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:44:08 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/christmas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few of My Favorite Christmas Songs</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-12-21-my-favorite-christmas-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:44:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-12-21-my-favorite-christmas-songs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/S6wDzvibd_Q&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Hands down my favorite Christmas song of 2018. I passed up this album in favor of Jackie Gleason&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Tis The Season&lt;/em&gt;, a purchase I do not regret, but this song is definitely worth the price of the vinyl. I love it when Frank sings melancholy, and this one has that quality in spades. Nostalgia, regret, and loneliness are all wrapped up in that golden bow of his amazing voice, a voice that forces your ears to attention when you hear it, never aging, never dulling, calling your life before your eyes, and all but materializing that glass of whiskey or scotch in your left hand, as your right hand reaches to pull the brim of your fedora down a little more to cover the tears in your eyes. Merry Christmas!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August into December at the Holiday Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/august-into-december-at-the-holiday-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/august-into-december-at-the-holiday-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8449/28674407714_ef688b56a7_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mr. Pumpkin&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Mr. Pumpkin — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/28674407714/&#34; title=&#34;Mr. Pumpkin&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.holidaywarehouse.com/&#34;&gt;Holiday Warehouse&lt;/a&gt; is a largish, and rather outstanding, independent holiday decor shop located in Plano, Texas. Like its well known cousin The &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/&#34;&gt;Decorator&amp;rsquo;s Warehouse&lt;/a&gt; in Arlington, the concentration is mainly on Christmas, but not as exclusively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Hour&#39;s Wreck the Halls</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1695/23471270343_deab39ff5a_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Wreck the Halls — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/23471270343/&#34; title=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;2015 was the year I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tobyblog.com/2015/09/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever.html&#34;&gt;Dark Hour Haunted House&lt;/a&gt;, and you probably realize by now what a fan I am. We are very fortunate to live in an area with access to a year round haunt. To be able to be successful at that requires a level of quality and showmanship, frankly, above your average haunt. Not to detract from anyone else in the business (no one can do it all!), but I think it does hold true. In getting to know these guys and the haunt itself a little better over these past few months, it is becoming clear how much of an inspiration they are to other folks in the industry. And I&amp;rsquo;ve still not yet discovered all they have to offer!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Decorator&#39;s Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>The Decorator&amp;rsquo;s Warehouse, located in Arlington, Texas, bills itself as Texas&amp;rsquo;s largest Christmas store. And it is very large. But what really impresses you upon entering the place is just how jam-packed it is with holiday and seasonal baubles, as if despite its football-field size floor space they still did not have quite enough room to fit everything.&amp;nbsp;
As soon as you walk in the door you&amp;rsquo;re assaulted with holiday cheer; the entrance is rather elaborately decorated and serves as both a picture station and portal of sorts into this alternate dimension that feels something like Santa&amp;rsquo;s attic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>