<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/categories/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 15:13:21 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/categories/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Parish Brewing</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/parish-brewing-louisiana-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 15:13:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/parish-brewing-louisiana-beer/</guid>
      <description>Looks to me like South Louisiana microbrews are coming of age. I think the time has come to get my hand on a few of these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detective Pikachu Was As Good As It Could Be</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190514-detective-pikachu-was-as-good-as-it-could-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190514-detective-pikachu-was-as-good-as-it-could-be/</guid>
      <description>In other news, I saw Detective Pikachu with the family a few days ago, and I think we all left impressed. Some strong acting and genuinely funny moments. Pikachu singing the Pokémon cartoon theme song was a highlight for me. But does Ryan Reynolds have to be in literally every movie now? That being said, he did a wonderful job. A really enjoyable and charming movie. Go see it. With your kids, of course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got the Munchies? Try Hypnotic Donuts.</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190501-hypnotic-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190501-hypnotic-donuts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1558136445/img/36C549F3-4677-426F-8ECB-3E7C87F986F1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a rainy, Seattle-y Saturday morning in Dallas when I decided to take the kids out for a Daddy-Daughter-Baby Day run to Hypnotic Donuts, one of those fancy donut places that seem to be popping up around town these days like vape shops were five about years ago. They&amp;rsquo;d been asking me to take them on a Pokémon hunt, and I decided I&amp;rsquo;d treat them to breakfast as a bonus and incentive for getting up extra early.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three New Pasadena Restaurants </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190419-three-new-pasadena-restaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190419-three-new-pasadena-restaurants/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1555717674/img/ABB60CD5-A457-4710-A103-8E22A15D25DC.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have decided that when presented with a choice between the familiar and the new, I am going to lean in favor of new experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cajun Treats</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/cajun-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 21:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/cajun-treats/</guid>
      <description>This video is something of a personal achievement, having been now just under two years in the making, and passing, as it does, yet another milestone in the revitalization of this little blog. Yeah, I know, that&amp;rsquo;s sort of a grandiose way to introduce a video where I discuss the merits of quail eggs and potato chips with friends and family, but there we are. It means something to me — hard to quantify — to be active on the site again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Libre</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-taco-libre/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-taco-libre/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1552629476/img/576933C9-5E92-4C23-B1AF-8B342EF82BDF.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather was warmer today. I could feel spring in my bones. I get that way around this time of year. Maybe I was feeling a little homesick. Whatever the case, I&amp;rsquo;ve been craving Mexican food. I noticed this little while walking around during my lunch break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I was standing outside the door reading the posted menuboard, an older lady passing by said to me &amp;ldquo;Go in. You&amp;rsquo;ll like it. It&amp;rsquo;s really good.&amp;rdquo; I took that as a sign.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Times at the El Portal</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-el-portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-el-portal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1552625591/img/761E75E1-8A2E-4D98-9348-5951E7436215.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took a detour that night after my trip to the antique store. I passed along back streets, out of the way plazas, anywhere that looked like it might afford me new scenery. I stumbled across El Portal behind the headquarters of the Planetary Society, its aromas drawing my attention before I&amp;rsquo;d even rounded the corner to lay site on the place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucc-ees Beaver Nuggets with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bucc-ees-beaver-nuggets-with-review-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bucc-ees-beaver-nuggets-with-review-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Join Brian and I in downtown Garland, Texas as we dish on one of the state’s finest contributions to the culinary world, Beaver Nuggets.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasadena Eats</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180520-pasadena-eats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:59:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180520-pasadena-eats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/960/42132774932_29c870ce99_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Retro Store in Pasadena, California</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180510-the-retro-store-pasadena/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 16:42:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180510-the-retro-store-pasadena/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/946/42090262291_c42d9822cd_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween at Joanns Fabrics</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180406-halloween-at-joanns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 11:27:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180406-halloween-at-joanns/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/4373/36040402923_de601519f8_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Jack O&#39; Lantern Rug&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Sick</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20180328-so-sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:46:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20180328-so-sick/</guid>
      <description>Being sick on a trip is the worst. I&amp;rsquo;ve mostly been sleeping every spare moment I get. Managed to catch a pretty decent cheese ball of a movie, though. It was old school campy fun in the best way. Nicely captured the feel of old 80s schlock-horror movies like The Gate and Return of the Living Dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Latte Beer and Ace Pumpkin Cider</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20171124-pumpkin-latte-ace-pumpkin-cider/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 10:49:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20171124-pumpkin-latte-ace-pumpkin-cider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/4580/38604886832_fe51a449c7_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year while out shopping for turkey and wine, I discovered a couple of very fallish, and very Thanksgiving-appropriate beverages I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with you all. One is a new seasonal coffee brew from my favorite DFW brewery &lt;a href=&#34;http://martinhousebrewing.com/&#34;&gt;Martin House&lt;/a&gt;, and the other is a special cider I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in three years — &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160802-ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/&#34;&gt;Ace&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; own extraordinary Pumpkin Cider. Read on!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cauldron Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:53:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Joined once again by nostalgia blogger and good friend Brian Hammons of reviewtheworld.com, Augie and I team up to complete our trilogy of Skittles reviews, this time looking at the legendary and rarely sighted Cauldron Skittles variety, now in its second year on store shelves. Does the candy itself live up to the promise of its bright orange bag? We find out, and the answer may just shock you. (It probably won&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Lemax Village Pieces for 2017</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20170930-lemax-village-additions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 10:40:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20170930-lemax-village-additions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/4350/36014831924_f50f3785ae_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brightside Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 15:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</guid>
      <description>Join me, Augie, and superpal Brian of Review the World for installment number two in this soon to be classic trilogy of Skittles candy reviews. This time we look at Brightside Skittles, the very flipside of the Darkside reviewed a couple of years back with Brian on his last visit to Dallas. A great theme for summer and sunny days, will Brightside warm your tummy as we slip into fall and all things pumpkin spice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smells Like Halloween at Yankee Candle</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20170904-yankee-candle-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 09:41:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20170904-yankee-candle-halloween/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/4422/36040105263_2d20381447_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s in a smell? The power to evoke. Memories. People. Places. And special times in our lives. Seasons long forgotten. All brought back in an instant the second a particular aroma hits our nostrils. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that scented candles, long thought domain of grandmas and boring little gift shops, have become respected among the nostalgia set in recent years. I read once that people don&amp;rsquo;t remember scents; that you remember the things associated with it or the strong feelings the scent creates, but the brain does not store memory of the scent itself. And now I find myself trying to remember what the woods smell like in autumn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Skittles Review with Brian</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 23:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, folks.
It has been a while now since I&amp;rsquo;ve been active on this site, but life has not held still for me and the family. Since the last time I posted anything of significance, quite a great deal has happened, actually, much of which was originally destined for publication here. Well, as it does, life got in the way, priorities shifted, my free time diminished, etc. etc. — and the gist of it all is that you folks were left unattended for many months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2015-2016</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20170101-top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20170101-top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again folks, that magical time between Christmas and New Year where thoughtful commentators like myself come out with their end of year retrospectives; and continuing a tradition I established a couple of years back on this site, I intend to give you my take on the best of my buddy Brian Hammons&#39; output over on the internet&amp;rsquo;s most beloved nostalgia blog, ReviewTheWorld.com.
You can catch up on previous years&#39; content by taking a look at my other lists:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August into December at the Holiday Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160911-august-into-december-at-the-holiday-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160911-august-into-december-at-the-holiday-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/8430/29188949732_55bd1cfc2f_o.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mr. Pumpkin&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.holidaywarehouse.com/&#34;&gt;Holiday Warehouse&lt;/a&gt; is a largish, and rather outstanding, independent holiday decor shop located in Plano, Texas. Like its well known cousin The &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150826-the-decorators-warehouse/&#34;&gt;Decorator&amp;rsquo;s Warehouse&lt;/a&gt; in Arlington, the concentration is mainly on Christmas, but not as exclusively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bollywood Burrito</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160811-the-bollywood-burrito/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160811-the-bollywood-burrito/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Sq3xak90kZg/V6zwoaw0I7I/AAAAAAAAC40/evK2MCidSAEDtEYEMePNyQVFAWYgzkF1QCLcB/s2048/IMG_5441.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember Taco Naan, the Mexican-Indian hybrid restaurant &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140226-taco-naan-review/&#34;&gt;I wrote about&lt;/a&gt; a long time back? I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the very same one my buddy &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/2015/03/texas-taco-challenge-taco-naan-vs-fuel.html&#34;&gt;Brian featured&lt;/a&gt; on his second trip to the Big D, where he stacked up its offerings against the nationally renowned taco dive Fuel City. Well, they&amp;rsquo;re still around and busier and better than ever! The place is expanding like mad, doubling its interior floor space and hopefully renovating those dismal restrooms. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know because I&amp;rsquo;ve never had the courage to try them again. But you don&amp;rsquo;t go to Taco Naan to use the bathroom, man, so no worries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Czech Stop and Slovaceks</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-czech-stop-and-slovaceks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-czech-stop-and-slovaceks/</guid>
      <description>After a long hiatus, my front seat food review series is back! This time I feature some of the Waco area&amp;rsquo;s finest gas station Czech cuisine. If you&amp;rsquo;re ever in the area you should absolutely stop at one or both of these fine establishments. Such a treat.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Pineapple Cider &amp; Shannon Irish Red</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160802-ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160802-ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/8520/28657569041_a2ed23b73f_o.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ace Pineapple Cider&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beer is great year-round, but summer brings its own varieties. I noticed recently that hard ciders are becoming more popular. I had a chance to sample a new one from Ace, makers of an outstanding pumpkin cider that I am very much looking forward to having again this fall. Their pear cider, available in all seasons, merits a future review. But this one I had not seen before.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing 30th Anniversary Movies</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160606-amazing-30th-anniversary-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160606-amazing-30th-anniversary-movies/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the 30th anniversary of two very special, very &amp;ldquo;eighties&amp;rdquo; movies that I happen to love. The (legitimate) Transformers The Movie, and Space Camp, which I watched for the first time only a year or so ago with the kids.
I honestly can&amp;rsquo;t remember when I first saw the Transformers movie, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the theaters. I was the only one of my group of friends that caught it months, if not years later, after it came out on VHS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sfanthor! House of Wax</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160415-sfanthor-house-of-wax/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160415-sfanthor-house-of-wax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/1549/25950434656_93b18a4748_o.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tobyblog and creep&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here in North Texas the sun is shining. The weather is warming up. The world outside is getting brighter. The Texas wildflowers are already in bloom, thanks to a mild and soggy winter. In the woods, things are moving. The itchy season is upon us, and the window of opportunity for a lot of local geocaches is closing, as the casual players tend to steer clear of anything that might put them in the way of tall grass, poison ivy, or the dreaded tick.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lights Out For Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160121-lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160121-lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/1666/23960351439_7b05ad37c0_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you remember &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150410-a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/&#34;&gt;Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt?&lt;/a&gt; I wrote about that place around this time last year. It&amp;rsquo;s closed now. I had a dream about it the other night, or rather its next incarnation, which was as a hybrid Christmas/Halloween store. I know the owners have an interest in Christmas things, so that detail is not too surprising. But in my dream, there was also a functional toilet over by the register. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what that was supposed to mean.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Hour&#39;s Wreck the Halls</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160101-dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20160101-dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/5714/23469822034_1c729f586f_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2015 was the year I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150921-the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/&#34;&gt;Dark Hour Haunted House&lt;/a&gt;, and you probably realize by now what a fan I am. We are very fortunate to live in an area with access to a year round haunt. To be able to be successful at that requires a level of quality and showmanship, frankly, above your average haunt. Not to detract from anyone else in the business (no one can do it all!), but I think it does hold true. In getting to know these guys and the haunt itself a little better over these past few months, it is becoming clear how much of an inspiration they are to other folks in the industry. And I&amp;rsquo;ve still not yet discovered all they have to offer!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150921-the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150921-the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-2FRIs6Ct-Fc/VgDXNDwW06I/AAAAAAAACcY/NajCMB6v3Rc/s2048/DH17.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&amp;rsquo;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&amp;rsquo;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&amp;rsquo;t get caught! Cause you know, awkward.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprechers Root Beer Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating our third anniversary of Buddy Team reviews, TheVCubeSolver and I team up to tackle the legendary Sprechers Root Beer. It&amp;rsquo;s good stuff!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Spooks on YouTube: Apparitions</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150831-free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150831-free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for something spooky to watch as we wind our way down to Halloween, but find yourself bored by the usual fare of cheesy monster movies or gross slasher flicks? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re in the mood for something a little more thoughtful; a little more substantial, perhaps? Let me show you something interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DPDeV43LDds&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Decorator&#39;s Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150826-the-decorators-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150826-the-decorators-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-qpeZXgKa9cM/VcvUoyR-aJI/AAAAAAAACX0/cV2Hn4jOi9I/s2048/DSC04571.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Decorator&amp;rsquo;s Warehouse, located in Arlington, Texas, bills itself as Texas&amp;rsquo;s largest Christmas store. And it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; very large. But what really impresses you upon entering the place is just how jam-packed it is with holiday and seasonal baubles, as if despite its football-field size floor space they still did not have quite enough room to fit everything.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aisles &amp; Aisles of Halloween at At Home </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20150727-aisles-of-halloween-at-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20150727-aisles-of-halloween-at-at-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-Xivo-U5lONM/VbcX07M_97I/AAAAAAAACQs/mYKBdfkFbE8/s2048/IMG_0001.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bahama Bucks</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bahama-bucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bahama-bucks/</guid>
      <description>Katie and the gang over at Cheap Thrills invited me and the kids to do a co-review highlighting some of our favorite summer treats. You can check out their submission, Culver&amp;rsquo;s Frozen Custard, below.
  Naturally, I jumped at the chance to introduce you guys to one of the hidden treasures of our little neighborhood — Bahama Bucks!
Bucks is sort of like Jimmy Buffett&amp;rsquo;s own sno-cone stand. It serves sno-cones and tropical smoothies, some coffee drinks, and you can even get mixed fruit cups there if you&amp;rsquo;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kranky Coffee</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Straight off a Dollar Store shelf at the lovely Grapevine Mills Mall in Grapevine, Texas, and stocked just a few bins over from the storied Orchard Skittles, comes Kranky Candy, the coffee dusted confection you will soon come to know and love. Is it an afternoon snack? A breakfast substitute? Repurposed industrial by-product? You decide.
Joining me in his first proper appearance* on Tobyblog is my good friend Brian Hammons of ReviewTheWorld.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit to Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150410-a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150410-a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-5f6E4EuUntQ/VRbDEIWGqAI/AAAAAAAABws/owuiYxsrxGs/s2048/FullSizeRender%2B11.jpg&#34;
         alt=&#34;Dr. Channard from Hellraiser II, in all his glory&#34;/&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Dr. Channard from Hellraiser II, in all his glory&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt is a boutique shop in Dallas specializing in horror and sci-fi collectibles, memorabilia, paraphernalia, and… well, you just gotta see it, folks. It&amp;rsquo;s an amazing place. I discovered them only recently after attending the St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Slay Weekend event at &lt;a href=&#34;http://darkhourhauntedhouse.com/&#34;&gt;Dark Hour Haunted House&lt;/a&gt; in Plano. They were a sponsor of that particular show, so Dark Hour graciously gave them some floor space to sell a few wares after the show and otherwise promote the store. Now it&amp;rsquo;s not like Dallas has a whole lot of shops like this; in fact, I cannot think of &lt;em&gt;one other&lt;/em&gt;. So it piqued my interest. I noticed that they are located only a short distance across the river from where I currently work, so I decided to pop in on my next available lunch hour.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Chix Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20141203-super-chix-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20141203-super-chix-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-amX4B6z6bBM/VH_u7e2JqGI/AAAAAAAABpo/Lvwkw1Duirg/s2048/IMG_0346.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have reached &amp;ldquo;Peak Blogger&amp;rdquo; in this society, folks. If the existence of Tobyblog was not proof of that already, take a look at the above picture. It was a cold, blustery Saturday afternoon and I was visiting nearby Arlington. It was around lunchtime and I had some time to kill, so I decided to walk over to the nearby strip mall and scope out the restaurants. There were a surprising number of cuisines on offer for such a small area, but this place caught my eye. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/&#34;&gt;Brian Hammons&lt;/a&gt; had mentioned to me recently how his buddy Nick Van Bever is a fan of chicken strips and fries. I figured I&amp;rsquo;d do some recon for Nick, in case he ever makes his way down to Dallas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Dias De Los Muertos at World Market</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140927-los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140927-los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-jxBynb6fbbQ/VCa81QdRisI/AAAAAAAABYE/oDRuHs5PaBQ/s2048/DSC02222.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Already a great place to find exotic candies, foreign soda pop, and specialty food items at any time of the year (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/2014/09/3-green-sodas.html&#34;&gt;Brian Hammons&lt;/a&gt;, you know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about), World Market really comes alive for Halloween. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got one in your area, get down there right now and check their selection. The stuff they carry is definitely outside of the Target/Big Lots/Dollar Store Halloween mold, but that&amp;rsquo;s not to say it&amp;rsquo;s super expensive. This year the emphasis is (appropriately) on Halloween&amp;rsquo;s Mexican cousin, El Dia de los Muertos — The Day of the Dead — because of a merchandising tie-in with the upcoming movie &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bookoflifemovie.com/&#34;&gt;The Book of Life&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Dino Drac Funpack, Sep 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140906-opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-sep-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140906-opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-sep-2014/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-eJtzOcWGoH0/VAv1ERbJbhI/AAAAAAAABKQ/1KHejU1g0GU/s2048/DSC01904.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Dino Drac Funpack, Aug 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140906-opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-aug-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140906-opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-aug-2014/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-IYv6uEVZdEY/VAvxIKOraoI/AAAAAAAABGc/RrYVW7CQyUw/s2048/IMG_1735.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liver and Gizzards Review, with Sriracha Whoopie Pies</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/liver-and-gizzards-review-with-sriracha-whoopie-pies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/liver-and-gizzards-review-with-sriracha-whoopie-pies/</guid>
      <description>My buddy Brian Hammons over at Review the World requested another video food review, so I though I&amp;rsquo;d introduce him to a down-home treat from my childhood. I hope you&amp;rsquo;re happy with the results. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, this one is a bit of a deep dive; a little something for my hardcore devotees. That is, people that like watching me eat stuff in my car. And yes, I manage to add yet another stain to my car seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Halloween Village at Michaels</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140823-incredible-halloween-village-at-michaels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140823-incredible-halloween-village-at-michaels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-9EU7kxb09Y0/U_YwFMV_fLI/AAAAAAAAA6Q/EEIYtDJvZ4s/s2048/IMG_1667.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Halloween lovers everywhere, if you have never seen the Lemax Spooky Town collection at Michaels, find one near you and go there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snickers Varieties and Lays Cappuccino Chips</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/snickers-varieties-and-lays-cappuccino-chips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/snickers-varieties-and-lays-cappuccino-chips/</guid>
      <description>To celebrate the recent one year anniversary of our father/son Tumblr site, TheVCubeSolver and I teamed up to review an assortment of Snickers bars we found at CVS. And as a special bonus, we take a look at the trendy new Lays Cappuccino potato chips.
Enjoy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween at Big Lots</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140807-halloween-at-big-lots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140807-halloween-at-big-lots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-T4PPeI9JIWg/U-Kfhb6-DlI/AAAAAAAAAxs/AFXIe1xozHg/s1024/blogger-image-1422700385.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Greetings, friends! It&amp;rsquo;s been a few days since my last update, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t been idle. Have you noticed how early the stores are stocking for Halloween this year? I blogged about my first sighting at &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140726-halloween-has-arrived-at-at-home/&#34;&gt;At Home (formerly Garden Ridge)&lt;/a&gt; which was on July 1st, a full one month earlier than last year. (And if you&amp;rsquo;re interested, that was at a chain called Home Goods, where the theme of ravens &amp;amp; blackbirds predominated.) Naturally, I&amp;rsquo;ve been keeping an eye on the usual merchants ever since, and they have not disappointed!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yankee Candle Halloween Preview</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140803-yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140803-yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-6FJ3nuF1Rq0/U96JVc7d8MI/AAAAAAAAAvw/1XjHAlNOflA/s2048/IMG_1603.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yesterday Yankee Candle had a special one-day preview of their upcoming Halloween 2014 collection, and we dropped in to get a look. Thanks to &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/perkyjewels?lang=en&#34;&gt;PerkyJewels on Twitter&lt;/a&gt; for the tip-off!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Has Arrived at At Home</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140726-halloween-has-arrived-at-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140726-halloween-has-arrived-at-at-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-_gwhccKqpqY/U9SAkCQ1olI/AAAAAAAAAlA/cJhMhsf1OfE/s2048/IMG_1422.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Garden Ridge recently declared bankruptcy, and are now being reincorporated as At Home. But true to form, the seasons still come early there and stay late.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My dear wife noticed yesterday that one of the nearby stores had been refurbished, so we decided to drop in and check it out. I of course had high hopes for what to expect, and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropping Quarters</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140725-dropping-quarters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140725-dropping-quarters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a little independent retro gaming store in Plano that is the closest thing to a real arcade that I&amp;rsquo;ve ever experienced with the kids. There are still a lot of places you could call &amp;ldquo;arcades&amp;rdquo;, mostly attached to chain family restaurants like Chuck-E-Cheese or entertainment complexes like Fun Zone or Amazing Jakes. But the key differentiator for me is that the machines take real quarters, preferably only one per play. I always hated changing tokens, and to me the idea of plopping tokens into a machine screws with the mythology somehow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restroom Tissue Dispensers</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140724-restroom-tissue-dispensers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140724-restroom-tissue-dispensers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(Works best if you read this in an Andy Rooney-esque whine.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This keeps happening to me over and over and over again lately. I have to make use of the public facilities (seldom a delightful experience anyway), I go to the sink, wash my hands, look up, and see this mess —&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-54e0eSjh9S8/U9FwlwwqJqI/AAAAAAAAAkA/WBmtk8iqmGc/s640/blogger-image--541685519.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now what is wrong with this picture? Take a look at how this works.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Food Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140723-new-orleans-food-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140723-new-orleans-food-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-rHaibYXANIw/U8_Hy4ggYiI/AAAAAAAAAio/oW6JSP1QZeQ/s640/blogger-image-1201992581.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New Orleans is, of course, a city known for its food, home to some of the best chefs in the country. I was in town recently, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d check out some of the local establishments and give you guys a virtual sight-tasting tour. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the hotel vending machine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anniversary Candy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140619-anniversary-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140619-anniversary-candy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-xm0JFA17S_I/U6R9zcsBA4I/AAAAAAAAAew/h2zWFMTegHk/s640/blogger-image--2114821383.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aren&amp;rsquo;t I lucky? How many guys get to have a truly one of a kind candy made just for them?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Toe 2 Toe&#34; Review: Chili Cheese Fries</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140518-toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2014 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140518-toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE CONTENDERS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melter&amp;rsquo;s (Irving)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-GzMOCiX1j9E/U3Wap9B7m3I/AAAAAAAAAXo/5B7VYui7oaI/s2048/melters.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;melty burgers and loaded baked potatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;14 year old native Dallas establishment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 locations, downtown Dallas &amp;amp; Irving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;low key atmosphere with an emphasis on the food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;vs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Burger Fi (Garland)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-zpMVPy9mjiw/U3WbZ7lYInI/AAAAAAAAAXw/Y2IJ4-zwtdw/s2048/bfi.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;upscale burgers and hot dogs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Florida chain with scores of locations around the country&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;50s/60s diner aesthetic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;thick, home-cut fries and real angus beef&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kryptonite Kandy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kryptonite-kandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kryptonite-kandy/</guid>
      <description>Another bonus retro review! TheVCubeSolver hits up Popcorn Papa and takes a look at some very green rock candy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taki&#39;s, Cane Sugar Soda Pops</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</guid>
      <description>This is an older review from TheVCubeSolver and I very much inspired by the hijinks of Brian Hammons and the gang over at Review the World. In it we take a look at a couple of different varieties of Taki&amp;rsquo;s chips and some cane sugar soda pops we picked up at the local coffee shop.
Oh, and you&amp;rsquo;ll notice I&amp;rsquo;m calling myself &amp;ldquo;Meeks, the Pedestrian&amp;rdquo;. Cause we were trying to have code names or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Naan Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140226-taco-naan-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140226-taco-naan-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-kOWZdp1hKUM/Uw7fZHHQ_MI/AAAAAAAAASo/PaKzZurs9tA/s2048/Screen+Shot+2014-02-27+at+12.45.36+AM.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go back, right now, and take a look at my &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/videos/zyka-indian-food-review/&#34;&gt;Zyka India Food restaurant review.&lt;/a&gt; Notice anything suspicious about the Chicken 65? Take a closer look at those ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jalapenos. Onions. Cilantro. Sound familiar?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</guid>
      <description>Back in the summer of 2013 TheVCubeSolver and I dropped by the local candy shop to review Blue Bunny&amp;rsquo;s Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes, a push-pop like product in three weird flavors. It turned out to be a complete and total sensory experience.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zyka Indian Food Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zyka-indian-food-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zyka-indian-food-review/</guid>
      <description>I review some Indian food from my car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2013</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-top10-reviewtheworld-episodes-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140202-top10-reviewtheworld-episodes-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since Brian and Review the World were my main inspirations in starting my own blog, I figured it would be fitting to begin by introducing some of my favorite episodes from the past year. According to Brian, 2013 was one of the busiest years he&amp;rsquo;s ever had on the site, and it shows. He had a ton of great content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;10-the-brian-and-tim-show-episode-25-halloween-extra---ufo-and-ghost-discussionhttpwwwreviewtheworldcom201310b-show-25-ufo-ghost-discussionhtmlm0&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/2013/10/b-show-25-ufo-ghost-discussion.html?m=0&#34;&gt;#10: The Brian and Tim Show Episode #25: Halloween Extra - UFO and Ghost Discussion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sort of an extended special segment of the 2013 Halloween episode, Brian and Tim decide to talk about their own experiences with the paranormal. Basically this was how my cousins and I spent many a late night when I was younger, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure by the end of this you&amp;rsquo;ll be talking to your screen wanting to add your two cents. Who knows? Maybe some of mine will get featured on this blog one day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3nAdksT_dCw&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
