<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>travel on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in travel on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 10:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 09.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Arrived in beautiful Telluride, Colorado, and yes, this is my first update since day #2 of vacation. So much for my Travel Log. Between lack of cell signal and surrendering my phone to the kid, and straight up being too busy and/or exhausted, I haven’t had much opportunity for posting.
We’ve been busy!
Back to the Grand Canyon this year, and this time we got to spend a night in the park, with a chance to do some dawn/dusk shots of the canyon itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 02.02</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190803-road-trip-travel-log-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190803-road-trip-travel-log-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Finally made it to Red Rock State Park, and made a couple of new discoveries along the way. Our route took us through what turned out be the incredibly beautiful Coconino National Forest, a place we have vowed to return. If Tolkien’s Elves were a real thing, they might just choose to live in a place like that. Verdant green forests around the bases of giant granite mountains, interspersed all along the way with little villages and expensive looking cabin retreats, with lights hanging from the trees across bridges that span crystal clear mountain streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 02.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190802-road-trip-travel-log-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190802-road-trip-travel-log-02-01/</guid>
      <description>On the road from Albuquerque to Flagstaff, near which we turn south to Red Rock State Park in Arizona. The kids are keen to get in a hike today, the first “real” day of our vacation, as far as I’m concerned. It’s been fun watching the younger two get excited over taking pictures from the car with the little Instax Mini. That was Kassi’s great idea. We bought Anthony around 150 exposures and his eyes got wide when I told him I wanted him to use every single one by the end of the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 01.02</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190801-road-trip-travel-log-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190801-road-trip-travel-log-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Picture of me in the Llano Estacado, Texas’s “wine country”. On the road for quite a while and still not out of the state. Holding up well. Fear the little one may be coming down with a cold. Hope he’s better after some rest.
Changed restaurant plans and will revisit our old favorite in Albuquerque for the third year in a row.
The food there has always been great, though the service is consistently slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 01.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190801-road-trip-travel-log-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190801-road-trip-travel-log-01-01/</guid>
      <description>We’re well in to the big family road trip of 2019, and the obligatory Texas pit stop at Bucc-ees has been checked off the list. Would have sent you guys a pic from the storied Bucc-ees bathrooms, but I was too excited about these new hot n’ spicy Beaver Nuggets! You can hear all about my first experience with those glorified Corn Pops in this review I did last year with my good buddy Brian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bits and Bobs</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190710-bits-and-bobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 17:33:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190710-bits-and-bobs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1562790874/img/IMG_3630.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made a promise to myself that I would never waste time on this blog apologizing for sporadic posting. So instead of doing that, I think I&amp;rsquo;ll do that other thing where I throw a few pictures at you and catch you up on recent developments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Thing?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190614-lax-sound-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 16:54:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190614-lax-sound-tour/</guid>
      <description>I decided to do something today I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to do for quite a while. I&amp;rsquo;m bringing back what they used to call in the early days of podcasting &amp;ldquo;soundseeing tours&amp;rdquo;, wherein people just recorded the ambient sounds of interesting places they visited or things they were doing. Not much time to do a writeup on this, as I&amp;rsquo;m about to board my flight, but here you can join me on my customary walk from Tom Bradley International terminal across the length and breadth of the airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three New Pasadena Restaurants </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190419-three-new-pasadena-restaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190419-three-new-pasadena-restaurants/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1555717674/img/ABB60CD5-A457-4710-A103-8E22A15D25DC.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have decided that when presented with a choice between the familiar and the new, I am going to lean in favor of new experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>45</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190418-45/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190418-45/</guid>
      <description>Today I had a lot of reminders that there are people out there who love and care for me a great deal. My wife, parents, and children. My brothers, cousins, and family. Friends old and new. I am thankful for all of them. I am thankful for the things I have, inside and out. I am thankful for the places God has brought me to in the past year.
I met a man on the street named Emery Lambus who asked me for a couple of bucks to buy lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasadena in Bloom</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190415-pasadena-in-bloom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190415-pasadena-in-bloom/</guid>
      <description>The streets of Old Town Pasadena are lined this April in pink and purple blooms. A little natural spring beauty. Something of a birthday treat from God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roof Access</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190415-roof-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190415-roof-access/</guid>
      <description>I get irrationally excited when I see ROOF ACCESS. But it’s never actually accessible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selfie from Cali</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190315-selfie-from-cali/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190315-selfie-from-cali/</guid>
      <description>That’s a wrap for this trip. It’s been fun trying a new hotel and exploring a different part of the city. Perhaps next time I’ll try to take in more of the cultural life. There’s always something going on in Pasadena.
Now home again to Texas and the people I love. See you soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Libre</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-taco-libre/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-taco-libre/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1552629476/img/576933C9-5E92-4C23-B1AF-8B342EF82BDF.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather was warmer today. I could feel spring in my bones. I get that way around this time of year. Maybe I was feeling a little homesick. Whatever the case, I&amp;rsquo;ve been craving Mexican food. I noticed this little while walking around during my lunch break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I was standing outside the door reading the posted menuboard, an older lady passing by said to me &amp;ldquo;Go in. You&amp;rsquo;ll like it. It&amp;rsquo;s really good.&amp;rdquo; I took that as a sign.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Times at the El Portal</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-el-portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-el-portal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1552625591/img/761E75E1-8A2E-4D98-9348-5951E7436215.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took a detour that night after my trip to the antique store. I passed along back streets, out of the way plazas, anywhere that looked like it might afford me new scenery. I stumbled across El Portal behind the headquarters of the Planetary Society, its aromas drawing my attention before I&amp;rsquo;d even rounded the corner to lay site on the place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horn Player</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-horn-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190314-horn-player/</guid>
      <description>A street musician doing his thing in Old Town Pasadena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Methodist Church</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190312-old-methodist-church/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190312-old-methodist-church/</guid>
      <description>The interesting things you run across when you decide to walk the mile and a half back to the hotel instead of Uber-ing. This is an old Methodist Church in the Playhouse District of Pasadena. Almost looks like an entrance to another world. A secret garden. A little foreboding perhaps.
There was a lot about this area I’d like to explore. I’ll be back again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Play Poison</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190312-let-s-play-poison/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190312-let-s-play-poison/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s someone buried under there. That&amp;rsquo;s the name. And see the date? Poison! Get off!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For the Lightly Bosomed Woman</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190312-for-the-lightly-bosomed-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190312-for-the-lightly-bosomed-woman/</guid>
      <description>I see what you did there, Flattery. And for the moderately bosomed woman? Out of luck, I suppose… 👙</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out West Again</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190219-working-in-pasadena/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 23:42:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190219-working-in-pasadena/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/7804/46429733404_0b482a5236_o.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What should I say? What can I say? Perhaps a little about where I find myself these days. What I&amp;rsquo;m up to. Best keep it brief. I want to encourage myself to update these pages a little more frequently this year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasadena Eats</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180520-pasadena-eats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:59:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180520-pasadena-eats/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/960/42132774932_29c870ce99_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Retro Store in Pasadena, California</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180510-the-retro-store-pasadena/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 16:42:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180510-the-retro-store-pasadena/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/946/42090262291_c42d9822cd_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maneki Neko Exhibit at the San Francisco Airport</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180329-maneki-neko/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 23:53:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180329-maneki-neko/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/794/40412447885_e7631aa6e2_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Sick</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20180328-so-sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:46:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20180328-so-sick/</guid>
      <description>Being sick on a trip is the worst. I&amp;rsquo;ve mostly been sleeping every spare moment I get. Managed to catch a pretty decent cheese ball of a movie, though. It was old school campy fun in the best way. Nicely captured the feel of old 80s schlock-horror movies like The Gate and Return of the Living Dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greetings from Redwood City</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180328-oracle-headquarters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 15:45:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20180328-oracle-headquarters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/902/26431323287_a749c73e35_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
