<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Texas Frightmare Weekend on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/texas-frightmare-weekend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Texas Frightmare Weekend on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 14:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/texas-frightmare-weekend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lights Out For Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>#pic { display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; }   Do you remember Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt? I wrote about that place around this time last year. It&amp;rsquo;s closed now. I had a dream about it the other night, or rather its next incarnation, which was as a hybrid Christmas/Halloween store. I know the owners have an interest in Christmas things, so that detail is not too surprising. But in my dream, there was also a functional toilet over by the register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diana Levin&#39;s Pocket Watch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-levins-pocket-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-levins-pocket-watch/</guid>
      <description>While in attendance at Texas Frightmare Weekend I picked up a small pocket watch as a souvenir for my daughter from the booth of Diana Levin. Check out her gallery on her website. Or better yet, if you like what you see you can buy something from her Etsy store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Frightmare Weekend</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/texas-frightmare-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/texas-frightmare-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This year I attended Texas Frightmare Weekend for the first time. By now it seems like forever ago. But lucky you — I saved all the pictures! So here they are without much verbal adornment, or it&amp;rsquo;d probably take me another month and a half to get this up.

I suggest you take your time with this post. It&amp;rsquo;s a big one. Really savor the photographs. Left-click to enlarge them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screening Phantasm With The Tall Man</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</guid>
      <description>From a respectful write-up on Texas Frightmare Weekend by Dread Central:
Can we stop calling Texas Frightmare Weekend a “regional con” now? The first reader I met this year was Aaron from Australia, who had flown all the way here to experience TFW as his FIRST con.
I met that guy! Twice. Sat right next to him at the special 35mm screening of Phantasm at the Alamo Draft House in Richardson.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>