<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/categories/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journal on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 13:10:58 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/categories/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunchtime Walks on Quarantine</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lunchtime-walks-on-quarantine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 13:10:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lunchtime-walks-on-quarantine/</guid>
      <description>Things have become very busy for me over the last couple of weeks. I&amp;rsquo;ve been given primary streaming and video responsibilities for our church during the lockdown, all the while ramping up for a new gig at my job, and working on an interesting side project as well — a product shoot for a friend at church who is opening up an Etsy store. (On a side note, I&amp;rsquo;ve never done anything like that and was honored that she even asked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CV Lockdown Blues. Missing California.</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/missing-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 14:18:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/missing-california/</guid>
      <description>I suppose it can&amp;rsquo;t be helped; every year as March drags into April, as the days get hotter and the brief Texas spring looks more toward the summer, the early zeal of the Lenten discipline wears off, and the sacrifices once willingly undertaken become an annoyance and a burden. These things are only compounded by the enforced isolation and the looming prospect of an almost anti-climatic, if not mildly depressing, Pascha undertaken as it is this year without the usual joy of communal celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lunch Options</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lunch-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lunch-options/</guid>
      <description>I was at the juice bar today getting an “Immune Booster” (beet, ginger, cayenne — I could use it right now)…
…when I noticed this alternative
It was a cup of donuts. They were selling donuts by the cup. At the juice bar.
Today, I chose wisely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Birthday, Kass</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/happy-birthday-kass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/happy-birthday-kass/</guid>
      <description>Wishing the best of birthdays to my beloved and fellow blogger. If only it could be from Hawaii again this year. I promise to make some Mai Tais this weekend to commemorate it, and maybe post some of those pics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning 31</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/turning-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/turning-31/</guid>
      <description>About damn time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassi Blogs the Plano Balloon Fest</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/k2-plano-balloon-fest-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 15:57:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/k2-plano-balloon-fest-2019/</guid>
      <description>Because I wanted to share her picture of me stuffing my face with a gigantic turkey leg. Also, &amp;lsquo;Murica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassi Blogs the Little Elm Autumn Fest</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/k2-little-elm-fallfest-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 15:35:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/k2-little-elm-fallfest-2019/</guid>
      <description>She&amp;rsquo;s right, the Little Elm Autumn Fest was a blast. We went Friday on Oktoberfest night and the polka band was amazing, as were the food trucks and local craft beer. It was crowded, and we had to park a fair distance away, but we had a good time and were able to do what we went there to do. This is gonna be on our must-do list next year, but I think I&amp;rsquo;d like to get there earlier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working From Malls</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/working-from-malls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 11:11:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/working-from-malls/</guid>
      <description>I love working from shopping malls. I was just telling Kassi the other day that they offer several advantages that suit me and my work style well. Doors open early. Easy access to restrooms. Most have at least some access to power; and free wifi, though I always tether. The ambient noise is generally at an appropriate level, though my current environment has somewhat more than the usual. More than anything I appreciate the large, wide open spaces and natural light that filters in through the ceiling glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIP Frank Dog, 2013 – 2019</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/rip-frank-dog-2013-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 12:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/rip-frank-dog-2013-2019/</guid>
      <description>I’m sorry, Frank. Despite driving us crazy sometimes, you were ever a good friend and protector. I know it wasn’t you’re fault. I hope somehow you understood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 09.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Arrived in beautiful Telluride, Colorado, and yes, this is my first update since day #2 of vacation. So much for my Travel Log. Between lack of cell signal and surrendering my phone to the kid, and straight up being too busy and/or exhausted, I haven’t had much opportunity for posting.
We’ve been busy!
Back to the Grand Canyon this year, and this time we got to spend a night in the park, with a chance to do some dawn/dusk shots of the canyon itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 02.02</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Finally made it to Red Rock State Park, and made a couple of new discoveries along the way. Our route took us through what turned out be the incredibly beautiful Coconino National Forest, a place we have vowed to return. If Tolkien’s Elves were a real thing, they might just choose to live in a place like that. Verdant green forests around the bases of giant granite mountains, interspersed all along the way with little villages and expensive looking cabin retreats, with lights hanging from the trees across bridges that span crystal clear mountain streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 02.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-02-01/</guid>
      <description>On the road from Albuquerque to Flagstaff, near which we turn south to Red Rock State Park in Arizona. The kids are keen to get in a hike today, the first “real” day of our vacation, as far as I’m concerned. It’s been fun watching the younger two get excited over taking pictures from the car with the little Instax Mini. That was Kassi’s great idea. We bought Anthony around 150 exposures and his eyes got wide when I told him I wanted him to use every single one by the end of the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 01.02</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Picture of me in the Llano Estacado, Texas’s “wine country”. On the road for quite a while and still not out of the state. Holding up well. Fear the little one may be coming down with a cold. Hope he’s better after some rest.
Changed restaurant plans and will revisit our old favorite in Albuquerque for the third year in a row.
The food there has always been great, though the service is consistently slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 01.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-01-01/</guid>
      <description>We’re well in to the big family road trip of 2019, and the obligatory Texas pit stop at Bucc-ees has been checked off the list. Would have sent you guys a pic from the storied Bucc-ees bathrooms, but I was too excited about these new hot n’ spicy Beaver Nuggets! You can hear all about my first experience with those glorified Corn Pops in this review I did last year with my good buddy Brian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fire Sign</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-fire-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 12:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-fire-sign/</guid>
      <description>The name of this sculpture is Entwine, I think a reference to The Lord of the Rings. It’s supposed to be a tree, or plant, to symbolize Wylie’s connection to its roots. I always thought of it as a campfire, and I think that imagery fits much better for a library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bits and Bobs</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-10-bits-and-bobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 17:33:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-10-bits-and-bobs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1562790874/img/IMG_3630.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made a promise to myself that I would never waste time on this blog apologizing for sporadic posting. So instead of doing that, I think I&amp;rsquo;ll do that other thing where I throw a few pictures at you and catch you up on recent developments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show Some Love To My Spouseblog</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-08-kassiblog-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 17:41:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-08-kassiblog-update/</guid>
      <description>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been following Kassi over on her personal blog, by all means go there and check it out. She&amp;rsquo;s been killing it lately, posting about all the family stuff I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to be getting to over on this site, but have been too lame to do. I swear she can fire off 3 or 4 posts by the time I&amp;rsquo;m done editing the same number of photos. Practice, I guess?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odds and Ends</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/journal-for-june-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 16:55:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/journal-for-june-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1561413959/img/kelsey.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s just say today feels more like Kelsey Grammer than Jason Momoa.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richardson&#39;s Cottonwood Art Festival</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cottonwood-art-fest-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cottonwood-art-fest-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/40876956893_f61f62e832_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/40876956893/&#34; title=&#34;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Somewhere around the beginning of May (and again in the fall) the city of Richardson, Texas invites artists from across the country to gather in Cottonwood Park for a big market day celebration of beauty and imagination. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cottonwoodartfestival.com&#34;&gt;The Cottonwood Art Festival&lt;/a&gt; features some brilliant and rigorously curated talent, and is described by the artists themselves as one of the best art shows in the country. This year we decided to pay a visit as a family. And although the younger two would crap out early from the mild heat and post-rainy day humidity, we did manage to hang around just long enough for me to discover my new favorite artist, Alla Tsank.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More on her later.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassi Blogs, Too</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/kassiblog-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:46:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/kassiblog-too/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My wife Kassi recently started her own blog of a more private nature, and she&amp;rsquo;s written a wonderful article about all of the many things going on in our lives last week, including our baptism, preparation for Pascha, and the appearance of the first clusters of firewheels in Dallas. Take a look.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Log: A New House</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dreamlog-a-new-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:14:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dreamlog-a-new-house/</guid>
      <description>I woke up from a vivid dream this morning. I&amp;rsquo;d just arrived home from a business trip to California, and Kassi was very excited to show me the changes that had been made to our neighborhood in my absence. Everyone had gotten a new house, it seems, and the neighborhood itself had been newly laid out, and its boundaries expanded. Our house had been moved to the backside of the neighborhood by the creek, and the wooded area around the creek had been developed, so that our house, instead of looking out onto a wooded ravine as it would currently, was now at a &amp;ldquo;T&amp;rdquo; intersection in the middle of the larger neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>45</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/45/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/45/</guid>
      <description>Today I had a lot of reminders that there are people out there who love and care for me a great deal. My wife, parents, and children. My brothers, cousins, and family. Friends old and new. I am thankful for all of them. I am thankful for the things I have, inside and out. I am thankful for the places God has brought me to in the past year.
I met a man on the street named Emery Lambus who asked me for a couple of bucks to buy lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ash Wednesday, Great Lent</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-06-ash-wednesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 23:28:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-06-ash-wednesday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7851/40345372543_3e0f96a5b4_b.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Theotokos Icon&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Theotokos Icon — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/40345372543/&#34; title=&#34;Theotokos Icon&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Today is Ash Wednesday, the Catholic holy day that begins the penitential season of Lent. This year I will not be celebrating as a Catholic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year on September 1st Kassi and I, after a long season of spiritual apathy and suffering, took our first steps into the Russian Orthodox Church. There were private reasons, of course. Personal reasons that are always at the core of any conversion; but also open reasons. We did not take the step lightly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out West Again</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-19-working-in-pasadena/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 23:42:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-19-working-in-pasadena/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7804/46429733404_b4819b49bc_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Twilight Over Pasadena&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Twilight Over Pasadena — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/46429733404/&#34; title=&#34;Twilight Over Pasadena&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What should I say? What can I say? Perhaps a little about where I find myself these days. What I&amp;rsquo;m up to. Best keep it brief. I want to encourage myself to update these pages a little more frequently this year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit to Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Channard from Hellraiser II, in all his glory
  Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt is a boutique shop in Dallas specializing in horror and sci-fi collectibles, memorabilia, paraphernalia, and… well, you just gotta see it, folks. It&amp;rsquo;s an amazing place. I discovered them only recently after attending the St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Slay Weekend event at Dark Hour Haunted House in Plano. They were a sponsor of that particular show, so Dark Hour graciously gave them some floor space to sell a few wares after the show and otherwise promote the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Halloween Merch of the Year</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/first-halloween-merch-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 06:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/first-halloween-merch-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Technically spotted on July 1 at Michaels. Thanks to Swagger Mom for the tip-off about fall going up this week. That made me wonder, and my suspicions checked out.
And yeah, it was mostly generic fall decorations on a couple of shelves, but over on the other side of the store, on a lonely end cap display, there was this:
Unmistakable. Halloween ribbon.
Frankensteins, witches, spiders, skeletons… Have you ever stopped to think how rich Halloween is in iconography?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is Coming</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/summer-is-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/summer-is-coming/</guid>
      <description>In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s already here. My woodland trekking has been sidelined a bit due to having to nurse a sumac rash, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be back soon enough. Here&amp;rsquo;s hoping you guys get out and sweat a bit this summer. Enjoy the late evenings while you can! DST. What a gift from Mr. Nixon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wylie&#39;s Angel</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/wylies-angel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/wylies-angel/</guid>
      <description>I like geocaching for lots of reasons. I like to be outside. I like discovering new places. I like walking and connecting with nature. But occasionally I learn something as well. Usually it&amp;rsquo;s just local historical trivia, or maybe a geography lesson. But sometimes the lesson is more personal, and as in this case, tragic.
The morning started out with a trip to the Trinity Trails in Wylie, Texas for some hiking and caching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day of Decisions</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-day-of-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-day-of-decisions/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m celebrating a major personal milestone today, and I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a more fitting way to commemorate it on this site than by encouraging you all to watch one of my favorite episodes of The Ray Bradbury Theater from 1989, The Wonderful Death of Dudley Stone. This episode is indeed all about decisions, priorities, and focusing on what&amp;rsquo;s important in life.
Part 1   Part 2   Part 3   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOUND OBJECTS: A PHOTOLOG OF GEOCACHING SWAGARTICLE I EVIL ZOMBIE CLOWN</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/found-objects-a-photolog-of-geocaching-swagarticle-i-evil-zombie-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/found-objects-a-photolog-of-geocaching-swagarticle-i-evil-zombie-clown/</guid>
      <description>I have no particular fear of clowns. I am not one of those people. But this thing gives me the creeps. Downright turns my stomach.
I found it in an ammo can in a small copse of woods near the office, nestled among a collection of unremarkable trinkets. It&amp;rsquo;s only about an inch or so high, so it took me a second to realize that it carries in its left hand a severed human arm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>