<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/categories/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journal on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/categories/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Richardson&#39;s Cottonwood Art Festival</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cottonwood-art-fest-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cottonwood-art-fest-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/40876956893_f61f62e832_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/40876956893/&#34; title=&#34;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somewhere around the beginning of May (and again in the fall) the city of Richardson, Texas invites artists from across the country to gather in Cottonwood Park for a big market day celebration of beauty and imagination. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cottonwoodartfestival.com&#34;&gt;The Cottonwood Art Festival&lt;/a&gt; features some brilliant and rigorously curated talent, and is described by the artists themselves as one of the best art shows in the country. This year we decided to pay a visit as a family. And although the younger two would crap out early from the mild heat and post-rainy day humidity, we did manage to hang around just long enough for me to discover my new favorite artist, Alla Tsank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More on her later.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassi Blogs, Too</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/kassiblog-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:46:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/kassiblog-too/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My wife Kassi recently started her own blog of a more private nature, and she&amp;rsquo;s written a wonderful article about all of the many things going on in our lives last week, including our baptism, preparation for Pascha, and the appearance of the first clusters of firewheels in Dallas. Take a look.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Log: A New House</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dreamlog-a-new-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:14:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dreamlog-a-new-house/</guid>
      <description>I woke up from a vivid dream this morning. I&amp;rsquo;d just arrived home from a business trip to California, and Kassi was very excited to show me the changes that had been made to our neighborhood in my absence. Everyone had gotten a new house, it seems, and the neighborhood itself had been newly laid out, and its boundaries expanded. Our house had been moved to the backside of the neighborhood by the creek, and the wooded area around the creek had been developed, so that our house, instead of looking out onto a wooded ravine as it would currently, was now at a &amp;ldquo;T&amp;rdquo; intersection in the middle of the larger neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>45</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/45/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/45/</guid>
      <description>Today I had a lot of reminders that there are people out there who love and care for me a great deal. My wife, parents, and children. My brothers, cousins, and family. Friends old and new. I am thankful for all of them. I am thankful for the things I have, inside and out. I am thankful for the places God has brought me to in the past year.
I met a man on the street named Emery Lambus who asked me for a couple of bucks to buy lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ash Wednesday, Great Lent</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-06-ash-wednesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 23:28:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-06-ash-wednesday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7851/40345372543_3e0f96a5b4_b.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Theotokos Icon&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Theotokos Icon — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/40345372543/&#34; title=&#34;Theotokos Icon&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today is Ash Wednesday, the Catholic holy day that begins the penitential season of Lent. This year I will not be celebrating as a Catholic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year on September 1st Kassi and I, after a long season of spiritual apathy and suffering, took our first steps into the Russian Orthodox Church. There were private reasons, of course. Personal reasons that are always at the core of any conversion; but also open reasons. We did not take the step lightly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out West Again</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-19-working-in-pasadena/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 23:42:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-19-working-in-pasadena/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7804/46429733404_b4819b49bc_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Twilight Over Pasadena&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Twilight Over Pasadena — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/46429733404/&#34; title=&#34;Twilight Over Pasadena&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What should I say? What can I say? Perhaps a little about where I find myself these days. What I&amp;rsquo;m up to. Best keep it brief. I want to encourage myself to update these pages a little more frequently this year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>