<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gaming on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/gaming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gaming on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 23:29:44 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/gaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Infexxion-34</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190304-infexxion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 23:29:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190304-infexxion/</guid>
      <description>Infexxion is an iPhone game based on the old arcade game Attax. My cousin Carl introduced me to it. There was a cabinet in the lobby of a (surely long-since demolished?) movie theater in what is now a rough part of Lafayette, Louisiana. I forget what we were seeing that night. He played — I didn&amp;rsquo;t, as I recall. It had a weird, edgy kind of quality to it, like an Exidy game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Hell is This Poster For the Sonic the Hedgehog Movie?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190222-sonic-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 22:27:13 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20190222-sonic-movie/</guid>
      <description>The Sonic the Hedgehog movie comes out this year.&#xA;Are you hyped, nostalgia boys?!&#xA;Because if you look at this poster and get hyped, I&amp;rsquo;m calling the cops. Seriously, who designed this freakish movie poster and why is he/she not in jail/hell?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropping Quarters</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140725-dropping-quarters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140725-dropping-quarters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a little independent retro gaming store in Plano that is the closest thing to a real arcade that I&amp;rsquo;ve ever experienced with the kids. There are still a lot of places you could call &amp;ldquo;arcades&amp;rdquo;, mostly attached to chain family restaurants like Chuck-E-Cheese or entertainment complexes like Fun Zone or Amazing Jakes. But the key differentiator for me is that the machines take real quarters, preferably only one per play. I always hated changing tokens, and to me the idea of plopping tokens into a machine screws with the mythology somehow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
