<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>

    <title>@tobyblog’s Tobyblog - Horror</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/horror/index.xml</link>
    <description>All entries in Horror on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <atom:link href="/tags/horror/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Sfanthor! House of Wax</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
         (Toby Marks)</author>
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25343644294/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Sfanthor banner&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Sfanthor banner&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1482/25343644294_37a4e6d0e8_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;Here in North Texas the sun is shining. The weather is warming up. The world outside is getting brighter. The Texas wildflowers are already in bloom, thanks to a mild and soggy winter. In the woods, things are moving. The itchy season is upon us, and the window of opportunity for a lot of local geocaches is closing, as the casual players tend to steer clear of anything that might put them in the way of tall grass, poison ivy, or the dreaded tick.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is a season I have grown to love. Especially because it heralds the return of my beloved firewheels, the wonderful gaillardias that blanket the countryside around these parts, that channel the power and living energy of the Texas sun into something beautiful and delicate — as delicate and precious as life. That&amp;rsquo;s a sense that perhaps only the very young, and the older, possess. I&amp;rsquo;m not that old, but I look forward.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And perhaps that is why a guy like me is never far from thoughts of fall, and pumpkins, and cool night winds. So it is no surprise that in the middle of all this awakening spring glory I find myself back in the shadows, on a quest to discover if in the heart of Texas something is still left of the spirit of the bizarre, the otherwordly, and the mysterious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name=&#39;more&#39;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25950456836/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;The Bride of Frankenstein&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;The Bride of Frankenstein&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1532/25950456836_84eb2a136b_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;It was almost a year ago that I first blogged about &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tobyblog.com/2015/04/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt.html&#34;&gt;Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt&lt;/a&gt; in Oak Cliff. The Crypt is gone now, lost to the real-world horror of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tobyblog.com/2016/01/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt.html&#34;&gt;neighborhood gentrification&lt;/a&gt;. (I will have more to say about that later on.) I&amp;rsquo;ve kept in touch with the owners, my friends Andrea and Kathy, and they will be making an appearance at the upcoming &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.texasfrightmareweekend.com/&#34;&gt;Texas Frightmare Weekend&lt;/a&gt; convention in April. They will have a booth and will be selling lots of curious items under the Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt banner. I would encourage all of you to attend and buy lots from them. Many of their items will surely be one of a kind. And you can even tell them Tobyblog sent you. Who knows what might happen?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They tell me their plan is to take the store online, and I genuinely hope that they are able to do that, as I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;m not finished giving them money yet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25950454746/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Hulk TP&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Hulk TP&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1448/25950454746_c68d8c5afe_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;But still, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for the loss. It was a unique place. Maybe a little too unique. I used to wonder if it could really be possible that there was nothing else like it outside of California (that was the line I would use). But did I really believe that? Surely there had to be others. Texas is a big state, after all. And there are pockets of weirdness everywhere, especially in college towns, or sometimes in little places you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t expect. I&amp;rsquo;m not particularly well traveled, either, so what do I know? Anything could be out there. Maybe right around the corner. And so I began to look for signs of life…&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25675806150/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Demon baby&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Demon baby&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1672/25675806150_9cc69df145_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;I believe it was right around the time of Texas Frightmare Weekend 2015, as I was investigating some of the various merchants and attendees, that I ran across mention of &lt;a href=&#34;http://sfanthor.bustis.com/&#34;&gt;Sfanthor!&lt;/a&gt;, thanks to the horror blog &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bloodovertexas.com/&#34;&gt;Blood Over Texas&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I would suggest you link on over and &lt;a href=&#34;http://bloodovertexas.com/?p=2084&#34;&gt;read that now&lt;/a&gt;. It&amp;rsquo;s a short and very well-written article, and you can probably see why my eyes perked up.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color:lightblue&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;The castle is, Sfanthor, a shop celebrating sci-fi, fantasy and horror — the name is a mashup of those three genres and is full of everything your dark heart desires. Vintage comics, toys, jewelry, collectibles and T-shirts, including horror shirts by local company, Pallbearer Press. Created by one of the coolest, weird shops in town, Museum of the Weird on 6th street (downtown Austin), Sfanthor is following in it’s predecessors footsteps by adding a cool museum to the mix.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25675806600/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Models&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Models&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1569/25675806600_7dc5bdf6dc_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;I did not need to read on, but of course I did! It sounded a lot like the Crypt, but with a bonafide wax museum attached?! This was a promising place, and so I told myself I&amp;rsquo;d need to get down there one day soon and check it out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Well, somehow that turned into a year. Such is life. But an opportunity recently arose to make the trip with my bold cousin Carl (with whom I am planning some surprising new projects, friends!), and so I was finally able to make good on my promise.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25343660184/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Keep Austin Weird frisbee&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Keep Austin Weird frisbee&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1462/25343660184_e88e16e3ab_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;This was a couple of weeks ago during Austin&amp;rsquo;s notorious SXSW festival. Like Mardi Gras in New Orleans, the festival is compromised of a ton of little venues and events that happen all throughout the city. It brings in a lot of folks from out of town, and as a result all traffic on the main arteries pretty much grinds to a halt. Nevertheless, we somehow managed to navigate our way around much of that as we made our way down to Congress Avenue.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25950450886/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Bride pillow&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Bride pillow&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1641/25950450886_d3a2448c0c_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;The castle (and it &lt;em&gt;does&lt;/em&gt; look from the outside like a small castle) is located along a trendy downtown strip among exotic food trailers and local boutiques. I recommend street viewing the place. There is a lot of foot traffic. Austin is a fashionable, hipster-ish college town, sort of like Texas&amp;rsquo;s version of Portland, with its own reputation for weirdness — &amp;rdquo;Keep Austin Weird&amp;rdquo; is a popular commercial slogan — and is known for having a lively music scene. Back in the heyday of the Outlaw movement in country music, there was a show on PBS called Austin City Limits which generally bored the hell out of me. I&amp;rsquo;d probably have a much better appreciation for it now. To my surprise it&amp;rsquo;s still taping and airing uninterrupted after 40 years. My point is that it&amp;rsquo;s a hip town, much more so than Dallas, and if a place like Sfanthor! were going to make it in Texas, Austin seems like it would be a safe bet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But I dunno. When you consider the runaway popularity of places like Dark Hour and the ridiculously huge Texas Frightmare Weekend, the freak population may be more slanted towards North Texas than is at first apparent.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25881404361/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Elf lady&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Elf lady&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1697/25881404361_125e7c56d5_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;After declining a chicken burrito from nextdoor Mrs. P&amp;rsquo;s, Carl and I crossed the portcullis and entered the gift shop, which is mainly what I had come for. A friendly guy behind the counter greeted us as we walked in, which turned out to be proprietor Dave Bustis. Remarkable guy. Turns out Sfanthor! is just the newest of his contributions to Austin&amp;rsquo;s cultural scene, his best known being the Museum of the Weird. He has another little shop selling oddities called The Lizard Lounge. You should check it out in person or online, because he has some neat things over there.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25675802480/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Masks&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Masks&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1666/25675802480_d886c6bff0_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;I asked if I could take some pics for publicity purposes and he graciously obliged.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I stopped a bit just to let my eyes wander around the place. There were so many things to look at, my head was spinning. I recalled that feeling from somewhere before…&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25675800020/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Comic rack&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Comic rack&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1680/25675800020_7e53c04ab1_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;427&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;I instantly knew my four hours on the road had not been wasted. I came looking for a successor to Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt, and what I found was something different; a new experience, but satisfying in the same way. What shone out to me was the tremendous labor of love that was evident in everything from the selection to the displays to the structure of the building itself; things that made the Crypt so special. Bustis has really put his heart and soul into the place, and who knows how much time and money. Along that bustling Austin pavement he somehow lowered a drawbridge into an extraordinary world.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25855557092/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Comic shelves&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Comic shelves&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1685/25855557092_5cc50990e6_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;The gift shop portion of Sfanthor! is not as large as Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt, nor the inventory as extensive, but what they do carry is all highly desirable stuff. There are the models, collector&amp;rsquo;s pieces, toys, books, DVDs, masks, and games I remember from the old store — but added to that are postcards, posters, t-shirts, pins, and novelty items. It has a heavy emphasis on t-shirts, comics, and magazines — particularly Famous Monsters of Filmland — which sell for what seemed to me like frustratingly high prices.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25347627913/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Games&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Games&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1670/25347627913_26e31d2207_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;Among my favorite items in the store were the tourist-friendly postcards and mini-movie posters celebrating the Universal Monsters pantheon. There were some really good ones.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25675793050/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Mr. Hyde&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Mr. Hyde&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1557/25675793050_f99f67ac38_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;There were some very nicely painted models as well. Did I mention the Universal Monsters tribute? That was a theme that played heavily throughout the store.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The masks were really top-notch. Detailed and well painted, they were very eye-catching. Reminded me of something you might find at the Monsterpalooza convention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25347624213/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Frankenstein&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Frankenstein&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1630/25347624213_d620f7e130_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;While we were looking around Mr. Bustis explained that the deal on for that day was free tickets to the attached museum with the purchase of a t-shirt. We didn&amp;rsquo;t want to pass up that offer, so we each picked out one for ourselves. Carl got a Bigfoot shirt, I believe, and I chose a nice red one advertising the Museum of the Weird. The shirts were good material and fit well. I felt like that was a score.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25343649514/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Karloff and Lugosi&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Karloff and Lugosi&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1542/25343649514_a1c6cd3aa4_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;There was such a large variety of comics I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but peruse them a bit, even though my collecting days are long since over. I noticed they had a nice Transformers #1 UK edition that were I twenty years younger I would have insisted upon. I once owned a random issue of the US comic where they &amp;ldquo;guest starred&amp;rdquo; the UK storyline for some unknown reason. I remember the British story being far, far more entertaining than the American one, and having something to do with time-traveling Autobots.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25950439786/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;The Mummy&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;The Mummy&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1567/25950439786_0a8a780975_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;I kept an eye out for the odd affordable (and therefore overlooked) issue of Famous Monsters, but alas found none that interested me in my price range. I suppose collectors have driven the price up in the last few years.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25950438726/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;King Kong&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;King Kong&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1691/25950438726_eaf5725570_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;At some point we agreed it was time to take our goods up to the register and settle our business so we could try the museum. That&amp;rsquo;s when I became better acquainted with the owner. He saw that I had picked up a copy of his Museum of the Weird comic, something that looked like a Tales from the Crypt knock-off made for advertising the museum, and offered to sign it for me. I thought it was a strange offer, but decided why not, sure. It was only later that I discovered that he owned both museums, and had actually written and drawn the first comic strip in the book! Not only that, but of the four stories presented in the comic his was far and away the best, in my opinion. Not only was the story creepy and intelligent, but the tone and style was a spot-on homage to Jack Chick and his Chick tracts. In retrospect I think I&amp;rsquo;m as impressed by my signed comic, picked up on a whim because it matched my shirt, as I was by the rest of the experience. A truly great find!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25950436496/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Creature 3D Billboard&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creature 3D Billboard&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1693/25950436496_84158dff5b_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;488&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;The little winding path of the museum is entered by stepping into the hall just off to the right of where you enter the gift shop. It is devoted to the Golden and Silver ages of horror film, from the Silent Era to the advent of Hammer and Christopher Lee. It is more or less divided into sections covering each decade from the 1910s to the 1970s, with breakout sections dedicated to certain films or actors. Information is conveyed through plaques that hang on the walls, and illustrated by wax sculptures depicting many classic monsters from film history.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25675789820/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;It Came From Outer Space&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;It Came From Outer Space&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1539/25675789820_da15495ae4_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s worth taking your time there, as the museum is not all that large. This is not a Madame Tussaud&amp;rsquo;s, but it is nonetheless impressive, and moreover, fun. It&amp;rsquo;s like they carved out all the cruft from a full-sized wax museum, all the slightly off renditions of James Dean and Marilyn Monroe and George W. Bush, and just got straight to the good stuff. The only stuff most of you guys care about, anyway. And a few of the figures are particularly well done. That Mr. Hyde, for instance — how creepy is that? And Lon Chaney&amp;rsquo;s character from London After Midnight, with that maniacal smile, sets the tone perfectly for the entire collection. I can&amp;rsquo;t say enough how satisfied I was with the tour.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25347616643/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Bud&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Bud&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1543/25347616643_64f312aed2_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;And get a load of the facilities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Located about halfway through the museum is one of the nicest public bathrooms you&amp;rsquo;ll ever run across, and matches the interior quite well. Not that it&amp;rsquo;s decked out with fake webbing or gargoyle toilets, but the heavy doors and dark wood do give it something of a gothic effect. I&amp;rsquo;d highly recommend you take advantage of the toilet while you&amp;rsquo;re there.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25950440726/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Restroom door&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Restroom door&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1712/25950440726_11e64498b5_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;427&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;The back half of the tour covers the later years of the classic horror era, and includes life-sized figures of The Wolf Man and The Creature from the Black Lagoon, along with assorted aliens, including, as you round the final corner, what appeared to be the big showpiece of the museum, which I&amp;rsquo;ll leave as a surprise for those who venture out there. Needless to say is was an outstanding model, very nicely displayed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;a data-flickr-embed=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/25950434656/in/dateposted-public/&#34; title=&#34;Tobyblog and creep&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Tobyblog and creep&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1549/25950434656_ac5292d44b_z.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;script async=&#34;&#34; charset=&#34;utf-8&#34; src=&#34;//embedr.flickr.com/assets/client-code.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt; &lt;p&gt;As we said our goodbyes and thanked the owner Mr. Busti, I told him the story of Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt in Oak Cliff, and what he had to say just floored me. Turns out Sfanthor! also faces similar issues with developers who want to renovate the area. It was the same sad story all over again. He wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if Sfanthor! would be around at that location next Halloween, but we encouraged him to try to hold out as long as he could, and not give up on the place. He does have the option of expanding his Museum of the Weird to accommodate at least some of the pieces. Hopefully one way or another it works out for him and for all of us, and Texas doesn&amp;rsquo;t lose yet another of these places.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s all for now, folks. May have more on this place later. I&amp;rsquo;ve been researching the goings on at the MotW and have uncovered some pretty interesting things. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;!-- Wikplayer http://www.wikplayer.com --&gt;&lt;script data-config=&#34;{&#39;skin&#39;:&#39;skins/wikmini/funkyMiniRed/skin.css&#39;,&#39;volume&#39;:50,&#39;autoplay&#39;:true,&#39;shuffle&#39;:false,&#39;repeat&#39;:1,&#39;showcomment&#39;:false,&#39;marqueetexton&#39;:true,&#39;placement&#39;:&#39;mini&#39;,&#39;showplaylist&#39;:false,&#39;playlist&#39;:[{&#39;title&#39;:&#39;Something%20to%20Think%20About%20-%20Christopher%20Young%20-%20Hellraiser%20II&#39;,&#39;url&#39;:&#39;https%3A%2F%2Fsoundcloud.com%2Ftoby-marks-1%2Fsomething-to-think-about-christopher-young-hellraiser-ii&#39;}]}&#34; src=&#34;http://www.wikplayer.com/code.js&#34; type=&#34;text/javascript&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;&lt;!-- Wikplayer code end --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-dark-hour---best-haunt-ever/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
         (Toby Marks)</author>
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-dark-hour---best-haunt-ever/</guid>
        <description>&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-2FRIs6Ct-Fc/VgDXNDwW06I/AAAAAAAACcY/NajCMB6v3Rc/s1600/DH17.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;424&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-2FRIs6Ct-Fc/VgDXNDwW06I/AAAAAAAACcY/NajCMB6v3Rc/s640/DH17.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&#39;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&#39;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&#39;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&#39;t get caught! Cause you know, awkward.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a name=&#39;more&#39;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-cCy4s8Pmkrg/VgDXJAS7EbI/AAAAAAAACks/YtumO0Fl8uM/s1600/DH10.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;320&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-cCy4s8Pmkrg/VgDXJAS7EbI/AAAAAAAACks/YtumO0Fl8uM/s320/DH10.jpg&#34; width=&#34;240&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-jMOcDoTcNpk/VgDXMGifNwI/AAAAAAAACcI/IX6-7oksodE/s1600/DH13.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-jMOcDoTcNpk/VgDXMGifNwI/AAAAAAAACcI/IX6-7oksodE/s400/DH13.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-VtAojDLP8Rw/VgDXKDRawiI/AAAAAAAACkw/LLWGyAQaIqY/s1600/DH102.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-VtAojDLP8Rw/VgDXKDRawiI/AAAAAAAACkw/LLWGyAQaIqY/s640/DH102.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dark Hour is a haunted house in Plano, Texas. It is one of the premier haunted houses in the nation, in fact — open year round, with shows every month aside from August and November. No show in August, because it takes extra time to prepare for the BIG show in September/October. (And by the way I AM SO EXCITED for the big show!) And no show in November because they&#39;re recovering from October; that&#39;s how much they throw themselves into it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-jTV9NjDBmXk/VgDXZKmfIbI/AAAAAAAACf4/TRCGxhLsTDw/s1600/DH5.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-jTV9NjDBmXk/VgDXZKmfIbI/AAAAAAAACf4/TRCGxhLsTDw/s400/DH5.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-W2lUE99509g/VgDXOSSApoI/AAAAAAAACcs/RhMKOwQ2OCc/s1600/DH2.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-W2lUE99509g/VgDXOSSApoI/AAAAAAAACcs/RhMKOwQ2OCc/s640/DH2.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I refer to them personally as &#34;shows&#34; and not &#34;haunts&#34;, because to me it&#39;s Vegas-quality spectacle. You get sets, lights, costumes, makeup, story, acting, music, dancing — the whole shebang. Their level of professionalism, the attention to detail, is just awe-inspiring. These guys love what they do and they are proud of what they do, and it comes through in every aspect of their productions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-5QaLrTUDXsE/VgDXUq3dHDI/AAAAAAAACe8/a8XxkfpWh4A/s1600/DH4.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-5QaLrTUDXsE/VgDXUq3dHDI/AAAAAAAACe8/a8XxkfpWh4A/s640/DH4.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-kbXCoRbdAHY/VgDXMwB2DCI/AAAAAAAACcc/ZjwlB9mMJUc/s1600/DH16.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-kbXCoRbdAHY/VgDXMwB2DCI/AAAAAAAACcc/ZjwlB9mMJUc/s400/DH16.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To give you an example from a recent show, at the Summer Spirits event TheVCubeSolver and I were wending our way through the roughly 30,000 foot &#34;path&#34; that takes you through the three distinct sections of the haunt - the Dominion of the Dead, Coven Manor, and Voodoo Vengeance, when we passed through a kind of kitchen pantry area leading to a cafeteria lunch line filled full of some pretty gross stuff. As I scanned the scene my eyes settled upon a shelf lined with Calumet baking powder, an obscure reference to The Shining that I only caught because I had recently watched the documentary Room 237! That kind of blew me away, that somebody would go to that much trouble to incorporate such a minor, but incredibly satisfying little detail for folks &#34;in the know&#34;. These guys not only know their craft, but their audience as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-nB1FCXhbNZ8/VgDXO3ju0dI/AAAAAAAACk8/M0DuCQlpJLs/s1600/DH21.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-nB1FCXhbNZ8/VgDXO3ju0dI/AAAAAAAACk8/M0DuCQlpJLs/s640/DH21.jpg&#34; width=&#34;424&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-3GWqPXS5Rvo/VgDXPs-wyBI/AAAAAAAACk8/1y4OWmacyfY/s1600/DH24.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-3GWqPXS5Rvo/VgDXPs-wyBI/AAAAAAAACk8/1y4OWmacyfY/s640/DH24.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-daU0RmVLSPg/VgDXNih5lKI/AAAAAAAACc8/L6ndo80dFuc/s1600/DH18.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-daU0RmVLSPg/VgDXNih5lKI/AAAAAAAACc8/L6ndo80dFuc/s640/DH18.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I discovered Dark Hour almost by chance, while Googling for something interesting to do while my friend Brian from &lt;a href=&#34;http://reviewtheworld.com/&#34;&gt;reviewtheworld.com&lt;/a&gt; was in town from Ohio. When I found out there was a haunted house open that weekend it seemed like a no-brainer. Little did I expect, though, a haunt on the scale of Dark Hour.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-2oEE_BbePuM/VgDXVKyKVqI/AAAAAAAACeo/N10S3uZtn4s/s1600/DH41.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;213&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-2oEE_BbePuM/VgDXVKyKVqI/AAAAAAAACeo/N10S3uZtn4s/s320/DH41.jpg&#34; width=&#34;320&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-GO1NWzxn9TM/VgDXObar-LI/AAAAAAAACk8/WztA5O-HNO4/s1600/DH20.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-GO1NWzxn9TM/VgDXObar-LI/AAAAAAAACk8/WztA5O-HNO4/s640/DH20.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As soon as you enter the building it&#39;s a full-on sensory assault. The first thing you notice is this incredibly pungent aroma — like an overpowering dark incense or something. I have no idea what that scent is, but I remember hoping by the end of the night that it would seep into my clothes so I could take it home with me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-shj_fspsCPE/VgDXR8dW6DI/AAAAAAAACk4/zh8gYR_ZUIA/s1600/DH31.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;425&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-shj_fspsCPE/VgDXR8dW6DI/AAAAAAAACk4/zh8gYR_ZUIA/s640/DH31.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-S9Z02Y22ksQ/VgDXQT6UZCI/AAAAAAAACk8/MnnUeW5fb4s/s1600/DH26.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-S9Z02Y22ksQ/VgDXQT6UZCI/AAAAAAAACk8/MnnUeW5fb4s/s640/DH26.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The lights are the next thing you notice, because everything inside is done up like a Dario Argento flick. Although it&#39;s basically dark as a cave in the entrance (it takes your eyes a second to adjust), strong colored lights accent a few animatronic greeters in the lobby, all dominated by this amazing 20 foot golem that stands over a smoking cauldron. I thought I had stepped into a black magic Chuck E. Cheese. My first instinct was just to stand there and gawp at the thing, and on return visits when it wasn&#39;t too busy we&#39;ve loitered a bit at the front just to take a closer look at everything they have going on there. Turns out there are a lot of little details that contribute to the basic story of the haunt. It&#39;s really well done.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-bSSZHAK2Mj8/VgDXLL-9cYI/AAAAAAAACkw/gs9nIlj-QAY/s1600/DH105.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-bSSZHAK2Mj8/VgDXLL-9cYI/AAAAAAAACkw/gs9nIlj-QAY/s400/DH105.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-EwnT8Hx_5hM/VgDXb_kvqXI/AAAAAAAACk4/CFk5gZaMsxc/s1600/DH56.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-EwnT8Hx_5hM/VgDXb_kvqXI/AAAAAAAACk4/CFk5gZaMsxc/s400/DH56.jpg&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-53kYklsq720/VgDXcWgSxYI/AAAAAAAACk4/k48rldYPED8/s1600/DH57.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-53kYklsq720/VgDXcWgSxYI/AAAAAAAACk4/k48rldYPED8/s640/DH57.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Yd4PUssgLEs/VgDXhewLSRI/AAAAAAAACkw/puUwAVRVC0Q/s1600/DH70.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Yd4PUssgLEs/VgDXhewLSRI/AAAAAAAACkw/puUwAVRVC0Q/s400/DH70.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The music is the next thing that hits you, and they like to switch that out from haunt to haunt, but it&#39;s never failed to bring a smile to my face. On occasion I&#39;ve caught some cool soundtrack stuff, like the unsettling synth of Italian prog-rock band Goblin. It was their theme music from Suspiria, that show about a girls&#39; boarding school secretly run by witches, that greeted you in the lobby the night of the aforementioned Summer Spirits show. A pitch-perfect nod right in the door that set the stage for what was to be a show crammed with movie and other fictional references.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-Dhq163SoQRY/VgDXj91piEI/AAAAAAAACiQ/S-AzLjLrR5M/s1600/DH8.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-Dhq163SoQRY/VgDXj91piEI/AAAAAAAACiQ/S-AzLjLrR5M/s640/DH8.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-72jOpcOrGAQ/VgDXTF6gMpI/AAAAAAAACeQ/RHbN1JJOxVA/s1600/DH36.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;320&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-72jOpcOrGAQ/VgDXTF6gMpI/AAAAAAAACeQ/RHbN1JJOxVA/s320/DH36.jpg&#34; width=&#34;213&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-5G8UioxRKOI/VgDXT-MtWJI/AAAAAAAACk4/zPnRNYOfUmM/s1600/DH37.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-5G8UioxRKOI/VgDXT-MtWJI/AAAAAAAACk4/zPnRNYOfUmM/s400/DH37.jpg&#34; width=&#34;266&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-lGzFETJNQAM/VgDXUQnoJII/AAAAAAAACec/H6ct83tPPgM/s1600/DH39.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;266&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-lGzFETJNQAM/VgDXUQnoJII/AAAAAAAACec/H6ct83tPPgM/s400/DH39.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-evEgofCEOEw/VgDXU7zRrYI/AAAAAAAACew/YHOMiwWBKpE/s1600/DH40.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-evEgofCEOEw/VgDXU7zRrYI/AAAAAAAACew/YHOMiwWBKpE/s640/DH40.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When the lines are bigger you get actors roaming the lobby to harass (er, warm up) the visitors and pose for pictures. These guys range from the funny to the downright disturbing. They generally like to interact with you so it&#39;s a good opportunity to practice your role playing skills, if you have them. Or you can just snap surreptitious pics like you&#39;re on safari in the nut house.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-9LjTpIPvcu8/VgDXUHzy2MI/AAAAAAAACeY/yJgY3gtOFwQ/s1600/DH38.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;266&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-9LjTpIPvcu8/VgDXUHzy2MI/AAAAAAAACeY/yJgY3gtOFwQ/s400/DH38.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-ztngWeMcsnU/VgDXP8aSNaI/AAAAAAAACk8/SKMNVQivRRg/s1600/DH25.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-ztngWeMcsnU/VgDXP8aSNaI/AAAAAAAACk8/SKMNVQivRRg/s400/DH25.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the really cool things about Dark Hour is that you generally get live entertainment while you wait in line. You can skip the long lines with a VIP pass, but for the life of me I don&#39;t know why anybody would want to. On one occasion I arrived a little early to shorter than usual lines and I was actually afraid I&#39;d miss the pre-show. By now I&#39;ve come to expect it as part of the warm-up. Occasionally they&#39;ll have live bands, which have always been great. From time to time you&#39;ll get dancers, and if you&#39;re REALLY lucky, Buddy Blood the singing vampire will come out and do his lounge act for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-RdCqlQ7ARXY/VgDXS4ztbQI/AAAAAAAACk4/uU2BJHhgyYs/s1600/DH34.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;clear: right; float: right; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-left: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;425&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-RdCqlQ7ARXY/VgDXS4ztbQI/AAAAAAAACk4/uU2BJHhgyYs/s640/DH34.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Vs7rI9ZmpBU&#34; width=&#34;560&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-kU38YajA-_E/VgDXgA1eaNI/AAAAAAAACkw/M8P7Lfc4mGQ/s1600/DH67.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-kU38YajA-_E/VgDXgA1eaNI/AAAAAAAACkw/M8P7Lfc4mGQ/s640/DH67.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-7jruePfUa6M/VgDXga8mc2I/AAAAAAAACkw/3Zx6hnYhkJU/s1600/DH68.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-7jruePfUa6M/VgDXga8mc2I/AAAAAAAACkw/3Zx6hnYhkJU/s640/DH68.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5HUHjh2cvzY&#34; width=&#34;560&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-KWEfZNkAnzA/VgDXic-9YPI/AAAAAAAACkw/1Euak3OoJtI/s1600/DH73.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-KWEfZNkAnzA/VgDXic-9YPI/AAAAAAAACkw/1Euak3OoJtI/s640/DH73.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You are not allowed to take pictures inside the haunt, which would be both ridiculous and impractical. Still, though, I wish I could because there is so much on the inside worth capturing. The set design takes your breath away in places, like at the entrance to Voodoo Vengeance. You&#39;re encouraged to move along at a reasonable pace but sometimes you just want to stop and take it all in. I have sometimes wondered what I look like to the monsters as I stumble through the haunt, mouth agape and occasionally turning the wrong way or running into things. Then they did this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/hszYgS8GRJ0&#34; width=&#34;560&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We&#39;re the first guys featured in the scare cam! There I am, captured on camera, shoving TheVCubeSolver into the arms of a monster as I make a speedy exit from the room. I try to be a good father, and the monsters appreciate that. Once I made one of the actors break character just enough to laugh at me and yell &#34;World&#39;s Greatest Father!&#34; after I came close to jabbing my son in the eye with a glow stick after overreacting to a jump scare. My fault? I say it was a good show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-2o3-ShW54cQ/VgDXhqjF35I/AAAAAAAACkw/PcWC9nVlqcY/s1600/DH72.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-2o3-ShW54cQ/VgDXhqjF35I/AAAAAAAACkw/PcWC9nVlqcY/s640/DH72.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-UiLxhGgLiaM/VgDXkF6GujI/AAAAAAAACiU/pqgdfk904ZY/s1600/DH80.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-UiLxhGgLiaM/VgDXkF6GujI/AAAAAAAACiU/pqgdfk904ZY/s400/DH80.jpg&#34; width=&#34;258&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-u7-MrbUda2c/VgDXkefqfII/AAAAAAAACic/JX2X3LqDjZA/s1600/DH81.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;320&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-u7-MrbUda2c/VgDXkefqfII/AAAAAAAACic/JX2X3LqDjZA/s640/DH81.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Vip6eFIt9RM/VgDXiiNvJ5I/AAAAAAAACkw/hn_9qLUOqUI/s1600/DH75.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Vip6eFIt9RM/VgDXiiNvJ5I/AAAAAAAACkw/hn_9qLUOqUI/s640/DH75.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Dark Hour puts on several shows connected by a common storyline. The story arch is flexible enough to allow them to change things up a bit from production to production, but the extent to which each year&#39;s shows vary is still being worked out. You can catch up on all the lore on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://darkhourhauntedhouse.com/spell/&#34;&gt;Dark Hour website&lt;/a&gt;, and there&#39;s a great breakdown of the monthly shows, about half of which I have not yet seen, over on the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hauntworld.com/featured_article/dallas_texas_haunted_house_dark_hour_attraction_scariest_best&#34;&gt;HauntWorld blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-jvZDLa0wpTk/VgDXm1kS1iI/AAAAAAAACjE/tsnwqg__Ba0/s1600/DH87.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;240&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-jvZDLa0wpTk/VgDXm1kS1iI/AAAAAAAACjE/tsnwqg__Ba0/s320/DH87.jpg&#34; width=&#34;320&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-v5jy39CdRZg/VgDXn5L2TZI/AAAAAAAACkk/VgIziJhMUfk/s1600/DH88.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-v5jy39CdRZg/VgDXn5L2TZI/AAAAAAAACkk/VgIziJhMUfk/s640/DH88.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-A37BQu6gJsk/VgDXoxqYutI/AAAAAAAACkg/WcVo4q38ueU/s1600/DH90.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-A37BQu6gJsk/VgDXoxqYutI/AAAAAAAACkg/WcVo4q38ueU/s640/DH90.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-U5BSbyHleDs/VgDXn7qIwRI/AAAAAAAACjQ/cbWCNgcIFlU/s1600/DH89.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-U5BSbyHleDs/VgDXn7qIwRI/AAAAAAAACjQ/cbWCNgcIFlU/s640/DH89.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-6KS_2BgNi0M/VgDXl1nqR-I/AAAAAAAACiw/v5mVDUM909M/s1600/DH85.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-6KS_2BgNi0M/VgDXl1nqR-I/AAAAAAAACiw/v5mVDUM909M/s400/DH85.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Afterwards there is always an add-on attraction which you can participate in for an additional charge, themed to go with the that month&#39;s haunt. Walpurgisnacht had a dark art gallery, Dog Days had a catered BBQ dinner, and Summer Spirits even had a prom night!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-e_Kqr_2l-Ts/VgDXmnHki9I/AAAAAAAACkw/Ht__lWc_vaE/s1600/DH86.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-e_Kqr_2l-Ts/VgDXmnHki9I/AAAAAAAACkw/Ht__lWc_vaE/s640/DH86.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-cebB8yHXbhc/VgDXpAUrfnI/AAAAAAAACkc/Q4nfEegKF3U/s1600/DH91.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-cebB8yHXbhc/VgDXpAUrfnI/AAAAAAAACkc/Q4nfEegKF3U/s640/DH91.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-GdcsWPRRnAo/VgDXrNG7c8I/AAAAAAAACkE/wzme50JNHBI/s1600/DH96.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-GdcsWPRRnAo/VgDXrNG7c8I/AAAAAAAACkE/wzme50JNHBI/s640/DH96.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Halloween haunt this year promises great things! All of the witches of the coven will make an appearance. The story is that a new witch has stepped forward to assume leadership — Vidua, the witch of suffering. Sounds like they&#39;re gearing up for something extra scary. Then apparently there is an after-haunt that pays tribute to the classic Universal monsters. I can&#39;t wait to see what these guys have waiting for us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-E09huy1yCZA/VgDXryaf4DI/AAAAAAAACkM/9H-gVl5veCw/s1600/DH98.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-E09huy1yCZA/VgDXryaf4DI/AAAAAAAACkM/9H-gVl5veCw/s640/DH98.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Zlf5S4VVJ5s/VgDXJ4IW0CI/AAAAAAAACkw/9L5qEB5HNTQ/s1600/DH101.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Zlf5S4VVJ5s/VgDXJ4IW0CI/AAAAAAAACkw/9L5qEB5HNTQ/s640/DH101.jpg&#34; width=&#34;426&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-_MZX-mLqOmk/VgDXXvX39eI/AAAAAAAACfU/Ez60Um5IwXw/s1600/DH46.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;426&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-_MZX-mLqOmk/VgDXXvX39eI/AAAAAAAACfU/Ez60Um5IwXw/s640/DH46.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;See you there, folks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Screening Phantasm With The Tall Man</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
         (Toby Marks)</author>
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-wTzO_bNWPPc/VWmzIHjOooI/AAAAAAAACAY/xoBh6Qosgpg/s1600/IMG_2740.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-wTzO_bNWPPc/VWmzIHjOooI/AAAAAAAACAY/xoBh6Qosgpg/s640/IMG_2740.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;From a respectful write-up on Texas Frightmare Weekend by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dreadcentral.com/news/101193/event-report-texas-frightmare-weekend-2015/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dread Central&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;tr_bq&#34;&gt;Can we stop calling Texas Frightmare Weekend a “regional con” now? The first reader I met this year was Aaron from Australia, who had flown all the way here to experience TFW as his &lt;i&gt;FIRST&lt;/i&gt; con.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I met that guy! Twice. Sat right next to him at the special 35mm screening of Phantasm at the Alamo Draft House in Richardson. Cool guy. He was in fact, the first person that I met as well on my little &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.texasfrightmareweekend.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Texas Frightmare Weekend&lt;/a&gt; adventure.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a name=&#39;more&#39;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-Bl7ymg6Dmkw/VWm3FKet3YI/AAAAAAAACAk/cvTEQWYZLvs/s1600/IMG_2733.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;357&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-Bl7ymg6Dmkw/VWm3FKet3YI/AAAAAAAACAk/cvTEQWYZLvs/s640/IMG_2733.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The day before TFW kicked off they did some screenings of old movies with stars in attendance. I heard about three. There was one they did with Sid Haig at the Old Texas Theater – &lt;b&gt;Whatever happened to Spider Baby&lt;/b&gt;, I believe it was. Then Neve Campbell was there at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://drafthouse.com/dfw&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Alamo Drafthouse&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;b&gt;Scream&lt;/b&gt;. That apparently happened just before I got there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-BwX5s0gcZGo/VWm3FKmsefI/AAAAAAAACAo/87dL5lZLmBE/s1600/IMG_2735.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-BwX5s0gcZGo/VWm3FKmsefI/AAAAAAAACAo/87dL5lZLmBE/s640/IMG_2735.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then there was the one I was there to see –&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;Phantasm&lt;/b&gt;, in glorious 35mm. It was to be the final ever screening in 35mm, as the film stock was deteriorating too badly. Apparently the reel we were watching was director Don Coscarelli&amp;rsquo;s own personal copy. The entire cast (minus Reggie Banister, who had a flight delay or some such issue) plus Mr. Coscarelli was in attendance giving live commentary throughout the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To be honest, this was the highlight of TFW for me and I&amp;rsquo;ll definitely be on the lookout for similar events next year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-U5GnljVZZHE/VWm88MXm9uI/AAAAAAAACA8/EUrmIOAu-0Q/s1600/IMG_2736.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-U5GnljVZZHE/VWm88MXm9uI/AAAAAAAACA8/EUrmIOAu-0Q/s640/IMG_2736.jpg&#34; width=&#34;482&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To those of you who do not live within near proximity of an Alamo Drafthouse, I&amp;rsquo;m sorry. There are plenty of cinema/eateries around, at least in Dallas, but imagine one run by cinephiles who also had a fondness for top-shelf liquor, and you&amp;rsquo;ve got Alamo Drafthouse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They do cutesy things with the menu like offer themed drinks and meals to go along with the movie you&amp;rsquo;re watching, because presumably they give a damn about what they are doing and the experience they provide to the patron. I had a glass of &amp;ldquo;Mother&amp;rsquo;s Milk&amp;rdquo;, for instance, while I watched Fury Road. A creamy concoction of Maker&amp;rsquo;s Mark and other stuff. &lt;i&gt;Actual&lt;/i&gt; mother&amp;rsquo;s milk? I don&amp;rsquo;t recall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, the halls are covered in retro movie posters whose awesomeness I can barely describe.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-vXQ0W8wpzCA/VWm-rd009GI/AAAAAAAACBM/nqDb8t5DggU/s1600/IMG_3209.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-vXQ0W8wpzCA/VWm-rd009GI/AAAAAAAACBM/nqDb8t5DggU/s640/IMG_3209.jpg&#34; width=&#34;478&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not ashamed to say I wanted to steal that one. But, you know, crime and the police and all. At a certain point in my childhood I &lt;i style=&#34;font-weight: bold;&#34;&gt;was &lt;/i&gt;that guy in the movie poster. Had my own ninja outfit, my own homemade (and some actual) ninja weapons, the whole ninja &lt;i&gt;schmear&lt;/i&gt;. I thought I was the only guy that remembered that movie. Still has what I consider to be the greatest choreographed fight scene of all time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/HBLKjfR9734&#34; width=&#34;480&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To kick off the screening, some guy from the Drafthouse came out to introduce Coscarelli and the rest of the cast. He was young guy. Cursed a lot, I thought maybe to identify with us fans, who were presumably a bunch of rough, cursing plebes. Immediately before that we were treated to an extended cut of the new &lt;b&gt;Phantasm Ravager&lt;/b&gt; movie currently in production, featuring all the members of the original cast. I have to say, what we saw looked great.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Wn9y34SVmrY/VWm88dMWvWI/AAAAAAAACBA/hVRXe0LsPiY/s1600/IMG_2738.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Wn9y34SVmrY/VWm88dMWvWI/AAAAAAAACBA/hVRXe0LsPiY/s640/IMG_2738.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The movie is still in the editing stages and it sounds like distribution is a little sketchy at the moment, but they hope to have something out this year. And it sounds like it&amp;rsquo;ll definitely be showing at the Alamo Drafthouse, so SCORE. You know I&amp;rsquo;ll be there, sipping a Phan-tini or something and eating a Ravageburger with Tall Fries.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-ke5RCLUHKJ0/VWnJBKynJ6I/AAAAAAAACBc/qtzM8I5S8A8/s1600/IMG_2746.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;356&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-ke5RCLUHKJ0/VWnJBKynJ6I/AAAAAAAACBc/qtzM8I5S8A8/s640/IMG_2746.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After some discussion about the new film with Coscarelli and the guy in charge of Ravager, they introduced the cast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don Coscarelli struck me as a very personable, approachable, interesting guy who enjoys and is still somewhat mystified by the success and endurance of this movie he made in his early twenties at his Mom&amp;rsquo;s house. I was pleasantly surprised to learn that his followup to Phantasm was &lt;a href=&#34;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Beastmaster&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Beastmaster&lt;/a&gt;, starring Marc Singer, also a favorite of mine as a young kid. I did not know that!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-Wso2cPkTlMk/VWnNB8cKOuI/AAAAAAAACBw/USrZpAnbcwE/s1600/images.jpeg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-Wso2cPkTlMk/VWnNB8cKOuI/AAAAAAAACBw/USrZpAnbcwE/s1600/images.jpeg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;David Hartman, the man pictured above just to the left of Coscarelli, is the director of Ravager. He has worked mostly as an animator and artist, and the vast majority of his experience as a director has been with children&amp;rsquo;s cartoons. He&amp;rsquo;s a big fan of the Phantasm series, though, and seemed honored to be asked to do direct the new movie. I forget exactly what his connection was to Coscarelli. I suppose you could &lt;a href=&#34;http://lmgtfy.com/?q=don+coscarelli+david+hartman+phantasm+ravager&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Google that if you cared&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-jiQTiTjWJ9A/VWqAbtpJAZI/AAAAAAAACCE/sfMnDHEjrnE/s1600/IMG_2744.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;clear: left; float: left; margin-bottom: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-jiQTiTjWJ9A/VWqAbtpJAZI/AAAAAAAACCE/sfMnDHEjrnE/s640/IMG_2744.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kat Lester had a fun and flirtatious personality. Obviously very proud of her role in the movie. She makes her living now as a vampy singer, I believe. She seemed to have a crush on Bill Thornbury, but it felt like part of the act.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Michael Baldwin, who played the kid &amp;ldquo;Mike&amp;rdquo; in Phantasm, was a wisecracking smartass, but in a charming way, I suppose. He skipped out halfway through the screening to flirt with some girls in the lobby. #Hollywood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More on Bill Thornbury later.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reggie Bannister couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it, as mentioned earlier, but according to Coscarelli and the rest of the cast the character you see in the movie is EXACTLY WHAT HE&amp;rsquo;S LIKE IN REAL LIFE. I would have like to have seen him drive up the Drafthouse in that ice cream truck, then. Probably has some pot-filled Klondike bars in there.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-CnsEXhRpr_w/VWnJBsSN7pI/AAAAAAAACBg/MB8kQFhveMo/s1600/IMG_2749.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-CnsEXhRpr_w/VWnJBsSN7pI/AAAAAAAACBg/MB8kQFhveMo/s640/IMG_2749.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Horror legend Angus Scrimm, the venerable &amp;ldquo;Tall Man&amp;rdquo; of the movie, shuffled to the front of the theater to the sound of thunderous applause and a standing ovation. As a kid, what impressed me about the character of the Tall Man was his weirdness; his awkward gait (a natural side-effect of the lifts he used to augment his height), his anachronistic haircut, his gruff and terse demeanor. In real life Angus Scrimm is nothing like that at all. He&amp;rsquo;s more like a genteel old grandpa, and is treated as such by his many adoring fans and no less so by his fellow cast members and associates. Angus is old, and he shows his age. He&amp;rsquo;s a little hard of hearing, a little slow to follow lines of conversation. But he could be witty, and gracious, and had just as good a recall of those events of the filming nearly forty(!) years ago as any of the others. Don and Kat seemed especially deferential to him.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After introducing everyone they had a short Q&amp;amp;A session. I really wasn&amp;rsquo;t prepared, but I did chime in to ask whatever happened to that sweet muscle car from the movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/xmWawY01Qvo&#34; width=&#34;480&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt; &lt;/div&gt;Coscarelli had a sad note to add to what he said in the above clip: last he heard the &amp;lsquo;Cuda was rusting away in some scrapyard in Florida, being used for parts. What an inglorious end to such a cool car! No word on whatever happened to Reggie&amp;rsquo;s ice cream truck.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/--nzsVIUgl68/VWyYzIZs5fI/AAAAAAAACCk/o4NgofZLD2U/s1600/IMG_2742.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;476&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/--nzsVIUgl68/VWyYzIZs5fI/AAAAAAAACCk/o4NgofZLD2U/s640/IMG_2742.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, my exclamation seemed to grab the attention of Bill Thornbury, who played Mike&amp;rsquo;s big brother in the movie. After the Q&amp;amp;A he walked over to shake hands with me and Aaron and another fellow with whom we were in conversation. By some amazing luck I managed to reserve seats directly behind where the cast was seated, and immediately behind Bill.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-GLge8ib4tow/VWybJD7kyYI/AAAAAAAACCw/vTTaXLdAmbQ/s1600/phantasm-ball-1008x515.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;326&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-GLge8ib4tow/VWybJD7kyYI/AAAAAAAACCw/vTTaXLdAmbQ/s640/phantasm-ball-1008x515.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turns out he&amp;rsquo;s a really cool, laid back kind of guy. He&amp;rsquo;s a real musician, too. He and Reggie did a little set at the Phantasm Ball the opening night of TFW. Regretfully I missed it, because I really, really wanted to hear the full-cut live performance of &lt;i&gt;Sitting Here at Midnight&lt;/i&gt;. Damn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FHuOAnSeF_c&#34; width=&#34;560&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the clip from the movie. I think you will agree it is HOT AS LOVE. When I met Aaron and our other acquaintance the next day at the ball, they let me know I missed the performance. Apparently they did like four songs together. Come to think of it, I never even &lt;i&gt;saw&lt;/i&gt;&amp;nbsp;Reggie Bannister the entire time, not even at the table. My loss!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of us asked Bill how he ended up getting cast in the movie, and his story was fairly typical, I guess. Agent hooked him up with an audition. He was playing in a band at the time. We chatted for a while. He thanked us for being fans and for coming out to the screening.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then kind of an odd thing happened.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-KHDAfJuI2_8/VW5-ibfFpgI/AAAAAAAACD4/dAfdt5y_J-I/s1600/Screen%2BShot%2B2015-06-01%2Bat%2B11.04.38%2BPM.png&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;460&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-KHDAfJuI2_8/VW5-ibfFpgI/AAAAAAAACD4/dAfdt5y_J-I/s640/Screen%2BShot%2B2015-06-01%2Bat%2B11.04.38%2BPM.png&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My new buddy Aaron had ordered one of those themed Alamo Draft-burgers I mentioned previously, but had left the pickle. Thornbury starts eyeing it and is like &amp;ldquo;You gonna eat that?&amp;rdquo; Aaron tries to pass it off real smooth like &amp;ldquo;No, man, go ahead. It&amp;rsquo;s all yours.&amp;rdquo;, but I could tell by that slight bit of hesitation before he spoke that he&amp;rsquo;s wondering like WTF? By that time Bill was already halfway through his pickle spear just kind of staring at us. Then he says&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;tr_bq&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&amp;ldquo;I never met a pickle I didn&amp;rsquo;t like.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s my Bill Thornbury story, ladies and gentlemen. What a cool guy. I will never watch Phantasm again without remembering that episode. He went to his seat after that, which as I said was directly in front of us, and we all kind of stared at each other like &amp;ldquo;Did that just happen?&amp;rdquo;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hollywood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The screening began, and I have to say the live commentary from Coscarelli and the cast was fantastically entertaining. They cracked jokes, they gave plenty of curious background details about the process of filming the movie, threw out some trivia, and gave their personal thoughts. It was fun, and intimate. I was surprised at how well they all seemed to get along together. They were totally comfortable with each other and exhibited an easy family dynamic that added a lot to the experience. It felt more like we were hanging out with them than listening to a lecture.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coscarelli tended to steer the commentary. He&amp;rsquo;d usually give some background information about the scene we were watching, then try to get the others to chime in with their perspectives.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-b2Kty7p4sy4/VW6IwN0pGKI/AAAAAAAACEU/M_dpCv7FK2c/s1600/Phantasm22.png&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;217&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-b2Kty7p4sy4/VW6IwN0pGKI/AAAAAAAACEU/M_dpCv7FK2c/s400/Phantasm22.png&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;I found the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.movie-locations.com/movies/p/Phantasm.html#.VW6KbWAurjI&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;filming locations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;particularly interesting. Mike and Jody&amp;rsquo;s house in Phantasm was really Coscarelli&amp;rsquo;s mother&amp;rsquo;s house. The cemetery scenes were shot at a public park. The fortuneteller&amp;rsquo;s house was a nearby abandoned home that was only recently was torn down. And the outside of the funeral home was an old historic building that is open to the public today.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-KP4WmypMe7g/VW6IwPfWeSI/AAAAAAAACEQ/dnuDdviAJjU/s1600/PHANTASM20MIKE20THE20SPY.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-KP4WmypMe7g/VW6IwPfWeSI/AAAAAAAACEQ/dnuDdviAJjU/s1600/PHANTASM20MIKE20THE20SPY.jpg&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They all had plenty of amusing stories to tell. In the scene above, for instance, Mike had to crawl through an unexpected pile of dog poop without breaking character in order to nail the scene. They all remarked on what a consummate actor he was, stoically delivering his lines whilst smeared with crap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Kat Lester, who seemed to enjoy playing the part of the weird seductress, was unusually quick to point out that she did &lt;b&gt;NOT&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;do any of the&amp;nbsp;nude scenes in the movie. Instead, stand-ins were used for the couple of scenes where the &amp;ldquo;action&amp;rdquo; got heated. She tried to embarrass Bill Thornbury during the makeout scenes, but my man was probably thinking about those pickles he just ate. Damn good pickles at the Drafthouse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-EI8357qjnyg/VXZqjnY8vLI/AAAAAAAACFI/L7PjTjDabRQ/s1600/7112_3.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;346&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-EI8357qjnyg/VXZqjnY8vLI/AAAAAAAACFI/L7PjTjDabRQ/s640/7112_3.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;Coscarelli mentioned being influenced by a few people that I also love, namely Ray Bradbury and Edgar Allen Poe. One influence he &lt;i&gt;didn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/i&gt; mention, though, was Frank Herbert. There were a couple of references in the movie to Herbert&amp;rsquo;s Dune novel. In the scene where Mike goes to visit the fortune teller he is asked to place his hand inside a mysterious box, after which he experiences great pain and cannot remove it from the box until he calms down and realizes that the pain is just an illusion or something. It&amp;rsquo;s a very close echo of the Gom Jabbar scene from the novel, where a young Paul Atreides has his manhood tested by use of a similar device.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-KvuQIbIXrlg/VXZpHw2r9fI/AAAAAAAACFA/iv6f498X4Ko/s1600/tumblr_l9flzzDgLA1qa9fbg.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;240&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-KvuQIbIXrlg/VXZpHw2r9fI/AAAAAAAACFA/iv6f498X4Ko/s320/tumblr_l9flzzDgLA1qa9fbg.jpg&#34; width=&#34;320&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then there&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;Dunes&amp;rdquo; cantina. Coincidence, or not-so-subtle nod? For all I know he forgot all about it. Dune would have been fairly popular at the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every now and again Don would ask Angus to recollect his experiences in a certain scene or with the filming generally. He seemed to have a little trouble following the conversation, but when he spoke he was articulate and often funny. He went on at length about what a great actor Mike Baldwin was during the MacGyver scene in which he breaks out of his room by taping a shotgun shell to a hammer and using that to blast a hole through the door. Though there was no dialog, you could follow his thought processes as he put his unlikely plan together. The Tall Man regarded that as consummate thespianship.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-6l92bfURvq8/VXZsaajA43I/AAAAAAAACFU/qW30zkQyQmY/s1600/28676.gif&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-6l92bfURvq8/VXZsaajA43I/AAAAAAAACFU/qW30zkQyQmY/s1600/28676.gif&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The only time Angus spoke up of his own volition was right after the scene with the fortune teller. He interrupted Kat, I believe, to mention that the girl in the scene, Terrie Kalbus, had disappeared in real life and was never heard from again. Nobody else seemed to want to touch that, and I felt there was just a slight moment of awkwardness before Don moved the conversation in another direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And so, unintentionally, Angus provided us with what was the only really spooky moment of the night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-IaJlEjc91ds/VXi_qY4qDoI/AAAAAAAACF0/BMXIsQG7Y18/s1600/IMG_2758.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-IaJlEjc91ds/VXi_qY4qDoI/AAAAAAAACF0/BMXIsQG7Y18/s640/IMG_2758.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Phantasm is an odd movie. There is a dreamlike quality to it, and in the end you find out it &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; all a dream. Or was it? Coscarelli mentioned that during the early test screenings one audience was so disappointed at the &amp;ldquo;dream&amp;rdquo; reveal that a number of them started to walk out at that point, only to be told by Angus, in his most intimidating Tall Man voice, to sit right back down and stay till the credits rolled. That must have been surreal. But if you buy the dream theory, then what happens to Mike at the end? But if it&amp;rsquo;s not a dream, then how do you make sense of everything that happens after they bury the Tall Man down the well? The real answer is that, similar to the conclusion of the fantastic series The Prisoner starring Patrick McGoohan, there was no real &amp;ldquo;master plan&amp;rdquo; for the ending; rather they patched together different segments to satisfy the audience after the original idea proved unpopular. Nobody knew how it was going to end. They filmed multiple endings and spliced at least two of them together. It&amp;rsquo;s confused, and doesn&amp;rsquo;t set up well for a sequel. It&amp;rsquo;s doubtful Coscarelli ever planned on one. But the ending works. It&amp;rsquo;s true to the oddness of the rest of the movie. Is it all a dream? A dream within a dream? The ends are loosely tied, leaving lots of room for interpretation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(It must be noted that the ending was controversial for the time. The bad guy won, didn&amp;rsquo;t he? The Tall Man lived, and he comes back for the good guy in the end. A kid, mind you. That just wasn&amp;rsquo;t done back in those days.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Cnrgx9YQm90/VXi_qLXwHMI/AAAAAAAACF4/qSBfsTp9wn8/s1600/IMG_2777.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;300&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Cnrgx9YQm90/VXi_qLXwHMI/AAAAAAAACF4/qSBfsTp9wn8/s400/IMG_2777.jpg&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My take on Phantasm? As I watched the movie that night up on the big screen, and for probably the fifth or sixth time, listening to the director and the stars give their takes on it, a new vision of the movie occurred to me. I once saw someone in a magazine describe Phantasm as a spooky after-school special (remember those?). I agree, though not in the sense he meant that. The movie is a dream, but not a literal one. It is a dreamlike exploration of a young man&amp;rsquo;s inner turmoil in dealing with the death of his family. Maybe it was a tragic accident, or maybe a series of accidents like the movie lays out, taking first his parents and then his older brother, but he&amp;rsquo;s left alone, and very suddenly. The Tall Man, the funeral home director, the undertaker, represents death, but also God, who has the power of life and death, and who takes people away without need for justification or explanation, for purposes of his own. Those left behind can only guess at what those are. Mike sets out on a path to confront the Tall Man, but the key to his victory is given away by the fortune teller. The pain that is holding Mike back, that is keeping him frozen, is just an illusion. Only when he learns to face his fears calmly and accept his situation can he hope to escape the black box of pain in which he is held. He is only partially successful, for though he is able to temporarily repress his feelings of grief, by &amp;ldquo;burying&amp;rdquo; the Tall Man down the well, they come back. In the dual symbolism mentioned above the return of the Tall Man at the end can also be seen as a manifestation of the inevitability of death; ultimately no one escapes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I walked away from the screening with a great sense of satisfaction. It was a night I enjoyed very much. While I was there I picked up a copy of Mondo&amp;rsquo;s new and beautifully packaged soundtrack, in LP format. Take a look.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;iframe allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/KVyByvtbKTw&#34; width=&#34;560&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for reading. If you liked this one, stayed tuned for my upcoming photo galleries from Texas Frightmare Weekend and Dark Hour Haunted House!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>A Visit to Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
         (Toby Marks)</author>
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</guid>
        <description>&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-5f6E4EuUntQ/VRbDEIWGqAI/AAAAAAAABws/owuiYxsrxGs/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B11.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-5f6E4EuUntQ/VRbDEIWGqAI/AAAAAAAABws/owuiYxsrxGs/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B11.jpg&#34; width=&#34;359&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966; font-family: &amp;quot;verdana&amp;quot; , sans-serif; font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;Dr. Channard from Hellraiser II, in all his glory&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;times&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;times new roman&amp;quot; , serif;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;times&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;times new roman&amp;quot; , serif;&#34;&gt;Collector&#39;s Crypt is a boutique shop in Dallas specializing in horror and sci-fi collectibles, memorabilia, paraphernalia, and… well, you just gotta see it, folks. It&#39;s an amazing place. I discovered them only recently after attending the St. Patrick&#39;s Slay Weekend event at &lt;a href=&#34;http://darkhourhauntedhouse.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Dark Hour Haunted House&lt;/a&gt; in Plano. They were a sponsor of that particular show, so Dark Hour graciously gave them some floor space to sell a few wares after the show and otherwise promote the store. Now it&#39;s not like Dallas has a whole lot of shops like this; in fact, I cannot think of &lt;i&gt;one other&lt;/i&gt;. So it piqued my interest. I noticed that they are located only a short distance across the river from where I currently work, so I decided to pop in on my next available lunch hour.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;times&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;times new roman&amp;quot; , serif;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;times&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;times new roman&amp;quot; , serif;&#34;&gt;I was not disappointed. In fact, what I found there &lt;i&gt;blew me away&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a name=&#39;more&#39;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-wr5bFFYqwGE/VRbDQFBI_EI/AAAAAAAAB0M/rnZYHwR_8ZI/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B9.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;222&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-wr5bFFYqwGE/VRbDQFBI_EI/AAAAAAAAB0M/rnZYHwR_8ZI/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B9.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966; font-family: &amp;quot;verdana&amp;quot; , sans-serif; font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;A Palace of the Weird&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Collector&#39;s Crypt is located not so much in a traditional storefront as in an older residential neighborhood. At first I thought I had the wrong place, but the shingle out front told me I had reached my proper destination. The building, or rather, the house — had the feel of some eccentric old grandma&#39;s residence; or maybe closer to autumn, of a &lt;i&gt;haunted house&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;As I stepped in the door I was greeted by a gnarled old butler who took my hat and coat as my eyes adjusted to the dim light of what I slowly realized was a &lt;b&gt;hall of dark wonders&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-oauvvNCubWs/VRbDPDZ__gI/AAAAAAAABz8/fpj89W9jc8Y/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B6.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-oauvvNCubWs/VRbDPDZ__gI/AAAAAAAABz8/fpj89W9jc8Y/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B6.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966; font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif; font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&#34;The doctor is in.&#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-mbXqjTf7DRg/VRbDFPOJUhI/AAAAAAAABxQ/1Cpib5wWGWU/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B15.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;478&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-mbXqjTf7DRg/VRbDFPOJUhI/AAAAAAAABxQ/1Cpib5wWGWU/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B15.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966; font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif; font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&#34;I RECOMMEND… AMPUTATION!&#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;My eyes were immediately drawn to the centerpiece of the room, and maybe even the whole store — an exquisitely carved, two foot resin model of Dr. Channard, the Johnny-come-lately Cenobite from Hellraiser II who somehow managed to kick the collective asses of all the established monsters in the movie. The detail on the piece is just incredible. You can hardly help gawking at it. I was doing just that when one of the friendly proprietresses noticed me. She introduced herself and explained that the piece comes with two interchangeable heads (one having a more placid, and one a more exercised expression) and is of the highest craftsmanship. She also gave me a little walkthrough of the store. I felt comfortable enough to ask her if I could snap some pictures, and she graciously allowed it.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-SRNSVRAwWjo/VRdtawrEtUI/AAAAAAAAB4o/xIXSM8TjVFo/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B33.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;478&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-SRNSVRAwWjo/VRdtawrEtUI/AAAAAAAAB4o/xIXSM8TjVFo/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B33.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966; font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif; font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;The haunted guestbook, a popular item this past Halloween&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The place has a few stock items, but the vast majority of the inventory is unlike anything I&#39;ve ever seen before. The place is loaded with antiques, and even better — custom made models and other memorabilia crafted &lt;i&gt;exclusively&lt;/i&gt; for the store. Some of their stuff you won&#39;t find anywhere else!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-1Ka-ZGnxXlw/VRdtWO1L_UI/AAAAAAAAB2s/k8D8GZWtqDI/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B2.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-1Ka-ZGnxXlw/VRdtWO1L_UI/AAAAAAAAB2s/k8D8GZWtqDI/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B2.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966; font-family: &amp;quot;verdana&amp;quot; , sans-serif; font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;HANDS OFF!!! THE COUNT IS MINE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Please do not visit the store and buy this beautiful etched plastic/plexiglass homage to Count Dracula. IT IS MINE. It belongs on my mantle next Halloween. I used some Photoshop chicanery to give it a spooky green coloring, but there&#39;s actually a little red lamp at the bottom that lights up all the etched borders from below. In a dark room, this would look magnificent. But you&#39;ll never know, &#39;cause I&#39;m going to buy it!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-oQQvAXhpQ24/VRdtYsg6s1I/AAAAAAAAB3w/L4dSP86GWO0/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B27.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;478&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-oQQvAXhpQ24/VRdtYsg6s1I/AAAAAAAAB3w/L4dSP86GWO0/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B27.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;70s Warhol kitsch with a &lt;i&gt;Tales From the Crypt&lt;/i&gt; veneer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-fMCS6JAHonE/VRdtXCglUEI/AAAAAAAAB3M/myHZTxODOhk/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B21.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;358&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-fMCS6JAHonE/VRdtXCglUEI/AAAAAAAAB3M/myHZTxODOhk/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B21.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Mutants, monsters, and old lace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Collector&#39;s Crypt has a large and varied inventory, from the gory to the fantastic. You can hardly move your eyes around without bumping them into a surprise or two, like the incredible selection of Godzilla merchandise on display. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-2d_lv9iviPI/VRdtZorb3pI/AAAAAAAAB4I/8sHvry01lvg/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B3.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;478&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-2d_lv9iviPI/VRdtZorb3pI/AAAAAAAAB4I/8sHvry01lvg/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B3.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;They almost seemed alive&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;That discovery really connected with me personally, because I recognized a few of those toys from the collection of an old childhood friend. I had not seen the like of them in thirty years. I remember visiting him at his Grandmother&#39;s house and watching Godzilla movies thrown up on the kitchen pantry doors by an old reel-to-reel projector borrowed from his dad. I remember the tin film canisters with the names of the movies written on tape labels, and the old lace curtains in his grandmother&#39;s dining room. Seeing this stuff gave me chills.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Y8ONIrnyelA/VRdtcJzeFvI/AAAAAAAAB5E/0rSJWtdFE38/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B5.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-Y8ONIrnyelA/VRdtcJzeFvI/AAAAAAAAB5E/0rSJWtdFE38/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B5.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Just your average, run of the mill, typical old dolls&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Every old doll is cursed. These were no spookier than the ones I remember in that old lady&#39;s collection back in Zapata, TX. Her house was filled with the things. How did she ever fall asleep?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-D9TG3Lf8MBQ/VRdtXhTW_kI/AAAAAAAAB3Q/qWijSSExZQk/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B23.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;358&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-D9TG3Lf8MBQ/VRdtXhTW_kI/AAAAAAAAB3Q/qWijSSExZQk/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B23.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Dr. Zaius hangs with Franken-Hitler&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-n9hBnOxQKBY/VRdtdF8deuI/AAAAAAAAB5c/MGCqgxZZQcg/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B8.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;240&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-n9hBnOxQKBY/VRdtdF8deuI/AAAAAAAAB5c/MGCqgxZZQcg/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B8.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;There&#39;s even an art gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Looking for some posters, movie prints, or horror-themed art? This place has it all. In fact, I&#39;m just now noticing that one of Frankenstein in profile. This is quality stuff, guys.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Q7ZBs9eLkbY/VRdtbMet-fI/AAAAAAAAB4s/9PC-hqY09kE/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B34.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Q7ZBs9eLkbY/VRdtbMet-fI/AAAAAAAAB4s/9PC-hqY09kE/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B34.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;A tribute poster to Ray Harryhausen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;One thing I admire about Collector&#39;s Crypt is that these guys have class. And they understand the roots of it all; the old Universal pantheon get the respect they deserve alongside modern greats like Freddy, Myers, and Pinhead. There&#39;s a place for everybody under this roof. They even have a whole room devoted to the characters of Tim Burton. How&#39;s that for weird?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-uDzhsvSDPeg/VRdtbklWioI/AAAAAAAAB44/Hw7aBjSTXs8/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B4.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-uDzhsvSDPeg/VRdtbklWioI/AAAAAAAAB44/Hw7aBjSTXs8/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B4.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;A trick of light and shadow, or a waking nightmare? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The ghost of Freddy Kreuger seemed to follow me in this room. Looking back, I can&#39;t seem to recall exactly what cast this apparition-like reflection on the glass. Was it only a reflection? &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-AXeDMpzys68/VRdtWRbSZrI/AAAAAAAAB28/CpYts_ODAjY/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B20.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-AXeDMpzys68/VRdtWRbSZrI/AAAAAAAAB28/CpYts_ODAjY/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B20.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Hey, I love Phantasm as much as the next guy…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I think maybe for that much I would expect the ball to really fly around, drilling holes in the heads of my enemies. Yes, some of the prices are a bit steep, but the place appeals to collectors, and the prices&amp;nbsp; reflect that a lot of these items are one of kind pieces, custom made for the store.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-wvhKZR2aV04/VRdtXOe4C4I/AAAAAAAAB3E/7a_R_E0Lddo/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B22.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-wvhKZR2aV04/VRdtXOe4C4I/AAAAAAAAB3E/7a_R_E0Lddo/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B22.jpg&#34; width=&#34;360&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Peeking into the Tim Burton room&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-ydJxuZJ7ks0/VRdtVWf0DsI/AAAAAAAAB2c/NAegm1tVjeA/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B16.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;252&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-ydJxuZJ7ks0/VRdtVWf0DsI/AAAAAAAAB2c/NAegm1tVjeA/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B16.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;For all your Tim Burton needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Homage, museum, bazaar? The Tim Burton showcase felt like all of those things. I&#39;m not a huge Burton guy myself, but it was fun poking my head around and scoping out all the oddities. I only wish I had got more pictures of the all the Edward Scissorhand merch, &#39;cause there was plenty.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-_B6f_Hx6NKs/VRdtUArPAnI/AAAAAAAAB18/3gW8C9_yjVM/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B13.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;478&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-_B6f_Hx6NKs/VRdtUArPAnI/AAAAAAAAB18/3gW8C9_yjVM/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B13.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Inspiration for the Monster High dolls?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-9W5KLbxOYEk/VRdtUc0bFyI/AAAAAAAAB2I/2BCeS7HwDng/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B14.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;356&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-9W5KLbxOYEk/VRdtUc0bFyI/AAAAAAAAB2I/2BCeS7HwDng/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B14.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Scenes and characters from &lt;i&gt;A Nightmare Before Christmas&lt;/i&gt; were of course a huge part of the... exhibit?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Bsav26t1474/VRdtc-eaSYI/AAAAAAAAB5Y/xotBJK5cQ_k/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B7.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Bsav26t1474/VRdtc-eaSYI/AAAAAAAAB5Y/xotBJK5cQ_k/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B7.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Sorry, Jack, &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am the Pumpkin King&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Nobody was around, so I had to get a selfie with this life-sized(?) Jack Skellington mannequin. He watches over all the Tim Burton collection. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-atnnTC8wcxs/VRdtYf3iCqI/AAAAAAAAB3o/bi5SwCWVG8Y/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B26.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-atnnTC8wcxs/VRdtYf3iCqI/AAAAAAAAB3o/bi5SwCWVG8Y/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B26.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;She was part of a set, with Jack on the right&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This comic portrait of Sally may have been the only piece of Tim Burton swag that I&#39;d actually walk away with. But if you&#39;re into Burton&#39;s oeuvre, this is definitely the place to come and load up. Not pictured in the corner of the room next to Sally is a little shelf devoted to Munsters memorabilia. I tell you, this place has it all!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-PK4uYrJvcPY/VRdtX6rCdBI/AAAAAAAAB3Y/eAcDGUecGSQ/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B24.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;356&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-PK4uYrJvcPY/VRdtX6rCdBI/AAAAAAAAB3Y/eAcDGUecGSQ/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B24.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Mike Myers sits comfortably next to toy robots and giant flies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;A lot of the store seemed less like a market, and more like the playhouse of some demented little rich kid.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-I4UjqI5GsQU/VRdtasltDMI/AAAAAAAAB4g/W_yiXRijKp0/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B32.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-I4UjqI5GsQU/VRdtasltDMI/AAAAAAAAB4g/W_yiXRijKp0/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B32.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Mermaid, but not little&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;times&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;times new roman&amp;quot; , serif;&#34;&gt;I&#39;ll be honest with you, I couldn&#39;t figure out &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;times&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;times new roman&amp;quot; , serif;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;times&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;times new roman&amp;quot; , serif;&#34;&gt;exactly &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;who this piece was supposed to appeal to, or for what occasion this was imagined to be appropriate. Maybe for taking out on the road, charging rubes five bucks a head for a peek? Very Bradbury-esque, this one.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/--hmjARkx2fY/VRdtZc_3fPI/AAAAAAAAB34/8NyDhbyXz_k/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B29.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/--hmjARkx2fY/VRdtZc_3fPI/AAAAAAAAB34/8NyDhbyXz_k/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B29.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;A little Dallas humor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Ah, the ebola days. What a time to live and work in Dallas. I stopped taking the train in as soon as the news broke, for fear it would be a perfect disease vector. And it is, too, but more so for colds and flu. This piece manages to reference and lampoon the disease without crossing the line into bad taste. A nice feat!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Aar-T_sRoc4/VRdtbipXCbI/AAAAAAAAB48/U0FzXEn0VXg/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B35.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Aar-T_sRoc4/VRdtbipXCbI/AAAAAAAAB48/U0FzXEn0VXg/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B35.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Universal appeal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I love this model series so much. Exquisite likenesses and marvelous detail. The Universal Monsters are well represented and very much beloved at Collector&#39;s Crypt. And is that a Frankenstein cookie jar I see back there?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-YIMXhoBS0CU/VRdtY63EKuI/AAAAAAAAB30/5AiMT78sQKc/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B28.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;478&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-YIMXhoBS0CU/VRdtY63EKuI/AAAAAAAAB30/5AiMT78sQKc/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B28.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;The Bride and her cronies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I&#39;ve noticed that the Bride of Frankenstein seems to be enjoying something of a resurgence these past few years, after being traditionally relegated to second-tier monster status. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-EyPc9WFCrQc/VRdteGVtAmI/AAAAAAAAB5w/9R3qb0JW4xk/s1600/FullSizeRender.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;478&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-EyPc9WFCrQc/VRdteGVtAmI/AAAAAAAAB5w/9R3qb0JW4xk/s1600/FullSizeRender.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;The Creature&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;...much like the long neglected Creature From the Black Lagoon, whose line of merchandise now includes such oddities as &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ebay.com/itm/Universal-Monsters-CREATURE-OF-THE-BLACK-LAGOON-STRING-LIGHT-SET-New-Gillman-/191028087158?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0&amp;amp;hash=item2c7a294976&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Halloween string lights&lt;/a&gt;. Somebody there must be a real fan, because he gets a whole shelf dedicated exclusively to him.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-k65rWZg5wfE/VRdtZ4El1JI/AAAAAAAAB4Q/uCgZLtSbE88/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B31.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-k65rWZg5wfE/VRdtZ4El1JI/AAAAAAAAB4Q/uCgZLtSbE88/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B31.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;There&#39;s plenty of sci-fi memorabilia, too&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In addition to Godzilla and crew, you can find custom models including Klaatu from The Day the Earth Stood Still, that cabbage-headed alien from The Twilight Zone, Morlocks from The Time Machine, the This Island Earth creature, and a ton more only vaguely familiar beasties from the Golden Age of Sci-Fi, if you&#39;re into that kind of thing. There&#39;s also a real-life Chucky doll. See it?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-U9W_qpi1vs0/VRdtVLQ-E7I/AAAAAAAAB2Y/CNZfJ-L81JQ/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B18.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;478&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-U9W_qpi1vs0/VRdtVLQ-E7I/AAAAAAAAB2Y/CNZfJ-L81JQ/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B18.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Something eerily reminiscent of the monster from Pee Wee&#39;s Playhouse&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The place just overflows with oddness. There are a thousand things you&#39;ve never seen before. &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-jALtrxIXy5M/VRdtTbj-WhI/AAAAAAAAB1o/2-LPRCrswR4/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B12.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-jALtrxIXy5M/VRdtTbj-WhI/AAAAAAAAB1o/2-LPRCrswR4/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B12.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;The house is not just lined with goodies, but decorated with them&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;times&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;times new roman&amp;quot; , serif;&#34;&gt;It&#39;s obvious that these guys love their work. The shop is more than just that; it&#39;s an intentional homage to the macabre and fantastic. It&#39;s a true museum of the weird.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-BwDPKhGbLOg/VRdtZ0dZ6hI/AAAAAAAAB4M/NNUlJaUn2rY/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B30.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-BwDPKhGbLOg/VRdtZ0dZ6hI/AAAAAAAAB4M/NNUlJaUn2rY/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B30.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;What is that thing?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Please visit Collector&#39;s Crypt and buy this stuff. If you see something you like here and you don&#39;t live in Dallas, call them and ask them to ship it to you. I&#39;m sure they can arrange something. Ghoulies like the one above come straight from the Island of Misfit Toys. They need a home.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-gPuATzinxKk/VRdtTstyzUI/AAAAAAAAB1w/YDliODquAQc/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B10.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-gPuATzinxKk/VRdtTstyzUI/AAAAAAAAB1w/YDliODquAQc/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B10.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;They got comics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Comics, records, CDs, DVDs, magazines (including Famous Monsters of Filmland), and all manner of media can be found in a little room at the back. You could spend hours searching through those shelves and bins. I was there for thirty minutes. You think I found all the treasures in that place? Hardly. So much more to discover. And the stock switches up regularly. How do I know that? Talk to the owners. They&#39;re really nice people. And they know Elvira.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-67F22CjpWC8/VRdtV08WGyI/AAAAAAAAB2o/WFG59gjoNNY/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B19.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-67F22CjpWC8/VRdtV08WGyI/AAAAAAAAB2o/WFG59gjoNNY/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B19.jpg&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;What I look like in the bathroom mirror at 6am&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-WSnMuhtboGg/VRdtVGt_vvI/AAAAAAAAB2g/nfg5t7UPEMU/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B17.jpg&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-WSnMuhtboGg/VRdtVGt_vvI/AAAAAAAAB2g/nfg5t7UPEMU/s1600/FullSizeRender%2B17.jpg&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Toys that you didn&#39;t think existed anymore. They&#39;re here!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I remember this &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.monsterscenes.net/mskits.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;line of model kits&lt;/a&gt; from when I was a kid, advertised in the back of old magazines like Fangoria. They were apparently banned for being too gruesome and exploitative. They&#39;re back. You know what I love about them? They don&#39;t merchandise any movie (not that that&#39;s inherently bad), they don&#39;t try to &#34;sell&#34; you anything at all. They&#39;re not about branding or tie-ins or anything like that. They just exist to celebrate the idea of mad scientists and mutant insects. They&#39;re pure in that way. And that&#39;s really what makes them seem so anachronistic. This one model, moderately priced, tucked away on a far corner shelf, seemed to me to be one of the greatest hidden treasures in the whole place. It might go ignored forever, easily overlooked, but if you have the spirit to appreciate it — man, what a steal.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-cT-rpm7PZ04/VRdtekHF4GI/AAAAAAAAB6E/0cbxEMn-qbk/s1600/IMG_1565.JPG&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-cT-rpm7PZ04/VRdtekHF4GI/AAAAAAAAB6E/0cbxEMn-qbk/s1600/IMG_1565.JPG&#34; width=&#34;480&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Be seeing you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-7g4dKWZOU_8/VRdtfe9-ZxI/AAAAAAAAB6U/lEtQowiflc8/s1600/IMG_1571.JPG&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-7g4dKWZOU_8/VRdtfe9-ZxI/AAAAAAAAB6U/lEtQowiflc8/s1600/IMG_1571.JPG&#34; width=&#34;360&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;My takeaway&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I left the store with a few smaller items and mementos for the kids. This one was probably my favorite. A vintage Burger King Kid&#39;s Club prize — a surprisingly high quality Dracula action figure with coffin included. Even came in the original protective sleeve. At the time they had like 20 Wolfmen, but only one Dracula. I picked up one of each. Frankenstein and the Creature From the Black Lagoon round out the set. I&#39;ll certainly be back to look for those.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-Fd59bwJrXTU/VRdte5SoHNI/AAAAAAAAB6I/33-QYRMPoAQ/s1600/IMG_1570.JPG&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;640&#34; src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-Fd59bwJrXTU/VRdte5SoHNI/AAAAAAAAB6I/33-QYRMPoAQ/s1600/IMG_1570.JPG&#34; width=&#34;360&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-family: &amp;quot;helvetica neue&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;arial&amp;quot; , &amp;quot;helvetica&amp;quot; , sans-serif;&#34;&gt;Best Prize Ever?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Collector&#39;s Crypt is a spectacular place. There is nothing else even remotely like it in Dallas. I look forward to returning there many times between now and Halloween. May they grow and thrive for years to come!&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: small;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;GO! &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.collectors-crypt.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;166&#34; src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/--l7W9jxGV9Y/VReIEq4-KDI/AAAAAAAAB6w/kAeDM7Me9tQ/s1600/77259c_c0c5d7dce0db40828b6997da652f2a36.jpg_srb_p_492_492_75_22_0.50_1.20_0.jpg&#34; width=&#34;200&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: large;&#34;&gt;CRAWL!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: large;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/CollectorsCrypt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; height=&#34;55&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-e_nnCgkTpN8/VReKUaDddfI/AAAAAAAAB68/rhB7H511tUY/s1600/Screen%2BShot%2B2015-03-29%2Bat%2B12.14.36%2BAM.png&#34; width=&#34;200&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;color: #ffd966;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;font-size: x-large;&#34;&gt;LIKE!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Mask of the Red Death</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-mask-of-the-red-death/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
         (Toby Marks)</author>
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-mask-of-the-red-death/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-LG5tJUTc_xU/VEJuvEURinI/AAAAAAAABis/MisjKk3frhA/s1600/IMG_2405.JPG&#34; imageanchor=&#34;1&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;&#34;&gt;&lt;img border=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-LG5tJUTc_xU/VEJuvEURinI/AAAAAAAABis/MisjKk3frhA/s1600/IMG_2405.JPG&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;The &amp;lsquo;Red Death&amp;rsquo; had long devastated the country. No pestilence had ever been so fatal, or so hideous. Blood was its Avatar and its seal — the redness and the horror of blood. There were sharp pains, and sudden dizziness, and then profuse bleeding at the pores, with dissolution.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;With such precautions the courtiers might bid defiance to contagion. The external world could take care of itself.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;All these and security were within. Without was the &amp;lsquo;Red Death.&amp;rsquo;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;His vesture was dabbled in &lt;i&gt;blood&lt;/i&gt;&amp;nbsp;— and his broad brow, with all the features of the face, was besprinkled with the scarlet horror.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;separator&#34; style=&#34;clear: both; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;From The Masque of the Red Death, By Edgar Allen Poe. You can read the &lt;a href=&#34;http://xroads.virginia.edu/~Hyper/POE/masque.html&#34;&gt;full story online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
