<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mexican Food on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/mexican-food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mexican Food on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 16:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/mexican-food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bollywood Burrito</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-bollywood-burrito/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-bollywood-burrito/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Sq3xak90kZg/V6zwoaw0I7I/AAAAAAAAC40/evK2MCidSAEDtEYEMePNyQVFAWYgzkF1QCLcB/s640/IMG_5441.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember Taco Naan, the Mexican-Indian hybrid restaurant &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/&#34;&gt;I wrote about&lt;/a&gt; a long time back? I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the very same one my buddy &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/2015/03/texas-taco-challenge-taco-naan-vs-fuel.html&#34;&gt;Brian featured&lt;/a&gt; on his second trip to the Big D, where he stacked up its offerings against the nationally renowned taco dive Fuel City. Well, they&amp;rsquo;re still around and busier and better than ever! The place is expanding like mad, doubling its interior floor space and hopefully renovating those dismal restrooms. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know because I&amp;rsquo;ve never had the courage to try them again. But you don&amp;rsquo;t go to Taco Naan to use the bathroom, man, so no worries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Naan Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/</guid>
      <description>Go back, right now, and take a look at my Zyka India Food restaurant review. Notice anything suspicious about the Chicken 65? Take a closer look at those ingredients. 

Jalapenos. Onions. Cilantro. Sound familiar? 
If you&amp;rsquo;re from Texas or anywhere in the Southwest you would immediately associate that combination with Mexican or Tex-Mex cuisine. There are other similarities, too, like the general spiciness, the use of chilis, or the penchant for using circular flatbread at every meal to sandwich ingredients and sop up sauces.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>