<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Youtube on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/youtube/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Youtube on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 15:33:03 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/youtube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to 2019</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2019-01-02-jazz-noir/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 15:33:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2019-01-02-jazz-noir/</guid>
      <description>Some sounds for dark days, and nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few of My Favorite Christmas Songs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-12-21-my-favorite-christmas-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:44:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-12-21-my-favorite-christmas-songs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/S6wDzvibd_Q&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Hands down my favorite Christmas song of 2018. I passed up this album in favor of Jackie Gleason&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Tis The Season&lt;/em&gt;, a purchase I do not regret, but this song is definitely worth the price of the vinyl. I love it when Frank sings melancholy, and this one has that quality in spades. Nostalgia, regret, and loneliness are all wrapped up in that golden bow of his amazing voice, a voice that forces your ears to attention when you hear it, never aging, never dulling, calling your life before your eyes, and all but materializing that glass of whiskey or scotch in your left hand, as your right hand reaches to pull the brim of your fedora down a little more to cover the tears in your eyes. Merry Christmas!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween is Officially On Hold</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-10-31-halloween-postponed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:34:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-10-31-halloween-postponed/</guid>
      <description>October, you have been one long, soggy mess. C&amp;rsquo;est la vie, I suppose. To commemorate what I anticipate to be tonight&amp;rsquo;s non-event, I have chosen this song to be the official &amp;ldquo;hold&amp;rdquo; music of Halloween 2018, to be played in a continuous loop until one metaphorically throws up one&amp;rsquo;s hands in disgust, and finally gives up the game. To pick it up again next year? Perhaps. But never quite in the same way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Long, San Francisco</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-10-26-so-long-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 00:24:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-10-26-so-long-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>A song to fit a very particular mood. It&amp;rsquo;s been a significant week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Once Upon a Time, Frank Sinatra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-10-17-frank-sinatra-once-upon-a-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 16:17:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-10-17-frank-sinatra-once-upon-a-time/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — The Great Pumpkin Waltz</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cover-battle-the-great-pumpkin-waltz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cover-battle-the-great-pumpkin-waltz/</guid>
      <description>We are officially in the &amp;ldquo;-BER months&amp;rdquo; now, a time of year that for my generation is indelibly stamped by the melancholy Peanuts cartoon soundtracks of Vince Guiraldi and his trio. Though the nostalgic quality of these tracks reaches fever pitch around Christmastime, we begin our seasonal contemplation with this wistful little tune, quickly supplanted in the Guiraldi lineup, but never quite forgotten. It remains one of my favorites, but I&amp;rsquo;ll only listen to it from the start of September through Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Spooks on YouTube: Apparitions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for something spooky to watch as we wind our way down to Halloween, but find yourself bored by the usual fare of cheesy monster movies or gross slasher flicks? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re in the mood for something a little more thoughtful; a little more substantial, perhaps? Let me show you something interesting.
 Apparitions&amp;nbsp;is a BBC miniseries about a Catholic exorcist who finds himself at the center of a satanic intrigue that reaches to the Vatican and threatens the world itself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>