<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>movies on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</title>
    <link>https://tobyblog.com/tags/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in movies on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2024 (c) Toby Marks</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tobyblog.com/tags/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Detective Pikachu Was As Good As It Could Be</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190514-detective-pikachu-was-as-good-as-it-could-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190514-detective-pikachu-was-as-good-as-it-could-be/</guid>
      <description>In other news, I saw Detective Pikachu with the family a few days ago, and I think we all left impressed. Some strong acting and genuinely funny moments. Pikachu singing the Pokémon cartoon theme song was a highlight for me. But does Ryan Reynolds have to be in literally every movie now? That being said, he did a wonderful job. A really enjoyable and charming movie. Go see it. With your kids, of course.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tonight You Belong To Me</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190305-the-jerk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 23:39:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190305-the-jerk/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had this song stuck in my head for a couple of days, and maybe if I post it I can get rid of it. It&amp;rsquo;s from The Jerk, and features Bernadette Peters, my first screen crush when I was just a little kid. That bit at the end where she pulls out the coronet still cracks me up. Still, it&amp;rsquo;s a touching scene, don&amp;rsquo;t you think? A little reminder that life can be sweet sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Hell is This Poster For the Sonic the Hedgehog Movie?</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190222-sonic-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 22:27:13 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190222-sonic-movie/</guid>
      <description>The Sonic the Hedgehog movie comes out this year.&#xA;Are you hyped, nostalgia boys?!&#xA;Because if you look at this poster and get hyped, I&amp;rsquo;m calling the cops. Seriously, who designed this freakish movie poster and why is he/she not in jail/hell?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So Sick</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20180328-so-sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:46:49 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20180328-so-sick/</guid>
      <description>Being sick on a trip is the worst. I&amp;rsquo;ve mostly been sleeping every spare moment I get. Managed to catch a pretty decent cheese ball of a movie, though. It was old school campy fun in the best way. Nicely captured the feel of old 80s schlock-horror movies like The Gate and Return of the Living Dead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazing 30th Anniversary Movies</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20160606-amazing-30th-anniversary-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20160606-amazing-30th-anniversary-movies/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the 30th anniversary of two very special, very &amp;ldquo;eighties&amp;rdquo; movies that I happen to love. The (legitimate) Transformers The Movie, and Space Camp, which I watched for the first time only a year or so ago with the kids.&#xA;I honestly can&amp;rsquo;t remember when I first saw the Transformers movie, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the theaters. I was the only one of my group of friends that caught it months, if not years later, after it came out on VHS.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Spooks on YouTube: Apparitions</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20150831-free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20150831-free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for something spooky to watch as we wind our way down to Halloween, but find yourself bored by the usual fare of cheesy monster movies or gross slasher flicks? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re in the mood for something a little more thoughtful; a little more substantial, perhaps? Let me show you something interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/DPDeV43LDds&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Real Star of Phantasm</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20140919-the-real-star-of-phantasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 22:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20140919-the-real-star-of-phantasm/</guid>
      <description>Here you go, folks, the real star of Phantasm — that bad-ass muscle car! A real thing of beauty, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even that much of a car guy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
