<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>potato chips on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/potato-chips/</link>
    <description>Recent content in potato chips on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 21:58:19 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/potato-chips/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cajun Treats</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/cajun-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 21:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/cajun-treats/</guid>
      <description>This video is something of a personal achievement, having been now just under two years in the making, and passing, as it does, yet another milestone in the revitalization of this little blog. Yeah, I know, that&amp;rsquo;s sort of a grandiose way to introduce a video where I discuss the merits of quail eggs and potato chips with friends and family, but there we are. It means something to me — hard to quantify — to be active on the site again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2015-2016</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again folks, that magical time between Christmas and New Year where thoughtful commentators like myself come out with their end of year retrospectives; and continuing a tradition I established a couple of years back on this site, I intend to give you my take on the best of my buddy Brian Hammons&#39; output over on the internet&amp;rsquo;s most beloved nostalgia blog, ReviewTheWorld.com.
You can catch up on previous years&#39; content by taking a look at my other lists:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snickers Varieties and Lays Cappuccino Chips</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/snickers-varieties-and-lays-cappuccino-chips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/snickers-varieties-and-lays-cappuccino-chips/</guid>
      <description>To celebrate the recent one year anniversary of our father/son Tumblr site, TheVCubeSolver and I teamed up to review an assortment of Snickers bars we found at CVS. And as a special bonus, we take a look at the trendy new Lays Cappuccino potato chips.
Enjoy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
