<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 16:07:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bollywood Burrito</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-bollywood-burrito/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-bollywood-burrito/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Sq3xak90kZg/V6zwoaw0I7I/AAAAAAAAC40/evK2MCidSAEDtEYEMePNyQVFAWYgzkF1QCLcB/s640/IMG_5441.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember Taco Naan, the Mexican-Indian hybrid restaurant &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/&#34;&gt;I wrote about&lt;/a&gt; a long time back? I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the very same one my buddy &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/2015/03/texas-taco-challenge-taco-naan-vs-fuel.html&#34;&gt;Brian featured&lt;/a&gt; on his second trip to the Big D, where he stacked up its offerings against the nationally renowned taco dive Fuel City. Well, they&amp;rsquo;re still around and busier and better than ever! The place is expanding like mad, doubling its interior floor space and hopefully renovating those dismal restrooms. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know because I&amp;rsquo;ve never had the courage to try them again. But you don&amp;rsquo;t go to Taco Naan to use the bathroom, man, so no worries.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Czech Stop and Slovaceks</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-czech-stop-and-slovaceks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-czech-stop-and-slovaceks/</guid>
      <description>After a long hiatus, my front seat food review series is back! This time I feature some of the Waco area&amp;rsquo;s finest gas station Czech cuisine. If you&amp;rsquo;re ever in the area you should absolutely stop at one or both of these fine establishments. Such a treat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tobyblog Thanksgiving Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-tobyblog-thanksgiving-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-tobyblog-thanksgiving-special/</guid>
      <description>After taking some time off to contemplate the overwhelming success of my Burger King poop tweet*, we now return to our regularly scheduled programming.
In truth October is always a busy month for us and I don&amp;rsquo;t have much spare time for blogging. This past Halloween was without a doubt the best yet, but I&amp;rsquo;ll save that retrospective for another day. For today we find ourselves at the end of November, as grand a month as any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprechers Root Beer Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/sprechers-root-beer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/sprechers-root-beer-review/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating our third anniversary of Buddy Team reviews, TheVCubeSolver and I team up to tackle the legendary Sprechers Root Beer. It&amp;rsquo;s good stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Chix Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-chix-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-chix-review/</guid>
      <description>We have reached &#34;Peak Blogger&#34; in this society, folks. If the existence of Tobyblog was not proof of that already, take a look at the above picture. It was a cold, blustery Saturday afternoon and I was visiting nearby Arlington. It was around lunchtime and I had some time to kill, so I decided to walk over to the nearby strip mall and scope out the restaurants. There were a surprising number of cuisines on offer for such a small area, but this place caught my eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liver and Gizzards Review, with Sriracha Whoopie Pies</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/liver-and-gizzards-review-with-sriracha-whoopie-pies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/liver-and-gizzards-review-with-sriracha-whoopie-pies/</guid>
      <description>My buddy Brian Hammons over at Review the World requested another video food review, so I though I&amp;rsquo;d introduce him to a down-home treat from my childhood. I hope you&amp;rsquo;re happy with the results. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, this one is a bit of a deep dive; a little something for my hardcore devotees. That is, people that like watching me eat stuff in my car. And yes, I manage to add yet another stain to my car seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Food Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/new-orleans-food-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/new-orleans-food-review/</guid>
      <description>New Orleans is, of course, a city known for its food, home to some of the best chefs in the country. I was in town recently, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d check out some of the local establishments and give you guys a virtual sight-tasting tour. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the hotel vending machine.


Hey, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten all day and I had a couple of hours to kill till my family showed up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>