<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Soda Pop on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/soda-pop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Soda Pop on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 23:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/soda-pop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2015-2016</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again folks, that magical time between Christmas and New Year where thoughtful commentators like myself come out with their end of year retrospectives; and continuing a tradition I established a couple of years back on this site, I intend to give you my take on the best of my buddy Brian Hammons&amp;rsquo; output over on the internet&amp;rsquo;s most beloved nostalgia blog, ReviewTheWorld.com.
You can catch up on previous years&amp;rsquo; content by taking a look at my other lists:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/halloween-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/halloween-special/</guid>
      <description>I love Halloween. You do, too. This video is a tribute to that season, to every memory and every thrill. To cold autumn nights. To the warm glow of jack o&amp;rsquo; lanterns. To spooky stories and cozy evenings. To every bit of magic and adventure in our lives. This is the story of Halloween 2013 as we experienced it; what has gone down in our lives and memories as THE BEST HALLOWEEN EVER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Dias De Los Muertos at World Market</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</guid>
      <description>Already a great place to find exotic candies, foreign soda pop, and specialty food items at any time of the year (Brian Hammons, you know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about), World Market really comes alive for Halloween. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got one in your area, get down there right now and check their selection. The stuff they carry is definitely outside of the Target/Big Lots/Dollar Store Halloween mold, but that&amp;rsquo;s not to say it&amp;rsquo;s super expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taki&#39;s, Cane Sugar Soda Pops</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</guid>
      <description>This is an older review from TheVCubeSolver and I very much inspired by the hijinks of Brian Hammons and the gang over at Review the World. In it we take a look at a couple of different varieties of Taki&amp;rsquo;s chips and some cane sugar soda pops we picked up at the local coffee shop. 
Oh, and you&amp;rsquo;ll notice I&amp;rsquo;m calling myself &amp;ldquo;Meeks, the Pedestrian&amp;rdquo;. Cause we were trying to have code names or something.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>