<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/categories/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 17:33:01 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/categories/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tia Lupita is Literal Awesome Sauce</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tia-lupita-and-yellowbird/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 17:33:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tia-lupita-and-yellowbird/</guid>
      <description>Of the craft sauces listed in the article, I can personally vouch for Tia Lupita (red, not the salsa verde) and pretty much all of the Yellowbird sauces from Austin. The thing that really sets Tia Lupita apart its strong cumin-y flavor, which I happen to love. That stuff is really great on eggs, but honestly goes with almost everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quarantine Cocktail Hour: Amaretto and Ginger</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/quarantine-cocktail-hour-amaretto-and-ginger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 17:17:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/quarantine-cocktail-hour-amaretto-and-ginger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1588198735/img/IMG_6887.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Welcome!&lt;/em&gt; Glad to have you over. Pull up a stool or something, cause it&amp;rsquo;s cocktail hour at the blog, and today we&amp;rsquo;re trying an idea I got from the folks over at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thrillist.com/drink/nation/what-to-mix-with-amaretto-cocktail-recipes&#34;&gt;Thrillist&lt;/a&gt; — an amaretto and ginger beer mixer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elote Ramen May be the King of Fusion Cuisine</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/elote-ramen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 08:41:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/elote-ramen/</guid>
      <description>This comes courtesy of good buddy Brian Hammons at reviewtheworld.com, now celebrating its 15th year on the internet, I believe. As if I didn&amp;rsquo;t need another reason during this lockdown to get my hands on some Tajin.
I tell you, fans, I could not be more ready to reintroduce cheese into my diet.
  Haters be silent. Cheese in ramen is a cheap American innovation, granted, but ramen is nothing if not versatile and accommodating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rim a Bloody Mary with Tajin?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tajin-seasoning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 16:30:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tajin-seasoning/</guid>
      <description>Man, I can&amp;rsquo;t wait till we can have some real Tex-Mex food again. And drink. 😞</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hogs Head Cheese: A Disappearing Delicacy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/hogs-head-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 09:28:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/hogs-head-cheese/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t claim that I was one who helped to postpone the extinction. Somebody told me once as a kid that it contained pig&amp;rsquo;s brains, so I never ate it. It pretty much looked like jello&amp;rsquo;d meat, too, which didn&amp;rsquo;t add to the appeal. I&amp;rsquo;d try it today, though, if I still lived there, and probably would like it. Vinegar and pork is not a bad combo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Food Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/new-orleans-food-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/new-orleans-food-review/</guid>
      <description>New Orleans is, of course, a city known for its food, home to some of the best chefs in the country. I was in town recently, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d check out some of the local establishments and give you guys a virtual sight-tasting tour. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the hotel vending machine.
Hey, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten all day and I had a couple of hours to kill till my family showed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Worry, Be Happy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dont-worry-be-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dont-worry-be-happy/</guid>
      <description>And that would make him the first of our kids to eat a Happy Meal.
Not sure if I like the new mascot. He tried to eat the baby&amp;rsquo;s noony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anniversary Candy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/anniversary-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/anniversary-candy/</guid>
      <description>Aren&amp;rsquo;t I lucky? How many guys get to have a truly one of a kind candy made just for them?
What you are looking at is an out of this world treat that I have dubbed &amp;ldquo;Anniversary Candy&amp;rdquo;. Made by my wife, purely for my own enjoyment.
She made the first batch a few years ago for Christmas, and it&amp;rsquo;s been a special request of mine ever since on celebratory occasions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Toe 2 Toe&#34; Review: Chili Cheese Fries</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2014 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</guid>
      <description>THE CONTENDERS:
Melter&amp;rsquo;s (Irving)
 melty burgers and loaded baked potatoes 14 year old native Dallas establishment 2 locations, downtown Dallas &amp;amp; Irving low key atmosphere with an emphasis on the food  vs.
Burger Fi (Garland)
 upscale burgers and hot dogs Florida chain with scores of locations around the country 50s/60s diner aesthetic thick, home-cut fries and real angus beef  MELTERS
Melters&#39; chili cheese fries were the first and, so far, only thing I&amp;rsquo;ve had off of their menu, but I&amp;rsquo;m already impressed with the place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
