<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dark Hour Haunted House on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/dark-hour-haunted-house/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dark Hour Haunted House on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 17:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/dark-hour-haunted-house/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Hour&#39;s Wreck the Halls</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1695/23471270343_deab39ff5a_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Wreck the Halls — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/23471270343/&#34; title=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2015 was the year I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tobyblog.com/2015/09/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever.html&#34;&gt;Dark Hour Haunted House&lt;/a&gt;, and you probably realize by now what a fan I am. We are very fortunate to live in an area with access to a year round haunt. To be able to be successful at that requires a level of quality and showmanship, frankly, above your average haunt. Not to detract from anyone else in the business (no one can do it all!), but I think it does hold true. In getting to know these guys and the haunt itself a little better over these past few months, it is becoming clear how much of an inspiration they are to other folks in the industry. And I&amp;rsquo;ve still not yet discovered all they have to offer!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</guid>
      <description>I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&#39;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&#39;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&#39;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&#39;t get caught!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Frightmare Weekend</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/texas-frightmare-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/texas-frightmare-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This year I attended Texas Frightmare Weekend for the first time. By now it seems like forever ago. But lucky you — I saved all the pictures! So here they are without much verbal adornment, or it&amp;rsquo;d probably take me another month and a half to get this up.

I suggest you take your time with this post. It&amp;rsquo;s a big one. Really savor the photographs. Left-click to enlarge them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>