<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Halloween on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/halloween/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Halloween on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 23:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/halloween/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nine Useless Jack O&#39; Lantern Templates</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/nine-useless-jack-o-lantern-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/nine-useless-jack-o-lantern-templates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/LWJYaep-0sg&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of these were taken from the huge catalog of templates over at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.stoneykins.com/&#34;&gt;Stoneykins.com&lt;/a&gt;, the vast majority of which are pretty cool and definitely not useless.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Halloween Toy of 2019</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/my-favorite-halloween-toy-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 17:52:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/my-favorite-halloween-toy-ever/</guid>
      <description>🎃📻🧡   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween is Officially On Hold</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-31-halloween-postponed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:34:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-31-halloween-postponed/</guid>
      <description>October, you have been one long, soggy mess. C&amp;rsquo;est la vie, I suppose. To commemorate what I anticipate to be tonight&amp;rsquo;s non-event, I have chosen this song to be the official &amp;ldquo;hold&amp;rdquo; music of Halloween 2018, to be played in a continuous loop until one metaphorically throws up one&amp;rsquo;s hands in disgust, and finally gives up the game. To pick it up again next year? Perhaps. But never quite in the same way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Frank Zappa Halloween Costume</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-25-zappa-halloween-77-costume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 17:25:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-25-zappa-halloween-77-costume/</guid>
      <description>I think I just found my Halloween costume for this year.
How did I ever miss this? It debuted just last year for the 40th anniversary celebration of Frank Zappa&amp;rsquo;s legendary Halloween concert series at The Palladium in New York. Zappa did Halloween concerts throughout the entirety of his career, but the one in 1977 is generally considered to be the apogee of that grand tradition.
To commemorate that series of shows (which ran from October 28-31), the family released a massive box set that includes all six concerts on a USB stick, in 24-bit WAV audio for a flawless sound experience, PLUS a jaw-dropping adult size Frank Zappa costume in vintage 70s plastic style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Halloween &amp; Hauntfest Convention</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-08-halloween-hauntfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:49:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-08-halloween-hauntfest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4339/36452811210_3a1f348349_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017 — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/36452811210/&#34; title=&#34;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



Normally scheduled in late August, the &lt;a href=&#34;http://halloweenandhaunt.com/&#34; title=&#34;The Halloween &amp;amp; Hauntfest Show&#34;&gt;Halloween &amp;amp; Hauntfest show&lt;/a&gt; is appropriately billed as &amp;ldquo;a gateway event to the Halloween season.&amp;rdquo; To those of us who kick off our official celebrations with the start of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dinosaurdracula.com/&#34;&gt;Dinosaur Dracula&amp;rsquo;s Halloween Countdown&lt;/a&gt; on September 1, the timing hits that perfect sweet spot. The anticipation, that period of time I like to call &amp;ldquo;the run-up to the countdown&amp;rdquo;, starts to build throughout August, so that by the time this event rolls around Kassi and the kids and I are practically bursting with Halloween excitement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smells Like Halloween at Yankee Candle</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-09-04-yankee-candle-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 09:41:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-09-04-yankee-candle-halloween/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4422/36040105263_67f5b87dbe_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Window advert&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Window advert — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/36040105263/&#34; title=&#34;Window advert&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s in a smell? The power to evoke. Memories. People. Places. And special times in our lives. Seasons long forgotten. All brought back in an instant the second a particular aroma hits our nostrils. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that scented candles, long thought domain of grandmas and boring little gift shops, have become respected among the nostalgia set in recent years. I read once that people don&amp;rsquo;t remember scents; that you remember the things associated with it or the strong feelings the scent creates, but the brain does not store memory of the scent itself. And now I find myself trying to remember what the woods smell like in autumn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August into December at the Holiday Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/august-into-december-at-the-holiday-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/august-into-december-at-the-holiday-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8449/28674407714_ef688b56a7_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mr. Pumpkin&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Mr. Pumpkin — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/28674407714/&#34; title=&#34;Mr. Pumpkin&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.holidaywarehouse.com/&#34;&gt;Holiday Warehouse&lt;/a&gt; is a largish, and rather outstanding, independent holiday decor shop located in Plano, Texas. Like its well known cousin The &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/&#34;&gt;Decorator&amp;rsquo;s Warehouse&lt;/a&gt; in Arlington, the concentration is mainly on Christmas, but not as exclusively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sfanthor! House of Wax</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/</guid>
      <description>Here in North Texas the sun is shining. The weather is warming up. The world outside is getting brighter. The Texas wildflowers are already in bloom, thanks to a mild and soggy winter. In the woods, things are moving. The itchy season is upon us, and the window of opportunity for a lot of local geocaches is closing, as the casual players tend to steer clear of anything that might put them in the way of tall grass, poison ivy, or the dreaded tick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lights Out For Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>#pic { display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; }   Do you remember Collector&#39;s Crypt? I wrote about that place around this time last year. It&#39;s closed now. I had a dream about it the other night, or rather its next incarnation, which was as a hybrid Christmas/Halloween store. I know the owners have an interest in Christmas things, so that detail is not too surprising. But in my dream, there was also a functional toilet over by the register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pumpkin for St. Michael</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-pumpkin-for-st.-michael/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-pumpkin-for-st.-michael/</guid>
      <description>September 29th is the feast of St. Michael the Archangel, or Michaelmas as it is known in European countries. St. Michael cast the devil out of heaven, and is the commander of the armies of God. He is traditionally shown fighting a dragon, or with his foot on the back of the devil. He is the patron of soldiers and police officers, but also of the ill and suffering. He has appeared to people at various times curing diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</guid>
      <description>I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&#39;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&#39;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&#39;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&#39;t get caught!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — The Great Pumpkin Waltz</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-the-great-pumpkin-waltz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-the-great-pumpkin-waltz/</guid>
      <description>We are officially in the &amp;ldquo;-BER months&amp;rdquo; now, a time of year that for my generation is indelibly stamped by the melancholy Peanuts cartoon soundtracks of Vince Guiraldi and his trio. Though the nostalgic quality of these tracks reaches fever pitch around Christmastime, we begin our seasonal contemplation with this wistful little tune, quickly supplanted in the Guiraldi lineup, but never quite forgotten. It remains one of my favorites, but I&amp;rsquo;ll only listen to it from the start of September through Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Spooks on YouTube: Apparitions</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for something spooky to watch as we wind our way down to Halloween, but find yourself bored by the usual fare of cheesy monster movies or gross slasher flicks? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re in the mood for something a little more thoughtful; a little more substantial, perhaps? Let me show you something interesting.
 Apparitions is a BBC miniseries about a Catholic exorcist who finds himself at the center of a satanic intrigue that reaches to the Vatican and threatens the world itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Decorator&#39;s Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>The Decorator&#39;s Warehouse, located in Arlington, Texas, bills itself as Texas&#39;s largest Christmas store. And it is very large. But what really impresses you upon entering the place is just how jam-packed it is with holiday and seasonal baubles, as if despite its football-field size floor space they still did not have quite enough room to fit everything.&amp;nbsp;
As soon as you walk in the door you&#39;re assaulted with holiday cheer; the entrance is rather elaborately decorated and serves as both a picture station and portal of sorts into this alternate dimension that feels something like Santa&#39;s attic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aisles &amp; Aisles of Halloween at At Home </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/aisles-aisles-of-halloween-at-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/aisles-aisles-of-halloween-at-at-home/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re just under 100 days to Halloween now, but there are certain places you can always depend on to roll out the spooky stock a little early. I covered At Home last year and this year&#39;s selection looks bigger and better than ever. For 2015 our local store has literally doubled the floor space devoted to Halloween goods. And, well, just take a look for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Frightmare Weekend</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/texas-frightmare-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/texas-frightmare-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This year I attended Texas Frightmare Weekend for the first time. By now it seems like forever ago. But lucky you — I saved all the pictures! So here they are without much verbal adornment, or it&#39;d probably take me another month and a half to get this up.

I suggest you take your time with this post. It&#39;s a big one. Really savor the photographs. Left-click to enlarge them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screening Phantasm With The Tall Man</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150610-screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20150610-screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-wTzO_bNWPPc/VWmzIHjOooI/AAAAAAAACAY/xoBh6Qosgpg/s1600/IMG_2740.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From a respectful write-up on Texas Frightmare Weekend by &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dreadcentral.com/news/101193/event-report-texas-frightmare-weekend-2015/&#34;&gt;Dread Central&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can we stop calling Texas Frightmare Weekend a “regional con” now? The first reader I met this year was Aaron from Australia, who had flown all the way here to experience TFW as his &lt;em&gt;FIRST&lt;/em&gt; con.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit to Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20150410-a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20150410-a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Channard from Hellraiser II, in all his glory
  Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt is a boutique shop in Dallas specializing in horror and sci-fi collectibles, memorabilia, paraphernalia, and… well, you just gotta see it, folks. It&amp;rsquo;s an amazing place. I discovered them only recently after attending the St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Slay Weekend event at Dark Hour Haunted House in Plano. They were a sponsor of that particular show, so Dark Hour graciously gave them some floor space to sell a few wares after the show and otherwise promote the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Very First Tobyblog Giveaway!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20141203-announcing-the-very-first-tobyblog-giveaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20141203-announcing-the-very-first-tobyblog-giveaway/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-dES21Y3gXxw/VHjUpreAJVI/AAAAAAAABnY/qgv9Zf_dOYY/s1600/DSC02792.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would you like to win this original 8 x 10 photograph that hung in our house this past Halloween?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tobyblog Halloween Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-halloween-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-halloween-special/</guid>
      <description>I love Halloween. You do, too. This video is a tribute to that season, to every memory and every thrill. To cold autumn nights. To the warm glow of jack o&#39; lanterns. To spooky stories and cozy evenings. To every bit of magic and adventure in our lives.
This is the story of Halloween 2013 as we experienced it; what has gone down in our lives and memories as THE BEST HALLOWEEN EVER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Iconography of Halloween: Skeletons</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140930-the-iconography-of-halloween-skeletons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140930-the-iconography-of-halloween-skeletons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-63LpKquAqBg/VCuQQPTZnnI/AAAAAAAABcg/QNzcV0lck1M/s1600/tumblr_inline_ncqnlhYHgi1rzwpy9.gif&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Dias De Los Muertos at World Market</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140927-los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140927-los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-jxBynb6fbbQ/VCa81QdRisI/AAAAAAAABYE/oDRuHs5PaBQ/s1600/DSC02222.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Star of Phantasm</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140919-the-real-star-of-phantasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 22:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140919-the-real-star-of-phantasm/</guid>
      <description>Here you go, folks, the real star of Phantasm — that bad-ass muscle car! A real thing of beauty, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even that much of a car guy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Halloween Village at Michaels</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140823-incredible-halloween-village-at-michaels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140823-incredible-halloween-village-at-michaels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-9EU7kxb09Y0/U_YwFMV_fLI/AAAAAAAAA6Q/EEIYtDJvZ4s/s1600/IMG_1667.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween at Big Lots</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140807-halloween-at-big-lots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140807-halloween-at-big-lots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-T4PPeI9JIWg/U-Kfhb6-DlI/AAAAAAAAAxs/AFXIe1xozHg/s640/blogger-image-1422700385.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yankee Candle Halloween Preview</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140803-yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140803-yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-6FJ3nuF1Rq0/U96JVc7d8MI/AAAAAAAAAvw/1XjHAlNOflA/s1600/IMG_1603.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Halloween Store Opening Soon</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140802-spirit-halloween-store-opening-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140802-spirit-halloween-store-opening-soon/</guid>
      <description>Took a little stroll through the neighborhood this morning, and what should we find?
Come September, tune in to Tobyblog for further details!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit To The Toy Store</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140801-a-visit-to-the-toy-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140801-a-visit-to-the-toy-store/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-i7RaY44btHc/U9rGOaPi9sI/AAAAAAAAAtE/RLcy-43mYYw/s1600/IMG_1200.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Has Arrived at At Home</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140726-halloween-has-arrived-at-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/photos/20140726-halloween-has-arrived-at-at-home/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-_gwhccKqpqY/U9SAkCQ1olI/AAAAAAAAAlA/cJhMhsf1OfE/s1600/IMG_1422.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Halloween Merch of the Year</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140712-first-halloween-merch-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 06:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140712-first-halloween-merch-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Technically spotted on July 1 at Michaels. Thanks to Swagger Mom for the tip-off about fall going up this week. That made me wonder, and my suspicions checked out.
And yeah, it was mostly generic fall decorations on a couple of shelves, but over on the other side of the store, on a lonely end cap display, there was this:
Unmistakable. Halloween ribbon.
Frankensteins, witches, spiders, skeletons… Have you ever stopped to think how rich Halloween is in iconography?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
