<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>summer on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/summer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in summer on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 09:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bahama Bucks</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bahama-bucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bahama-bucks/</guid>
      <description>Katie and the gang over at Cheap Thrills invited me and the kids to do a co-review highlighting some of our favorite summer treats. You can check out their submission, Culver&amp;rsquo;s Frozen Custard, below.
  Naturally, I jumped at the chance to introduce you guys to one of the hidden treasures of our little neighborhood — Bahama Bucks!
Bucks is sort of like Jimmy Buffett&amp;rsquo;s own sno-cone stand. It serves sno-cones and tropical smoothies, some coffee drinks, and you can even get mixed fruit cups there if you&amp;rsquo;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is Coming</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/summer-is-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/summer-is-coming/</guid>
      <description>In fact, it&#39;s already here. My woodland trekking has been sidelined a bit due to having to nurse a sumac rash, but I&#39;ll be back soon enough. Here&#39;s hoping you guys get out and sweat a bit this summer. Enjoy the late evenings while you can! DST. What a gift from Mr. Nixon! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taki&#39;s, Cane Sugar Soda Pops</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</guid>
      <description>This is an older review from TheVCubeSolver and I very much inspired by the hijinks of Brian Hammons and the gang over at Review the World. In it we take a look at a couple of different varieties of Taki&amp;rsquo;s chips and some cane sugar soda pops we picked up at the local coffee shop.
Oh, and you&amp;rsquo;ll notice I&amp;rsquo;m calling myself &amp;ldquo;Meeks, the Pedestrian&amp;rdquo;. Cause we were trying to have code names or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</guid>
      <description>Back in the summer of 2013 TheVCubeSolver and I dropped by the local candy shop to review Blue Bunny&amp;rsquo;s Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes, a push-pop like product in three weird flavors. It turned out to be a complete and total sensory experience.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>