<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 23:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nine Useless Jack O&#39; Lantern Templates</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/nine-useless-jack-o-lantern-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/nine-useless-jack-o-lantern-templates/</guid>
      <description>Most of these were taken from the huge catalog of templates over at Stoneykins.com, the vast majority of which are pretty cool and definitely not useless.
#9. Joker Joaquin Phoenix Already looks like you messed it up. Badly.
#8. Boo-Tay Why.
#7. Frank Sinatra Stein No.
#6. Two Youts Nothing says classic Halloween nostalgia like My Cousin Vinny.
5. Kim Jong Un Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;Rocket Man&amp;rdquo; be more appropriate for the 4th of July?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Album for September</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/an-album-for-september/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/an-album-for-september/</guid>
      <description>Doing chores, having a 🥃 while I listen to Frank’s album about growing old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Halloween Toy of 2019</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/my-favorite-halloween-toy-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 17:52:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/my-favorite-halloween-toy-ever/</guid>
      <description>🎃📻🧡   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Is a Many Splendored Thing</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/love-is-a-many-splendored-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 12:49:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/love-is-a-many-splendored-thing/</guid>
      <description>One of my earliest memories is asking my mom to borrow an old Hallmark music box that played this song. It was important to me, though I couldn&amp;rsquo;t explain why. I&amp;rsquo;d listen to it over and over again, long past the point of annoyance to everyone. Sometimes at night, when I was scared, I&amp;rsquo;d listen to it to help me sleep. It has a sad, but sweet melody. At about 2:00 it has the proper timing, then very quickly starts to unwind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faces</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 15:33:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/faces/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/48578600051_4fc9c2cd49_b.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time does take its toll on the body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you see when you look into a funhouse mirror? Another &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; staring out at you beneath the surface of the glass? &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maybe&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; you are really just one of a whole army of such &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo;s, none knowing for sure what side of the glass he falls on. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Maybe&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; the &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; you are now is just another picture frozen in time; something separate and distinct from all your past and future selves. Always dying, always being born; every thought and action carving its mark forever into the lines of your face and body.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now imagine an app on your phone that would let you peer into that funhouse — would let you see those possibilities, those infinite &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo;s that could have been. That &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; be?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, particularly those possibilities that involve you growing a beard, dying your hair, looking like a douchebag, or getting really old.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crow at the Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/grand-canyon-crow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 17:32:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/grand-canyon-crow/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s ready for fall?
You can count me in, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure &amp;ldquo;ready&amp;rdquo; is the best word for it. Summer seemed to pass by so fast this year. Barely had time to really enjoy it, it seems, before it&amp;rsquo;s practically gone. They say this happens as you get older, but I suspect in my case it has more to do with a dearth of time spent outside this year, soaking up sun and heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working From Malls</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/working-from-malls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 11:11:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/working-from-malls/</guid>
      <description>I love working from shopping malls. I was just telling Kassi the other day that they offer several advantages that suit me and my work style well. Doors open early. Easy access to restrooms. Most have at least some access to power; and free wifi, though I always tether. The ambient noise is generally at an appropriate level, though my current environment has somewhat more than the usual. More than anything I appreciate the large, wide open spaces and natural light that filters in through the ceiling glass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A History of the Puffy Toilet Seat</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/puffy-toilet-seats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 11:16:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/puffy-toilet-seats/</guid>
      <description>I always considered those things the grossest of the gross. But did get me thinking about alternative &amp;ldquo;comfortable&amp;rdquo; materials. A gel toilet seat? Cushion of air? Water? Yeah, like a water bed — but instead it&amp;rsquo;s a toilet seat.
And if you don&amp;rsquo;t already follow the bro-science blog of Dollar Shave Club, you should. Way better than The Onion these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RIP Frank Dog, 2013 – 2019</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/rip-frank-dog-2013-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 12:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/rip-frank-dog-2013-2019/</guid>
      <description>I’m sorry, Frank. Despite driving us crazy sometimes, you were ever a good friend and protector. I know it wasn’t you’re fault. I hope somehow you understood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 09.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Arrived in beautiful Telluride, Colorado, and yes, this is my first update since day #2 of vacation. So much for my Travel Log. Between lack of cell signal and surrendering my phone to the kid, and straight up being too busy and/or exhausted, I haven’t had much opportunity for posting.
We’ve been busy!
Back to the Grand Canyon this year, and this time we got to spend a night in the park, with a chance to do some dawn/dusk shots of the canyon itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s Your Smell?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/what-s-your-smell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/what-s-your-smell/</guid>
      <description>I wonder what coffee, grass, and new computer would smell like?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 02.02</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Finally made it to Red Rock State Park, and made a couple of new discoveries along the way. Our route took us through what turned out be the incredibly beautiful Coconino National Forest, a place we have vowed to return. If Tolkien’s Elves were a real thing, they might just choose to live in a place like that. Verdant green forests around the bases of giant granite mountains, interspersed all along the way with little villages and expensive looking cabin retreats, with lights hanging from the trees across bridges that span crystal clear mountain streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 02.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-02-01/</guid>
      <description>On the road from Albuquerque to Flagstaff, near which we turn south to Red Rock State Park in Arizona. The kids are keen to get in a hike today, the first “real” day of our vacation, as far as I’m concerned. It’s been fun watching the younger two get excited over taking pictures from the car with the little Instax Mini. That was Kassi’s great idea. We bought Anthony around 150 exposures and his eyes got wide when I told him I wanted him to use every single one by the end of the trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 01.02</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Picture of me in the Llano Estacado, Texas’s “wine country”. On the road for quite a while and still not out of the state. Holding up well. Fear the little one may be coming down with a cold. Hope he’s better after some rest.
Changed restaurant plans and will revisit our old favorite in Albuquerque for the third year in a row.
The food there has always been great, though the service is consistently slow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 01.01</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/road-trip-travel-log-01-01/</guid>
      <description>We’re well in to the big family road trip of 2019, and the obligatory Texas pit stop at Bucc-ees has been checked off the list. Would have sent you guys a pic from the storied Bucc-ees bathrooms, but I was too excited about these new hot n’ spicy Beaver Nuggets! You can hear all about my first experience with those glorified Corn Pops in this review I did last year with my good buddy Brian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Flushing Drugs Could Create “Meth-Gators”</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cops-flushing-drugs-could-create-meth-gators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cops-flushing-drugs-could-create-meth-gators/</guid>
      <description>The Alabama Meth-Gators is my new favorite college football team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sounds From a Mall</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-10-my-lunch-at-northpark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 12:32:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-10-my-lunch-at-northpark/</guid>
      <description>The second installment in my ongoing series of ambient environmental sound recordings. These are the sounds of me packing up my recorder and walking to the food court, where I order a bowl from Chipotle. I take my bowl outside to the patio to enjoy the fresh air and sunshine, after which I take a little walk around the mall to pick up some interesting sounds. And for the second time in a row I ran across a guy playing a piano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fire Sign</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-fire-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 12:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-fire-sign/</guid>
      <description>The name of this sculpture is Entwine, I think a reference to The Lord of the Rings. It’s supposed to be a tree, or plant, to symbolize Wylie’s connection to its roots. I always thought of it as a campfire, and I think that imagery fits much better for a library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bits and Bobs</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-10-bits-and-bobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 17:33:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-10-bits-and-bobs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1562790874/img/IMG_3630.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made a promise to myself that I would never waste time on this blog apologizing for sporadic posting. So instead of doing that, I think I&amp;rsquo;ll do that other thing where I throw a few pictures at you and catch you up on recent developments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show Some Love To My Spouseblog</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-08-kassiblog-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 17:41:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-07-08-kassiblog-update/</guid>
      <description>If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been following Kassi over on her personal blog, by all means go there and check it out. She&amp;rsquo;s been killing it lately, posting about all the family stuff I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to be getting to over on this site, but have been too lame to do. I swear she can fire off 3 or 4 posts by the time I&amp;rsquo;m done editing the same number of photos. Practice, I guess?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Independence Day 2019</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/independence-day-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/independence-day-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1562256320/img/09474C58-625F-4B47-88CF-4798FDAEB69B.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s no denying we live in troubled times in this country. Shared celebrations are a respite from the hate that seems set to smother our culture. They also serve as milestones, reminding us of the passage of time and providing a useful historical perspective on our own lives and the times we share with each other. For our part, we plan to celebrate like we haven’t in a while, venturing down to the mall later for the big party, then fireworks later tonight. Before that I’ll be grilling pizzas in the backyard, and I hope to get a lot of today on camera.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Odds and Ends</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/journal-for-june-24-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 16:55:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/journal-for-june-24-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1561413959/img/kelsey.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s just say today feels more like Kelsey Grammer than Jason Momoa.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guess Who&#39;s Coming to Dallas?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/bird-and-the-bee-at-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 21:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/bird-and-the-bee-at-trees/</guid>
      <description>Well, well. And I thought they&amp;rsquo;d retired. I suppose there are still a few living acts I&amp;rsquo;d pay to see after all. 🐦🐝 No idea whether we&amp;rsquo;ll make it out to this one, but might bee nice.
Read all about my love for their Hall and Oates cover album. And give those songs a deep listen.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Thing?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lax-sound-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 16:54:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lax-sound-tour/</guid>
      <description>I decided to do something today I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to do for quite a while. I&amp;rsquo;m bringing back what they used to call in the early days of podcasting &amp;ldquo;soundseeing tours&amp;rdquo;, wherein people just recorded the ambient sounds of interesting places they visited or things they were doing. Not much time to do a writeup on this, as I&amp;rsquo;m about to board my flight, but here you can join me on my customary walk from Tom Bradley International terminal across the length and breadth of the airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maggie May </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/maggie-may/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 22:50:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/maggie-may/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hogs Head Cheese: A Disappearing Delicacy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/hogs-head-cheese/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 09:28:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/hogs-head-cheese/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t claim that I was one who helped to postpone the extinction. Somebody told me once as a kid that it contained pig&amp;rsquo;s brains, so I never ate it. It pretty much looked like jello&amp;rsquo;d meat, too, which didn&amp;rsquo;t add to the appeal. I&amp;rsquo;d try it today, though, if I still lived there, and probably would like it. Vinegar and pork is not a bad combo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Ants Like Coffee?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/ants-harvest-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 09:55:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/ants-harvest-coffee/</guid>
      <description>🐜❤️☕️
Ants are my favorite insect. That they have actually been observed to plant coffee seeds, live in and among the plants they grow, and actually harvest the beans floors me with wonder for these remarkable creatures that are so different from us, yet so much resemble us in our social behaviors. This is real agriculture; and we already know they practice ranching and husbandry behaviors, with aphids for example — &amp;ldquo;milking&amp;rdquo; them of the dew produced by their bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richardson&#39;s Cottonwood Art Festival</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cottonwood-art-fest-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cottonwood-art-fest-2019/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/40876956893_f61f62e832_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/40876956893/&#34; title=&#34;The Extraordinary Paintings of Alla Tsank&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Somewhere around the beginning of May (and again in the fall) the city of Richardson, Texas invites artists from across the country to gather in Cottonwood Park for a big market day celebration of beauty and imagination. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cottonwoodartfestival.com&#34;&gt;The Cottonwood Art Festival&lt;/a&gt; features some brilliant and rigorously curated talent, and is described by the artists themselves as one of the best art shows in the country. This year we decided to pay a visit as a family. And although the younger two would crap out early from the mild heat and post-rainy day humidity, we did manage to hang around just long enough for me to discover my new favorite artist, Alla Tsank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More on her later.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detective Pikachu Was As Good As It Could Be</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/detective-pikachu-was-as-good-as-it-could-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/detective-pikachu-was-as-good-as-it-could-be/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1557888093/img/5F86E6CC-37E8-4256-BC38-E41AFDFCE5A8.gif&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other news, I saw Detective Pikachu with the family a few days ago, and I think we all left impressed. Some strong acting and genuinely funny moments. Pikachu singing the Pokémon cartoon theme song was a highlight for me. But does Ryan Reynolds have to be in literally every movie now? That being said, he did a wonderful job. A really enjoyable and charming movie. Go see it. With your kids, of course.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Albert</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/uncle-albert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/uncle-albert/</guid>
      <description>Currently enjoying at maximum volume.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kassi Blogs, Too</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/kassiblog-too/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:46:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/kassiblog-too/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My wife Kassi recently started her own blog of a more private nature, and she&amp;rsquo;s written a wonderful article about all of the many things going on in our lives last week, including our baptism, preparation for Pascha, and the appearance of the first clusters of firewheels in Dallas. Take a look.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dream Log: A New House</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dreamlog-a-new-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:14:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dreamlog-a-new-house/</guid>
      <description>I woke up from a vivid dream this morning. I&amp;rsquo;d just arrived home from a business trip to California, and Kassi was very excited to show me the changes that had been made to our neighborhood in my absence. Everyone had gotten a new house, it seems, and the neighborhood itself had been newly laid out, and its boundaries expanded. Our house had been moved to the backside of the neighborhood by the creek, and the wooded area around the creek had been developed, so that our house, instead of looking out onto a wooded ravine as it would currently, was now at a &amp;ldquo;T&amp;rdquo; intersection in the middle of the larger neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got the Munchies? Try Hypnotic Donuts.</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/hypnotic-donuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 18:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/hypnotic-donuts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1558136445/img/36C549F3-4677-426F-8ECB-3E7C87F986F1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was a rainy, Seattle-y Saturday morning in Dallas when I decided to take the kids out for a Daddy-Daughter-Baby Day run to Hypnotic Donuts, one of those fancy donut places that seem to be popping up around town these days like vape shops were five about years ago. They&amp;rsquo;d been asking me to take them on a Pokémon hunt, and I decided I&amp;rsquo;d treat them to breakfast as a bonus and incentive for getting up extra early.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An All New 👨🏻‍💻 Tobybase.com</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tobybase-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 16:18:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tobybase-update/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a site overhaul for my pro blog, Tobybase.com. Go check it out and tell me what you think! Now just need some new content…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Dangers of AI</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/when-ai-throws-shade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 15:50:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/when-ai-throws-shade/</guid>
      <description>What exactly are you trying to tell me, Facebook?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Resurrection of Archie Bunker</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/all-in-the-family-live-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 09:01:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/all-in-the-family-live-event/</guid>
      <description>You would think that in this &amp;ldquo;woke&amp;rdquo; era the comedies of Norman Lear would be better appreciated, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think his many efforts to reboot his old series are going anywhere. Not because of any politically touchy subject matter, but because he saw the humanity in all of his characters, including those like Archie Bunker who he used to illustrate everything he saw as wrong with modern American attitudes, but whom he based on his own beloved father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three New Pasadena Restaurants </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/three-new-pasadena-restaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/three-new-pasadena-restaurants/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1555717674/img/ABB60CD5-A457-4710-A103-8E22A15D25DC.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have decided that when presented with a choice between the familiar and the new, I am going to lean in favor of new experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>45</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/45/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/45/</guid>
      <description>Today I had a lot of reminders that there are people out there who love and care for me a great deal. My wife, parents, and children. My brothers, cousins, and family. Friends old and new. I am thankful for all of them. I am thankful for the things I have, inside and out. I am thankful for the places God has brought me to in the past year.
I met a man on the street named Emery Lambus who asked me for a couple of bucks to buy lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasadena in Bloom</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/pasadena-in-bloom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/pasadena-in-bloom/</guid>
      <description>The streets of Old Town Pasadena are lined this April in pink and purple blooms. A little natural spring beauty. Something of a birthday treat from God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roof Access</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/roof-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/roof-access/</guid>
      <description>I get irrationally excited when I see ROOF ACCESS. But it’s never actually accessible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helvetica Now</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/helvetica-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/helvetica-now/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;Helvetica Now is the tummy-tuck, facelift and lip filler we’ve been wanting, but were too afraid to ask for,” said Abbott Miller
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🎧 Soulshine</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/jukebox-franti-soulshine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 11:11:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/jukebox-franti-soulshine/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t you need it?
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring buds</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/spring-buds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/spring-buds/</guid>
      <description>All winter keep still.
Naked, silent. Dream until
spring ends cold’s vigil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flip Wilson</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/flip-wilson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/flip-wilson/</guid>
      <description>Today I passed up the opportunity to buy a vintage talking Flip Wilson doll that would tell me not to touch him inappropriately. #70s #beforenintendo</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time To Start It Up Again</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/time-to-start-it-up-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/time-to-start-it-up-again/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been too long out of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>300 Million Butterflies Coming To Texas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/300-million-butterflies-coming-to-texas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/300-million-butterflies-coming-to-texas/</guid>
      <description>Well, what do you know. It looks like the Monarchs have come back to life. I shall be ready. 📸</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cappuccino in the Morning </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cappuccino-in-the-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cappuccino-in-the-morning/</guid>
      <description>A cappuccino is a wonderful way to start the morning. Though this morning I can say I’ve had better. There was a guy here who had one of those ironic mustaches. He could make good coffee. I wonder where he went. And if he still has that mustache. And if he left, maybe, to startup some better place that specializes in morning cappuccinos? And where that place might be, and if they have WiFi?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who You Really Are</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/elder-joseph/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 12:02:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/elder-joseph/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/SDn_BXyCvLk&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Patrick’s Favorite Drink</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/st-patrick-s-favorite-drink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/st-patrick-s-favorite-drink/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating St. Patrick’s Day with a couple of Vodka Stingers. Kassi approves. 🍀</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selfie from Cali</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/selfie-from-cali/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/selfie-from-cali/</guid>
      <description>That’s a wrap for this trip. It’s been fun trying a new hotel and exploring a different part of the city. Perhaps next time I’ll try to take in more of the cultural life. There’s always something going on in Pasadena.
Now home again to Texas and the people I love. See you soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Libre</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-libre/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-libre/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1552629476/img/576933C9-5E92-4C23-B1AF-8B342EF82BDF.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The weather was warmer today. I could feel spring in my bones. I get that way around this time of year. Maybe I was feeling a little homesick. Whatever the case, I&amp;rsquo;ve been craving Mexican food. I noticed this little while walking around during my lunch break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I was standing outside the door reading the posted menuboard, an older lady passing by said to me &amp;ldquo;Go in. You&amp;rsquo;ll like it. It&amp;rsquo;s really good.&amp;rdquo; I took that as a sign.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Set of Antique Glasses</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-set-of-antique-glasses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-set-of-antique-glasses/</guid>
      <description>I always check out the glassware in antique shops. The Greek theme doesn&amp;rsquo;t really suit me, but I thought the ornate styling was good for a pic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Times at the El Portal</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/el-portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/el-portal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1552625591/img/761E75E1-8A2E-4D98-9348-5951E7436215.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took a detour that night after my trip to the antique store. I passed along back streets, out of the way plazas, anywhere that looked like it might afford me new scenery. I stumbled across El Portal behind the headquarters of the Planetary Society, its aromas drawing my attention before I&amp;rsquo;d even rounded the corner to lay site on the place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Horn Player</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/horn-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/horn-player/</guid>
      <description>A street musician doing his thing in Old Town Pasadena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Simple But Powerful Prayer </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-simple-but-powerful-prayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-simple-but-powerful-prayer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/ccAaMhSW_PY&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Methodist Church</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/old-methodist-church/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/old-methodist-church/</guid>
      <description>The interesting things you run across when you decide to walk the mile and a half back to the hotel instead of Uber-ing. This is an old Methodist Church in the Playhouse District of Pasadena. Almost looks like an entrance to another world. A secret garden. A little foreboding perhaps.
There was a lot about this area I’d like to explore. I’ll be back again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Play Poison</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/let-s-play-poison/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/let-s-play-poison/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s someone buried under there. That&amp;rsquo;s the name. And see the date? Poison! Get off!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For the Lightly Bosomed Woman</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/for-the-lightly-bosomed-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/for-the-lightly-bosomed-woman/</guid>
      <description>I see what you did there, Flattery. And for the moderately bosomed woman? Out of luck, I suppose… 👙</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tombstone Ideas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tombstone-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tombstone-ideas/</guid>
      <description>What I want my tombstone to look like, except with Firewheels and dandelions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jean — Rod McKuen</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-10-jean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 23:31:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-10-jean/</guid>
      <description>Listening.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rise and Shine</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/rise-and-shine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/rise-and-shine/</guid>
      <description>Rise and shine, people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brown Noise Tracks for Intense Focus</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-08-brown-noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:31:10 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-08-brown-noise/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Over the last couple of weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve had the need to maintain a greater focus in my work and study. I find brown noise to be good way of filtering out distractions, to allow the mind to concentrate on a task. Brown noise tends to sit at a lower frequency than white noise, so the sound is deeper and more meditative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some tracks that I like. Use headphones to get the most out of these.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/SHM-ympOZo0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Very low, like a muffled waterfall from a distance. Very good track.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Spring!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/happy-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/happy-spring/</guid>
      <description>Happy springtime to all you players out there. The weather’s warming up here in Texas. We’re coming out of winter. I think we’re through the worst of it. Are you looking for signs of new growth? Look to the trees! They’re always the first to show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ash Wednesday, Great Lent</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-06-ash-wednesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 23:28:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-06-ash-wednesday/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7851/40345372543_3e0f96a5b4_b.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Theotokos Icon&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Theotokos Icon — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/40345372543/&#34; title=&#34;Theotokos Icon&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Today is Ash Wednesday, the Catholic holy day that begins the penitential season of Lent. This year I will not be celebrating as a Catholic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year on September 1st Kassi and I, after a long season of spiritual apathy and suffering, took our first steps into the Russian Orthodox Church. There were private reasons, of course. Personal reasons that are always at the core of any conversion; but also open reasons. We did not take the step lightly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tonight You Belong To Me</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-05-the-jerk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 23:39:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-05-the-jerk/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had this song stuck in my head for a couple of days, and maybe if I post it I can get rid of it. It&amp;rsquo;s from The Jerk, and features Bernadette Peters, my first screen crush when I was just a little kid. That bit at the end where she pulls out the coronet still cracks me up. Still, it&amp;rsquo;s a touching scene, don&amp;rsquo;t you think? A little reminder that life can be sweet sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infexxion-34</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-04-infexxion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 23:29:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-03-04-infexxion/</guid>
      <description>Infexxion is an iPhone game based on the old arcade game Attax. My cousin Carl introduced me to it. There was a cabinet in the lobby of a (surely long-since demolished?) movie theater in what is now a rough part of Lafayette, Louisiana. I forget what we were seeing that night. He played — I didn&amp;rsquo;t, as I recall. It had a weird, edgy kind of quality to it, like an Exidy game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Love, She Weeps At Many Things</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-09-28-robot-mice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 01:41:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-09-28-robot-mice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7896/46298054945_02b92269c8_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Nightstand&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Nightstand — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/46298054945/&#34; title=&#34;Nightstand&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;My love, she weeps at many things,&lt;br&gt;
I would not for the world stop up her tears;&lt;br&gt;
She came in many years of drought&lt;br&gt;
And taught me just how right was private rain&lt;br&gt;
To touch the dust with smallest storm &lt;br&gt;
With emerald droppings from her eyes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current Mood 🌛</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-02-24-estate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2019 22:43:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-02-24-estate/</guid>
      <description>Go ahead. Pour a glass of whiskey 🥃 and enjoy this with me, won&amp;rsquo;t you? Forget about everything you have coming up this week. All that stuff. It&amp;rsquo;ll wait.
Right now just listen for moment.
Listen with me. Dim those lights. Turn up the music for a while. Just be.
Just close your eyes and listen. Don&amp;rsquo;t think too much about it. When&amp;rsquo;s the last time you were ever this…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What the Hell is This Poster For the Sonic the Hedgehog Movie?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-22-sonic-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 22:27:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-22-sonic-movie/</guid>
      <description>The Sonic the Hedgehog movie comes out this year.
Are you hyped, nostalgia boys?!
Because if you look at this poster and get hyped, I&amp;rsquo;m calling the cops. Seriously, who designed this freakish movie poster and why is he/she not in jail/hell?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#39;t Get Over This Cover Album</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-20-bird-and-the-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 23:07:28 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-20-bird-and-the-bee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I discovered the The Bird and Bee this past December when I heard their rendition of &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-12-21-my-favorite-christmas-songs/&#34;&gt;The Twelve Days of Christmas&lt;/a&gt; at a bar in Honolulu. That led me to this album, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been burning it up lately on drives and at work.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/V7rExwCkRYI&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s total ear candy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Out West Again</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-19-working-in-pasadena/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 23:42:48 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-19-working-in-pasadena/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm8.staticflickr.com/7804/46429733404_b4819b49bc_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Twilight Over Pasadena&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Twilight Over Pasadena — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/46429733404/&#34; title=&#34;Twilight Over Pasadena&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What should I say? What can I say? Perhaps a little about where I find myself these days. What I&amp;rsquo;m up to. Best keep it brief. I want to encourage myself to update these pages a little more frequently this year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Choice</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-18-everything-ends/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 23:11:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-18-everything-ends/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/img/IMG_1698.JPG&#34; alt=&#34;Mymy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Michael&#39;s Jazz Noir Album</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-01-03-you-have-been-loved/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-01-03-you-have-been-loved/</guid>
      <description>A pop take on jazz noir from his best album. Many years ago Kass and I listened to this cassette so much we broke the tape.
I hope you all are having a mellow moment, whenever it is for you. I know I am.
I find jazz noir goes best with whiskey.
🥃</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to 2019</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-01-02-jazz-noir/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 15:33:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-01-02-jazz-noir/</guid>
      <description>Some sounds for dark days, and nights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few of My Favorite Christmas Songs</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-12-21-my-favorite-christmas-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:44:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-12-21-my-favorite-christmas-songs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/S6wDzvibd_Q&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Hands down my favorite Christmas song of 2018. I passed up this album in favor of Jackie Gleason&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Tis The Season&lt;/em&gt;, a purchase I do not regret, but this song is definitely worth the price of the vinyl. I love it when Frank sings melancholy, and this one has that quality in spades. Nostalgia, regret, and loneliness are all wrapped up in that golden bow of his amazing voice, a voice that forces your ears to attention when you hear it, never aging, never dulling, calling your life before your eyes, and all but materializing that glass of whiskey or scotch in your left hand, as your right hand reaches to pull the brim of your fedora down a little more to cover the tears in your eyes. Merry Christmas!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween is Officially On Hold</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-31-halloween-postponed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:34:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-31-halloween-postponed/</guid>
      <description>October, you have been one long, soggy mess. C&amp;rsquo;est la vie, I suppose. To commemorate what I anticipate to be tonight&amp;rsquo;s non-event, I have chosen this song to be the official &amp;ldquo;hold&amp;rdquo; music of Halloween 2018, to be played in a continuous loop until one metaphorically throws up one&amp;rsquo;s hands in disgust, and finally gives up the game. To pick it up again next year? Perhaps. But never quite in the same way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Vermeule to Newman</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-26-from-vermeule-to-newman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 00:38:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-26-from-vermeule-to-newman/</guid>
      <description>Even if Francis is a liberal, it is far from clear to us that the proper response is liberalism. This, then, is the crux of the problem. Barring the Head of the Church returning, there will be other popes. Perhaps some will be, in the words of the great Louisiana philosopher and theologian I.J. Reilly, good authoritarian popes. Perhaps some will be liberals. However, the anti-liberal position works as well with a good authoritarian pope as it does with a liberal pope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Long, San Francisco</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-26-so-long-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2018 00:24:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-26-so-long-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>A song to fit a very particular mood. It&amp;rsquo;s been a significant week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revelation 17</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-24-the-whore-of-babylon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 01:26:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-24-the-whore-of-babylon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/da/Burgkmair_whore_babylon_color.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;a-meditation-on-a-figure-of-the-last-days&#34;&gt;A meditation on a figure of the last days.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;📖  Revelation 17, KJV&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there came one of the seven angels which had the seven vials, and talked with me, saying unto me, Come hither; I will shew unto thee the judgment of the great whore that sitteth upon many waters: with whom the kings of the earth have committed fornication, and the inhabitants of the earth have been made drunk with the wine of her fornication.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Once Upon a Time, Frank Sinatra</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-17-frank-sinatra-once-upon-a-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 16:17:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-10-17-frank-sinatra-once-upon-a-time/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Return of the Super Meganerd Fun Pack</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-27-super-meganerd-fun-pack-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-27-super-meganerd-fun-pack-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm1.staticflickr.com/890/41456059161_9dd099eb32_k.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Super Mega Nerd Fun Pack 2&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;The Super Mega Nerd Fun Pack 2 — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/41456059161/&#34; title=&#34;The Super Mega Nerd Fun Pack 2&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


Could this be the start of a grand birthday tradition? Watch me unbox the second giant care package gifted to me by my cousin, friend, and frequent collaborator — &lt;em&gt;Carl!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Frank Zappa Halloween Costume</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-25-zappa-halloween-77-costume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 17:25:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-25-zappa-halloween-77-costume/</guid>
      <description>I think I just found my Halloween costume for this year.
How did I ever miss this? It debuted just last year for the 40th anniversary celebration of Frank Zappa&amp;rsquo;s legendary Halloween concert series at The Palladium in New York. Zappa did Halloween concerts throughout the entirety of his career, but the one in 1977 is generally considered to be the apogee of that grand tradition.
To commemorate that series of shows (which ran from October 28-31), the family released a massive box set that includes all six concerts on a USB stick, in 24-bit WAV audio for a flawless sound experience, PLUS a jaw-dropping adult size Frank Zappa costume in vintage 70s plastic style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Halloween &amp; Hauntfest Convention</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-08-halloween-hauntfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:49:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-08-halloween-hauntfest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4339/36452811210_3a1f348349_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017 — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/36452811210/&#34; title=&#34;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


Normally scheduled in late August, the &lt;a href=&#34;http://halloweenandhaunt.com/&#34; title=&#34;The Halloween &amp;amp; Hauntfest Show&#34;&gt;Halloween &amp;amp; Hauntfest show&lt;/a&gt; is appropriately billed as &amp;ldquo;a gateway event to the Halloween season.&amp;rdquo; To those of us who kick off our official celebrations with the start of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dinosaurdracula.com/&#34;&gt;Dinosaur Dracula&amp;rsquo;s Halloween Countdown&lt;/a&gt; on September 1, the timing hits that perfect sweet spot. The anticipation, that period of time I like to call &amp;ldquo;the run-up to the countdown&amp;rdquo;, starts to build throughout August, so that by the time this event rolls around Kassi and the kids and I are practically bursting with Halloween excitement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When did people first start mowing lawns?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-08-history-of-mowing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 14:16:37 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-04-08-history-of-mowing/</guid>
      <description>Today I mowed the back yard for the first time this spring. I am behind. The weather and other duties had kept me off task. The grass was high, and each square foot I tread into submission was like a territory reclaimed for civilization.
I asked myself when people started doing this whole thing. Exactly how old is the time honored American activity of mowing the lawn? And why is this mundane chore, as therapeutic and contemplative as it is, not shown more love by those in the Big Nostalgia set, so connected as it is to real childhood and adolescent memory?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toby Awards</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-03-29-0900-toby-awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 09:47:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-03-29-0900-toby-awards/</guid>
      <description>And the Toby for Outstanding Building of the Year goes to… (Cut to rival building management teams dressed up in tuxedos, sitting on the edge of their seats.)
The Toby Awards? — Photo by Tobyblog on Flickr  Makes me wonder what a Toby looks like. Today, too sick to care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Sick</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-03-28-so-sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:46:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-03-28-so-sick/</guid>
      <description>Being sick on a trip is the worst. I&amp;rsquo;ve mostly been sleeping every spare moment I get. Managed to catch a pretty decent cheese ball of a movie, though. It was old school campy fun in the best way. Nicely captured the feel of old 80s schlock-horror movies like The Gate and Return of the Living Dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Year in Pictures — 2017 Edition</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-12-31-top-nine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-12-31-top-nine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/img/2017-12-31-top-nine/top9.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of my favorite pictures from the past year. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/75738497@N00/sets/72157688929748362&#34;&gt;See the full set on Flickr.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Latte Beer and Ace Pumpkin Cider</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-11-24-pumpkin-latte-ace-pumpkin-cider/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 10:49:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-11-24-pumpkin-latte-ace-pumpkin-cider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4580/38604886832_7bc4b06488_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Coffee, Pumpkin Pie, and Pumpkin Latte Beer&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Coffee, Pumpkin Pie, and Pumpkin Latte Beer — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/38604886832/&#34; title=&#34;Coffee, Pumpkin Pie, and Pumpkin Latte Beer&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


This year while out shopping for turkey and wine, I discovered a couple of very fallish, and very Thanksgiving-appropriate beverages I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with you all. One is a new seasonal coffee brew from my favorite DFW brewery &lt;a href=&#34;http://martinhousebrewing.com/&#34;&gt;Martin House&lt;/a&gt;, and the other is a special cider I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in three years — &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/&#34;&gt;Ace&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; own extraordinary Pumpkin Cider. Read on!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smells Like Halloween at Yankee Candle</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-09-04-yankee-candle-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 09:41:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-09-04-yankee-candle-halloween/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4422/36040105263_67f5b87dbe_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Window advert&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Window advert — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/36040105263/&#34; title=&#34;Window advert&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s in a smell? The power to evoke. Memories. People. Places. And special times in our lives. Seasons long forgotten. All brought back in an instant the second a particular aroma hits our nostrils. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that scented candles, long thought domain of grandmas and boring little gift shops, have become respected among the nostalgia set in recent years. I read once that people don&amp;rsquo;t remember scents; that you remember the things associated with it or the strong feelings the scent creates, but the brain does not store memory of the scent itself. And now I find myself trying to remember what the woods smell like in autumn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2015-2016</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again folks, that magical time between Christmas and New Year where thoughtful commentators like myself come out with their end of year retrospectives; and continuing a tradition I established a couple of years back on this site, I intend to give you my take on the best of my buddy Brian Hammons&amp;rsquo; output over on the internet&amp;rsquo;s most beloved nostalgia blog, ReviewTheWorld.com.
You can catch up on previous years&amp;rsquo; content by taking a look at my other lists:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August into December at the Holiday Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/august-into-december-at-the-holiday-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 13:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/august-into-december-at-the-holiday-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm9.staticflickr.com/8449/28674407714_ef688b56a7_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mr. Pumpkin&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Mr. Pumpkin — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/28674407714/&#34; title=&#34;Mr. Pumpkin&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.holidaywarehouse.com/&#34;&gt;Holiday Warehouse&lt;/a&gt; is a largish, and rather outstanding, independent holiday decor shop located in Plano, Texas. Like its well known cousin The &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/&#34;&gt;Decorator&amp;rsquo;s Warehouse&lt;/a&gt; in Arlington, the concentration is mainly on Christmas, but not as exclusively.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bollywood Burrito</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-bollywood-burrito/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-bollywood-burrito/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Sq3xak90kZg/V6zwoaw0I7I/AAAAAAAAC40/evK2MCidSAEDtEYEMePNyQVFAWYgzkF1QCLcB/s640/IMG_5441.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember Taco Naan, the Mexican-Indian hybrid restaurant &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/&#34;&gt;I wrote about&lt;/a&gt; a long time back? I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the very same one my buddy &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/2015/03/texas-taco-challenge-taco-naan-vs-fuel.html&#34;&gt;Brian featured&lt;/a&gt; on his second trip to the Big D, where he stacked up its offerings against the nationally renowned taco dive Fuel City. Well, they&amp;rsquo;re still around and busier and better than ever! The place is expanding like mad, doubling its interior floor space and hopefully renovating those dismal restrooms. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know because I&amp;rsquo;ve never had the courage to try them again. But you don&amp;rsquo;t go to Taco Naan to use the bathroom, man, so no worries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Pineapple Cider &amp; Shannon Irish Red</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/</guid>
      <description>Beer is great year-round, but summer brings its own varieties. I noticed recently that hard ciders are becoming more popular. I had a chance to sample a new one from Ace, makers of an outstanding pumpkin cider that I am very much looking forward to having again this fall. Their pear cider, available in all seasons, merits a future review. But this one I had not seen before.
Indeed, it called out to me from the shelf with unabashed summery fruitiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing 30th Anniversary Movies</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/amazing-30th-anniversary-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 14:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/amazing-30th-anniversary-movies/</guid>
      <description>Today marks the 30th anniversary of two very special, very &#34;eighties&#34; movies that I happen to love. The (legitimate) Transformers The Movie, and Space Camp, which I watched for the first time only a year or so ago with the kids.  I honestly can&#39;t remember when I first saw the Transformers movie, but it wasn&#39;t in the theaters. I was the only one of my group of friends that caught it months, if not years later, after it came out on VHS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Meganerd Fun Pack!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-meganerd-fun-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-meganerd-fun-pack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1507/26490173342_5105efd276_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;The Super Meganerd Fun Pack&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;The Super Meganerd Fun Pack — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/26490173342/&#34; title=&#34;The Super Meganerd Fun Pack&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What the pack?!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My cousin Carl, &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/&#34;&gt;as previously featured on Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt;, sent this to me for my birthday. Get a load. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like he knows me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sfanthor! House of Wax</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/</guid>
      <description>Here in North Texas the sun is shining. The weather is warming up. The world outside is getting brighter. The Texas wildflowers are already in bloom, thanks to a mild and soggy winter. In the woods, things are moving. The itchy season is upon us, and the window of opportunity for a lot of local geocaches is closing, as the casual players tend to steer clear of anything that might put them in the way of tall grass, poison ivy, or the dreaded tick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversations 2 – Thoughts on the Wii U</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/conversations-2-thoughts-on-the-wii-u/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/conversations-2-thoughts-on-the-wii-u/</guid>
      <description>TheVCubeSolver and I talk about the things we love about the Nintendo Wii U on a long drive home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lights Out For Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>#pic { display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; }   Do you remember Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt? I wrote about that place around this time last year. It&amp;rsquo;s closed now. I had a dream about it the other night, or rather its next incarnation, which was as a hybrid Christmas/Halloween store. I know the owners have an interest in Christmas things, so that detail is not too surprising. But in my dream, there was also a functional toilet over by the register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Hour&#39;s Wreck the Halls</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dark-hours-wreck-the-halls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm2.staticflickr.com/1695/23471270343_deab39ff5a_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Wreck the Halls — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/23471270343/&#34; title=&#34;Wreck the Halls&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;2015 was the year I discovered &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tobyblog.com/2015/09/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever.html&#34;&gt;Dark Hour Haunted House&lt;/a&gt;, and you probably realize by now what a fan I am. We are very fortunate to live in an area with access to a year round haunt. To be able to be successful at that requires a level of quality and showmanship, frankly, above your average haunt. Not to detract from anyone else in the business (no one can do it all!), but I think it does hold true. In getting to know these guys and the haunt itself a little better over these past few months, it is becoming clear how much of an inspiration they are to other folks in the industry. And I&amp;rsquo;ve still not yet discovered all they have to offer!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Pumpkin for St. Michael</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-pumpkin-for-st.-michael/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-pumpkin-for-st.-michael/</guid>
      <description>September 29th is the feast of St. Michael the Archangel, or Michaelmas as it is known in European countries. St. Michael cast the devil out of heaven, and is the commander of the armies of God. He is traditionally shown fighting a dragon, or with his foot on the back of the devil. He is the patron of soldiers and police officers, but also of the ill and suffering. He has appeared to people at various times curing diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</guid>
      <description>I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&#39;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&#39;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&#39;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&#39;t get caught!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — The Great Pumpkin Waltz</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-the-great-pumpkin-waltz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-the-great-pumpkin-waltz/</guid>
      <description>We are officially in the &amp;ldquo;-BER months&amp;rdquo; now, a time of year that for my generation is indelibly stamped by the melancholy Peanuts cartoon soundtracks of Vince Guiraldi and his trio. Though the nostalgic quality of these tracks reaches fever pitch around Christmastime, we begin our seasonal contemplation with this wistful little tune, quickly supplanted in the Guiraldi lineup, but never quite forgotten. It remains one of my favorites, but I&amp;rsquo;ll only listen to it from the start of September through Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Spooks on YouTube: Apparitions</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/free-spooks-on-youtube-apparitions/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for something spooky to watch as we wind our way down to Halloween, but find yourself bored by the usual fare of cheesy monster movies or gross slasher flicks? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re in the mood for something a little more thoughtful; a little more substantial, perhaps? Let me show you something interesting.
 Apparitions&amp;nbsp;is a BBC miniseries about a Catholic exorcist who finds himself at the center of a satanic intrigue that reaches to the Vatican and threatens the world itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Decorator&#39;s Warehouse</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-decorators-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>The Decorator&amp;rsquo;s Warehouse, located in Arlington, Texas, bills itself as Texas&amp;rsquo;s largest Christmas store. And it is very large. But what really impresses you upon entering the place is just how jam-packed it is with holiday and seasonal baubles, as if despite its football-field size floor space they still did not have quite enough room to fit everything.&amp;nbsp;
As soon as you walk in the door you&amp;rsquo;re assaulted with holiday cheer; the entrance is rather elaborately decorated and serves as both a picture station and portal of sorts into this alternate dimension that feels something like Santa&amp;rsquo;s attic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aisles &amp; Aisles of Halloween at At Home </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/aisles-aisles-of-halloween-at-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/aisles-aisles-of-halloween-at-at-home/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re just under 100 days to Halloween now, but there are certain places you can always depend on to roll out the spooky stock a little early. I covered At Home last year and this year&amp;rsquo;s selection looks bigger and better than ever. For 2015 our local store has literally doubled the floor space devoted to Halloween goods. And, well, just take a look for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diana Levin&#39;s Pocket Watch</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/diana-levins-pocket-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/diana-levins-pocket-watch/</guid>
      <description>While in attendance at Texas Frightmare Weekend I picked up a small pocket watch as a souvenir for my daughter from the booth of Diana Levin. Check out her gallery on her website. Or better yet, if you like what you see you can buy something from her Etsy store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Frightmare Weekend</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/texas-frightmare-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/texas-frightmare-weekend/</guid>
      <description>This year I attended Texas Frightmare Weekend for the first time. By now it seems like forever ago. But lucky you — I saved all the pictures! So here they are without much verbal adornment, or it&amp;rsquo;d probably take me another month and a half to get this up.

I suggest you take your time with this post. It&amp;rsquo;s a big one. Really savor the photographs. Left-click to enlarge them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screening Phantasm With The Tall Man</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</guid>
      <description>From a respectful write-up on Texas Frightmare Weekend by Dread Central:
Can we stop calling Texas Frightmare Weekend a “regional con” now? The first reader I met this year was Aaron from Australia, who had flown all the way here to experience TFW as his FIRST con.
I met that guy! Twice. Sat right next to him at the special 35mm screening of Phantasm at the Alamo Draft House in Richardson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit to Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Channard from Hellraiser II, in all his gloryCollector&#39;s Crypt is a boutique shop in Dallas specializing in horror and sci-fi collectibles, memorabilia, paraphernalia, and… well, you just gotta see it, folks. It&#39;s an amazing place. I discovered them only recently after attending the St. Patrick&#39;s Slay Weekend event at Dark Hour Haunted House in Plano. They were a sponsor of that particular show, so Dark Hour graciously gave them some floor space to sell a few wares after the show and otherwise promote the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noshing Tacos with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/noshing-tacos-with-review-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/noshing-tacos-with-review-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Once again we were proud to host buddy Brian Hammons of the food/candy/retro/life blog Review the World as he made his way down to Dallas for the big UFC 185 fight night. What a weekend! Among other things, I introduced Brian Hammons to some of the best tacos in the COUNTRY. Go see what resulted over on reviewtheworld.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2014/</guid>
      <description>One thing I love is end of year retrospectives. And in the grand tradition I started last year, I offer to you the top ten Review the World episodes of 2014. So clear your personal calendars, grab a bag of Rap Snacks, and settle in the for the show. These are all episodes I love, and I encourage you to watch every one in its entirety.
#10: Childhood Neighborhood Tour We begin with Brian&amp;rsquo;s most recent entry, one that was intended to cap all of his furious activity for 2014, and at one point, possibly forever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Year in Pictures</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-year-in-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-year-in-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Being a fan of post-Christmas year end wrap-ups, I decided to create a Flickr set highlighting some of the events and activities that filled our lives this year. These are not my best photos or even my favorites, but just a (largish) collection of pictures that capture the essence of 2014 for me. A little bit of countryside, a little bit of life at home. One or two guest appearances. Flowers and ponies and monsters and toys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Chix Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-chix-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-chix-review/</guid>
      <description>We have reached &#34;Peak Blogger&#34; in this society, folks. If the existence of Tobyblog was not proof of that already, take a look at the above picture. It was a cold, blustery Saturday afternoon and I was visiting nearby Arlington. It was around lunchtime and I had some time to kill, so I decided to walk over to the nearby strip mall and scope out the restaurants. There were a surprising number of cuisines on offer for such a small area, but this place caught my eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Very First Tobyblog Giveaway!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/announcing-the-very-first-tobyblog-giveaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/announcing-the-very-first-tobyblog-giveaway/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to win this original 8 x 10 photograph that hung in our house this past Halloween? It&amp;rsquo;s a portrait inspired by my all-time favorite Halloween blog, The Skull and Pumpkin of Mike Cathcart&amp;rsquo;s. The updates have been spotty over these past few years, but the back content is well worth discovering for yourself. If you do take a look, be sure to leave a comment in appreciation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mask of the Red Death</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-mask-of-the-red-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-mask-of-the-red-death/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The &amp;lsquo;Red Death&amp;rsquo; had long devastated the country. No pestilence had ever been so fatal, or so hideous. Blood was its Avatar and its seal — the redness and the horror of blood. There were sharp pains, and sudden dizziness, and then profuse bleeding at the pores, with dissolution.&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;With such precautions the courtiers might bid defiance to contagion. The external world could take care of itself.&amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;All these and security were within.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Iconography of Halloween: Skeletons</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-iconography-of-halloween-skeletons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2014 22:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-iconography-of-halloween-skeletons/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Most people don&#39;t consider, think, imagine what&#39;s inside them. Inside of everyone of us, that terrible representative of death. A skeleton.&#34;~From the short story Skeleton by Ray Bradbury





































 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Dias De Los Muertos at World Market</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</guid>
      <description>Already a great place to find exotic candies, foreign soda pop, and specialty food items at any time of the year (Brian Hammons, you know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about), World Market really comes alive for Halloween. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got one in your area, get down there right now and check their selection. The stuff they carry is definitely outside of the Target/Big Lots/Dollar Store Halloween mold, but that&amp;rsquo;s not to say it&amp;rsquo;s super expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retropalooza</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/retropalooza/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2014 15:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/retropalooza/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I took the kids to the amazing Retropalooza convention in Arlington, Texas, and boy did we have a blast! There were loads and loads of dealer tables with some very cool nostalgia items on display, classic and rare games galore, cosplayers, and even a few YouTube celebrities. Take a look at some of the fun things we discovered.
The owner of Tendril here was willing to let him go for a meagre forty dollars, making it the best deal I found.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Star of Phantasm</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-real-star-of-phantasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2014 22:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-real-star-of-phantasm/</guid>
      <description>Here you go, folks, the real star of Phantasm — that bad-ass muscle car! A real thing of beauty, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even that much of a car guy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Dino Drac Funpack, Sep 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-sep-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-sep-2014/</guid>
      <description>September has arrived, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to open another funpack from Dinosaur Dracula!

Most of you may already recognize Dinosaur Dracula as the preeminent nostalgia blog on the web. (If not, you may recall its previous incarnation, X-Entertainment) Matt, the guy that runs the site, puts on quite a show every year for the Halloween season, and I must say 2014 is already off to a great start! Watching his videos and reading his reviews has become sort of a Halloween tradition in our family, something we look forward to every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Dino Drac Funpack, Aug 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-aug-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-aug-2014/</guid>
      <description>Most of you may already recognize&amp;nbsp;Dinosaur Dracula&amp;nbsp;as the preeminent nostalgia blog on the web. (If not, you may recall its previous incarnation,&amp;nbsp;X-Entertainment) Matt, the guy that runs the site, puts on quite a show every year for the Halloween season, and I must say 2014 is already off to a great start! Watching his videos and reading his reviews has become sort of a Halloween tradition in our family, something we look forward to every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incredible Halloween Village at Michaels</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/incredible-halloween-village-at-michaels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/incredible-halloween-village-at-michaels/</guid>
      <description>HALLOWEEN LOVERS EVERYWHERE, IF YOU HAVE NEVER SEEN THE LEMAX SPOOKY TOWN COLLECTION AT MICHAELS, FIND ONE NEAR YOU AND GO THERE.&amp;nbsp;NOW.

I am not kidding.
I discovered the world of Lemax Village collectibles only a year ago. They also make Christmas sets, but the Halloween village is sold exclusively at Michaels. Now I&amp;rsquo;m not normally the kind of guy that goes gaga for stuff like this, but the artistry and imagination evident in these pieces is hard to deny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — Love Songs</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-love-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-love-songs/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time once again for one of my patented YouTube cover battles, and in typical fashion you pick the winner. Tonight&amp;rsquo;s theme is one of my favorite for YouTube covers — LOVE SONGS. I have my personal favorite, of course, but I won&amp;rsquo;t spoil it for you. Enjoy, and leave a comment to vote for the winner. The first track is by Goga, a local (Dallas) wedding singer and one-man-band act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween at Big Lots</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/halloween-at-big-lots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/halloween-at-big-lots/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, friends! It&amp;rsquo;s been a few days since my last update, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t been idle. Have you noticed how early the stores are stocking for Halloween this year? I blogged about my first sighting at At Home&amp;nbsp;(formerly Garden Ridge)&amp;nbsp;which was on July 1st, a full one month earlier than last year. (And if you&amp;rsquo;re interested, that was at a chain called Home Goods, where the theme of ravens &amp;amp; blackbirds predominated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yankee Candle Halloween Preview</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yankee Candle had a special one-day preview of their upcoming Halloween 2014 collection, and we dropped in to get a look. Thanks to @PerkyJewels #FF for the tip-off!


Tragically, most of the &#34;Bonies&#34; decorations were sold out by the time we got there. We were told by staff that most of the merchandise was gone within the first half-hour of the store opening, so that should show you the amazing pent-up demand for Halloween this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Halloween Store Opening Soon</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/spirit-halloween-store-opening-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/spirit-halloween-store-opening-soon/</guid>
      <description>Took a little stroll through the neighborhood this morning, and what should we find?
Come September, tune in to Tobyblog for further details!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit To The Toy Store</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-the-toy-store/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2014 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-the-toy-store/</guid>
      <description>The great thing about being a dad to small kids is that you always have a built-in excuse to be in the toy aisle. And if you have your kids with you then nobody looks twice at you as you gawk at all the amazing stuff on the store shelves these days. We are living in a golden age for toys and board games. Sure, there were a lot of really cool toys that I miss from the seventies and eighties that I wish my kids had a chance to experience, but today&#39;s market offers a certain quality and vast variety of toys and other amusements that the old days could never touch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Has Arrived at At Home</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/halloween-has-arrived-at-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 22:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/halloween-has-arrived-at-at-home/</guid>
      <description>Garden Ridge recently declared bankruptcy, and are now being reincorporated as At Home. But true to form, the seasons still come early there and stay late.
My dear wife noticed yesterday that one of the nearby stores had been refurbished, so we decided to drop in and check it out. I of course had high hopes for what to expect, and I wasn&amp;rsquo;t disappointed.

Indeed, Halloween and fall are in full swing there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropping Quarters</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dropping-quarters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 22:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dropping-quarters/</guid>
      <description>There is a little independent retro gaming store in Plano that is the closest thing to a real arcade that I&amp;rsquo;ve ever experienced with the kids. There are still a lot of places you could call &amp;ldquo;arcades&amp;rdquo;, mostly attached to chain family restaurants like Chuck-E-Cheese or entertainment complexes like Fun Zone or Amazing Jakes. But the key differentiator for me is that the machines take real quarters, preferably only one per play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restroom Tissue Dispensers</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/restroom-tissue-dispensers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/restroom-tissue-dispensers/</guid>
      <description>(Works best if you read this in an Andy Rooney-esque whine.)

This keeps happening to me over and over and over again lately. I have to make use of the public facilities (seldom a delightful experience anyway), I go to the sink, wash my hands, look up, and see this mess —


Now what is wrong with this picture? Take a look at how this works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — Red Rubber Ball</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-red-rubber-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-red-rubber-ball/</guid>
      <description>I woke up this morning with this song stuck in my head, thinking about my dad and the good progress he&amp;rsquo;s making recovering from a triple bypass operation.
I probably thought of it because I noticed it was in the repertoire of local musician Bruce Wilder, who graced us at the coffee shop one evening with his guitar.
  Here are my three favorite YouTube covers of this 1966 song by Paul Simon and Bruce Woodley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Food Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/new-orleans-food-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/new-orleans-food-review/</guid>
      <description>New Orleans is, of course, a city known for its food, home to some of the best chefs in the country. I was in town recently, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d check out some of the local establishments and give you guys a virtual sight-tasting tour. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the hotel vending machine.


Hey, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten all day and I had a couple of hours to kill till my family showed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baker Street</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/baker-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/baker-street/</guid>
      <description>Love this song. Local musician Bruce Wilder was recently performing it solo at Firewheel Coffee, my office away from the office. Makes me want to sneak up behind him with a giant saxophone and start blaring away at the appropriate moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Worry, Be Happy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dont-worry-be-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/dont-worry-be-happy/</guid>
      <description>And that would make him the first of our kids to eat a Happy Meal.Not sure if I like the new mascot. He tried to eat the baby&#39;s noony.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Halloween Merch of the Year</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/first-halloween-merch-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 06:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/first-halloween-merch-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Technically spotted on July 1 at Michaels. Thanks to The Swagger Mom for the tip-off about fall going up this week. That made me wonder, and my suspicions checked out.&amp;nbsp;

And yeah, it was mostly generic fall decorations on a couple of shelves, but over on the other side of the store, on a lonely end cap display, there was this:

Unmistakable. Halloween ribbon.

Frankensteins, witches, spiders, skeletons… Have you ever stopped to think how rich Halloween is in iconography?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer is Coming</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/summer-is-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2014 08:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/summer-is-coming/</guid>
      <description>In fact, it&#39;s already here. My woodland trekking has been sidelined a bit due to having to nurse a sumac rash, but I&#39;ll be back soon enough. Here&#39;s hoping you guys get out and sweat a bit this summer. Enjoy the late evenings while you can! DST. What a gift from Mr. Nixon! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Musical Interlude</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-musical-interlude/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 22:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-musical-interlude/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anniversary Candy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/anniversary-candy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/anniversary-candy/</guid>
      <description>Aren&amp;rsquo;t I lucky? How many guys get to have a truly one of a kind candy made just for them?

What you are looking at is an out of this world treat that I have dubbed &amp;ldquo;Anniversary Candy&amp;rdquo;. Made by my wife, purely for my own enjoyment.

She made the first batch a few years ago for Christmas, and it&amp;rsquo;s been a special request of mine ever since on celebratory occasions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wylie&#39;s Angel</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/wylies-angel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/wylies-angel/</guid>
      <description>I like geocaching for lots of reasons. I like to be outside. I like discovering new places. I like&amp;nbsp;walking and connecting with nature. But occasionally I learn something as well. Usually it&amp;rsquo;s just local historical trivia, or maybe a&amp;nbsp;geography&amp;nbsp;lesson. But sometimes the lesson is more personal, and as in this case, tragic.
The morning started out with a trip to the Trinity Trails in Wylie, Texas for some hiking and caching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Toe 2 Toe&#34; Review: Chili Cheese Fries</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2014 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</guid>
      <description>THE CONTENDERS:
Melter&amp;rsquo;s (Irving)
melty burgers and loaded baked potatoes14 year old native Dallas establishment2 locations, downtown Dallas &amp;amp; Irvinglow key atmosphere with an emphasis on the food&amp;nbsp;vs.Burger Fi (Garland)upscale burgers and hot dogsFlorida chain with scores of locations&amp;nbsp;around the country50s/60s diner aestheticthick, home-cut fries and real angus beef
MELTERS&amp;nbsp;
Melters&amp;rsquo; chili cheese fries were the first and, so far, only thing I&amp;rsquo;ve had off of their menu, but I&amp;rsquo;m already impressed with the place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Day of Decisions</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-day-of-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-day-of-decisions/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m celebrating a major personal milestone today, and I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a more fitting way to commemorate it on this site than by encouraging you all to watch one of my favorite episodes of The Ray Bradbury Theater from 1989, The Wonderful Death of Dudley Stone. This episode is indeed all about decisions, priorities, and focusing on what&amp;rsquo;s important in life. 
Part 1 
Part 2 
Part 3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOUND OBJECTS: A PHOTOLOG OF GEOCACHING SWAGARTICLE I EVIL ZOMBIE CLOWN</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/found-objects-a-photolog-of-geocaching-swagarticle-i-evil-zombie-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/found-objects-a-photolog-of-geocaching-swagarticle-i-evil-zombie-clown/</guid>
      <description>I have no particular fear of clowns. I am not one of those people. But this thing gives me the creeps. Downright turns my stomach. 
I found it in an ammo can in a small copse of woods near the office, nestled among a collection of unremarkable trinkets. It&amp;rsquo;s only about an inch or so high, so it took me a second to realize that it carries in its left hand a severed human arm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Naan Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/</guid>
      <description>Go back, right now, and take a look at my Zyka India Food restaurant review. Notice anything suspicious about the Chicken 65? Take a closer look at those ingredients. 

Jalapenos. Onions. Cilantro. Sound familiar? 
If you&amp;rsquo;re from Texas or anywhere in the Southwest you would immediately associate that combination with Mexican or Tex-Mex cuisine. There are other similarities, too, like the general spiciness, the use of chilis, or the penchant for using circular flatbread at every meal to sandwich ingredients and sop up sauces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Getting Better - Ken Nordine</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/youre-getting-better-ken-nordine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/youre-getting-better-ken-nordine/</guid>
      <description>My most popular Youtube upload.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geocaching Explained</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/geocaching-explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 21:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/geocaching-explained/</guid>
      <description>Geocaching is one of my main hobbies. Since I&amp;rsquo;m going to be posting a lot about it, here&amp;rsquo;s a formal introduction from Groundspeak, the company that runs the geocaching.com site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suncreek Park - More Than Meets The Eye</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/suncreek-park-more-than-meets-the-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/suncreek-park-more-than-meets-the-eye/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago my wife told me about a new park she had discovered while killing time between a couple of the kids&amp;rsquo; classes. 
While climbing an overpass she caught site of some paved trails just off the road that interested her enough to want to Google it later. The trails turned out to be part of Suncreek Park in Allen, Texas. The website claims Suncreek sports only four tenths of a mile of paved trails, so it&amp;rsquo;s not much for walking, hiking, or biking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon! Houston Winter Open</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/coming-soon-houston-winter-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/coming-soon-houston-winter-open/</guid>
      <description>A teaser for my upcoming documentary on the Houston Winter Open 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2013</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2013/</guid>
      <description>Since Brian and Review the World were my main inspirations in starting my own blog, I figured it would be fitting to begin by introducing some of my favorite episodes from the past year. According to Brian, 2013 was one of the busiest years he&amp;rsquo;s ever had on the site, and it shows. He had a ton of great content.
#10: The Brian and Tim Show Episode #25: Halloween Extra - UFO and Ghost Discussion Sort of an extended special segment of the 2013 Halloween episode, Brian and Tim decide to talk about their own experiences with the paranormal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning.</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-beginning./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-beginning./</guid>
      <description>My name is Toby. In spring of 2013 I discovered Brian Hammons&amp;rsquo; blog Review the World, and something clicked. Here was a guy, slightly my junior, getting out and enjoying life with his friends, exploring his local environment, and generally on fire with all the possibilities that an ordinary life offers to those who know how to look for them. I had spent the bulk of 2012 doing all those things with my two older kids while my wife was for the most part, regrettably, stuck at home working and/or gestating.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>