<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Candles on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/candles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Candles on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 09:41:11 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/candles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Smells Like Halloween at Yankee Candle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017-09-04-yankee-candle-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 09:41:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017-09-04-yankee-candle-halloween/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4422/36040105263_67f5b87dbe_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Window advert&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Window advert, by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Toby Marks&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/36040105263/&#34; title=&#34;Window advert&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


What&amp;rsquo;s in a smell? The power to evoke. Memories. People. Places. And special times in our lives. Seasons long forgotten. All brought back in an instant the second a particular aroma hits our nostrils. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that scented candles, long thought domain of grandmas and boring little gift shops, have become respected among the nostalgia set in recent years. I read once that people don&amp;rsquo;t remember scents; that you remember the things associated with it or the strong feelings the scent creates, but the brain does not store memory of the scent itself. And now I find myself trying to remember what the woods smell like in autumn.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Dias De Los Muertos at World Market</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</guid>
      <description>Already a great place to find exotic candies, foreign soda pop, and specialty food items at any time of the year (Brian Hammons, you know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about), World Market really comes alive for Halloween. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got one in your area, get down there right now and check their selection. The stuff they carry is definitely outside of the Target/Big Lots/Dollar Store Halloween mold, but that&amp;rsquo;s not to say it&amp;rsquo;s super expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yankee Candle Halloween Preview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yankee Candle had a special one-day preview of their upcoming Halloween 2014 collection, and we dropped in to get a look. Thanks to @PerkyJewels #FF for the tip-off!


Tragically, most of the &#34;Bonies&#34; decorations were sold out by the time we got there. We were told by staff that most of the merchandise was gone within the first half-hour of the store opening, so that should show you the amazing pent-up demand for Halloween this year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>