<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vacation on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</title>
    <link>https://tobyblog.com/tags/vacation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vacation on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2024 (c) Toby Marks</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 17:32:25 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tobyblog.com/tags/vacation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Crow at the Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190825-grand-canyon-crow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 17:32:25 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190825-grand-canyon-crow/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s ready for fall?&#xA;You can count me in, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure &amp;ldquo;ready&amp;rdquo; is the best word for it. Summer seemed to pass by so fast this year. Barely had time to really enjoy it, it seems, before it&amp;rsquo;s practically gone. They say this happens as you get older, but I suspect in my case it has more to do with a dearth of time spent outside this year, soaking up sun and heat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Worst Vacation Injuries</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190809-my-worst-vacation-injuries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 10:58:48 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190809-my-worst-vacation-injuries/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve visited a few spots with some potential for accidents, but so far my worst vacation injuries have been banging my head on the roof of the car unloading luggage (last year; my neck was sore for days), and scraping up my arm pretty bad after tripping over luggage in the dark (last night). It seems I have a problem with luggage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 09.01</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190809-road-trip-travel-log-09-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190809-road-trip-travel-log-09-01/</guid>
      <description>Arrived in beautiful Telluride, Colorado, and yes, this is my first update since day #2 of vacation. So much for my Travel Log. Between lack of cell signal and surrendering my phone to the kid, and straight up being too busy and/or exhausted, I haven’t had much opportunity for posting.&#xA;We’ve been busy!&#xA;Back to the Grand Canyon this year, and this time we got to spend a night in the park, with a chance to do some dawn/dusk shots of the canyon itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 02.02</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190803-road-trip-travel-log-02-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190803-road-trip-travel-log-02-02/</guid>
      <description>Finally made it to Red Rock State Park, and made a couple of new discoveries along the way. Our route took us through what turned out be the incredibly beautiful Coconino National Forest, a place we have vowed to return. If Tolkien’s Elves were a real thing, they might just choose to live in a place like that. Verdant green forests around the bases of giant granite mountains, interspersed all along the way with little villages and expensive looking cabin retreats, with lights hanging from the trees across bridges that span crystal clear mountain streams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 02.01</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190802-road-trip-travel-log-02-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190802-road-trip-travel-log-02-01/</guid>
      <description>On the road from Albuquerque to Flagstaff, near which we turn south to Red Rock State Park in Arizona. The kids are keen to get in a hike today, the first “real” day of our vacation, as far as I’m concerned. It’s been fun watching the younger two get excited over taking pictures from the car with the little Instax Mini. That was Kassi’s great idea. We bought Anthony around 150 exposures and his eyes got wide when I told him I wanted him to use every single one by the end of the trip.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 01.02</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190801-road-trip-travel-log-01-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190801-road-trip-travel-log-01-02/</guid>
      <description>Picture of me in the Llano Estacado, Texas’s “wine country”. On the road for quite a while and still not out of the state. Holding up well. Fear the little one may be coming down with a cold. Hope he’s better after some rest.&#xA;Changed restaurant plans and will revisit our old favorite in Albuquerque for the third year in a row.&#xA;The food there has always been great, though the service is consistently slow.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Road Trip Travel Log 01.01</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190801-road-trip-travel-log-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/20190801-road-trip-travel-log-01-01/</guid>
      <description>We’re well in to the big family road trip of 2019, and the obligatory Texas pit stop at Bucc-ees has been checked off the list. Would have sent you guys a pic from the storied Bucc-ees bathrooms, but I was too excited about these new hot n’ spicy Beaver Nuggets! You can hear all about my first experience with those glorified Corn Pops in this review I did last year with my good buddy Brian.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See You in Arizona</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190731-see-you-in-arizona/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 17:49:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190731-see-you-in-arizona/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s summer vacation time again, and I&amp;rsquo;m as excited as if I were returning to Hogwarts after a summer at the Dursley&amp;rsquo;s — a completely made up expression that I thought of just now purely as an excuse to post the picture below, of which I happen to be fond. Back when I had hair I might have been able to pass off a kind of Harry Potter-esque look. Now it&amp;rsquo;s more like Filch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dad Wagon is in Vacation Mode</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190723-the-dad-wagon-is-in-vacation-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 17:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190723-the-dad-wagon-is-in-vacation-mode/</guid>
      <description>Must be time for a road trip, because I find myself wondering what the wagon would look like with wood paneling.&#xA;🚙⛰🏜</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
