<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videos on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videos on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 11:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/videos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tobyblog 🎃Halloween🎃 Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-halloween-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-halloween-special/</guid>
      <description>I love Halloween. You do, too. This video is a tribute to that season, to every memory and every thrill. To cold autumn nights. To the warm glow of jack o&amp;rsquo; lanterns. To spooky stories and cozy evenings. To every bit of magic and adventure in our lives.
This is the story of Halloween 2013 as we experienced it; what has gone down in our lives and memories as THE BEST HALLOWEEN EVER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cajun Treats</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/cajun-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 21:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/cajun-treats/</guid>
      <description>This video is something of a personal achievement, having been now just under two years in the making, and passing, as it does, yet another milestone in the revitalization of this little blog. Yeah, I know, that&amp;rsquo;s sort of a grandiose way to introduce a video where I discuss the merits of quail eggs and potato chips with friends and family, but there we are. It means something to me — hard to quantify — to be active on the site again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucc-ees Beaver Nuggets with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bucc-ees-beaver-nuggets-with-review-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bucc-ees-beaver-nuggets-with-review-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Join Brian and I in downtown Garland, Texas as we dish on one of the state’s finest contributions to the culinary world, Beaver Nuggets.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cauldron Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:53:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Joined once again by nostalgia blogger and good friend Brian Hammons of reviewtheworld.com, Augie and I team up to complete our trilogy of Skittles reviews, this time looking at the legendary and rarely sighted Cauldron Skittles variety, now in its second year on store shelves. Does the candy itself live up to the promise of its bright orange bag? We find out, and the answer may just shock you. (It probably won&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brightside Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 15:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</guid>
      <description>Join me, Augie, and superpal Brian of Review the World for installment number two in this soon to be classic trilogy of Skittles candy reviews. This time we look at Brightside Skittles, the very flipside of the Darkside reviewed a couple of years back with Brian on his last visit to Dallas. A great theme for summer and sunny days, will Brightside warm your tummy as we slip into fall and all things pumpkin spice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Skittles Review with Brian</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 23:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, folks.
It has been a while now since I&amp;rsquo;ve been active on this site, but life has not held still for me and the family. Since the last time I posted anything of significance, quite a great deal has happened, actually, much of which was originally destined for publication here. Well, as it does, life got in the way, priorities shifted, my free time diminished, etc. etc. — and the gist of it all is that you folks were left unattended for many months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Czech Stop and Slovaceks</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-czech-stop-and-slovaceks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-czech-stop-and-slovaceks/</guid>
      <description>After a long hiatus, my front seat food review series is back! This time I feature some of the Waco area&amp;rsquo;s finest gas station Czech cuisine. If you&amp;rsquo;re ever in the area you should absolutely stop at one or both of these fine establishments. Such a treat.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frozard Man</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/frozard-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/frozard-man/</guid>
      <description>This is a tribute video to my brother. You can think of it as the pilot episode of a fictional reality show series. It includes some backyard wrestling, a special cooking segment also featured in the 2015 Thanksgiving Special, and a frog tossing competition using actual Louisiana bull frogs. It is wild, and like the man himself, not quite safe for work!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geocaching Lost Episodes</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/geocaching-lost-episodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 11:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/geocaching-lost-episodes/</guid>
      <description>Over the years I&amp;rsquo;ve accumulated a ton of never-used footage from our various geocaching adventures. Here they all are, wrapped up a big ball of video for you, my Tobyblogging public.
Enjoy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Play Mario Party 10</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/we-play-mario-party-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/we-play-mario-party-10/</guid>
      <description>The kids and I play Mario Party 10, the most inexplicably hated Mario Party of them all!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Geocoin Collection</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/my-geocoin-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/my-geocoin-collection/</guid>
      <description>You might find this interesting if you&amp;rsquo;re a hardcore geocaching or geocoin enthusiast, or an ASMR type.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We Play Wii Play Playthrough</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/we-play-wii-play-playthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 12:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/we-play-wii-play-playthrough/</guid>
      <description>TheVCubeSolver and I team up in this playthrough vid to reintroduce you to a seriously underrated classic on the Wii.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tobyblog Thanksgiving Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-thanksgiving-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-thanksgiving-special/</guid>
      <description>After taking some time off to contemplate the overwhelming success of my Burger King poop tweet*, we now return to our regularly scheduled programming.
In truth October is always a busy month for us and I don&amp;rsquo;t have much spare time for blogging. This past Halloween was without a doubt the best yet, but I&amp;rsquo;ll save that retrospective for another day. For today we find ourselves at the end of November, as grand a month as any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprechers Root Beer Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating our third anniversary of Buddy Team reviews, TheVCubeSolver and I team up to tackle the legendary Sprechers Root Beer. It&amp;rsquo;s good stuff!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Mega Fun Pack</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/super-mega-fun-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/super-mega-fun-pack/</guid>
      <description>The Super Mega Fun Pack geocache (GC5Z4X7) is a thinly-veiled tribute to Matt of dinosaurdracula.com and the amazing box of goodies that he puts together every month for his hordes of devoted fans. It&amp;rsquo;s only &amp;ldquo;veiled&amp;rdquo; at all because of the (understandable) policy of geocaching.com not to list any cache with references to commercial products. After going back and forth with them a bit about this, I relented and removed any overt references to Matt or his website, including changing the name of the cache from the original &amp;ldquo;The Dino Drac Fun Pack Geocache&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Super Mega Fun Pack&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bahama Bucks</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bahama-bucks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/bahama-bucks/</guid>
      <description>Katie and the gang over at Cheap Thrills invited me and the kids to do a co-review highlighting some of our favorite summer treats. You can check out their submission, Culver&amp;rsquo;s Frozen Custard, below.
  Naturally, I jumped at the chance to introduce you guys to one of the hidden treasures of our little neighborhood — Bahama Bucks!
Bucks is sort of like Jimmy Buffett&amp;rsquo;s own sno-cone stand. It serves sno-cones and tropical smoothies, some coffee drinks, and you can even get mixed fruit cups there if you&amp;rsquo;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kranky Coffee</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Straight off a Dollar Store shelf at the lovely Grapevine Mills Mall in Grapevine, Texas, and stocked just a few bins over from the storied Orchard Skittles, comes Kranky Candy, the coffee dusted confection you will soon come to know and love. Is it an afternoon snack? A breakfast substitute? Repurposed industrial by-product? You decide.
Joining me in his first proper appearance* on Tobyblog is my good friend Brian Hammons of ReviewTheWorld.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversations Series: The Nintendo NX</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/conversations-series-the-nintendo-nx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 10:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/conversations-series-the-nintendo-nx/</guid>
      <description>Join TheVCubeSolver and I as we discuss the recently announced NX project from Nintendo, a new and novel system that could be the successor to the beleaguered Wii U. But what exactly is it? For the moment, all we can do is guess. But I think we have some good ideas.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>March Cache Maintenance</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/march-cache-maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 11:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/march-cache-maintenance/</guid>
      <description>TheVCubeSolver and I hit the road on a pretty March morning to do some maintenance on a couple of our geocaches. The log for RtW #3 had filled up and Augie&amp;rsquo;s beaver cache had recently been reported missing. A little town, a little country. More geocaching goodness for you.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Night Cache</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/my-first-night-cache/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/my-first-night-cache/</guid>
      <description>Come along with the kids and I on our first night caching adventure. For the uninitiated among you, night caching is simply geocaching at night. Generally night caches are made so that you can&amp;rsquo;t find them during the daytime, by making use of trails of reflective tacks or tape or other forms of guidance visible only at night.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liver and Gizzards Review, with Sriracha Whoopie Pies</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/liver-and-gizzards-review-with-sriracha-whoopie-pies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/liver-and-gizzards-review-with-sriracha-whoopie-pies/</guid>
      <description>My buddy Brian Hammons over at Review the World requested another video food review, so I though I&amp;rsquo;d introduce him to a down-home treat from my childhood. I hope you&amp;rsquo;re happy with the results. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, this one is a bit of a deep dive; a little something for my hardcore devotees. That is, people that like watching me eat stuff in my car. And yes, I manage to add yet another stain to my car seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snickers Varieties and Lays Cappuccino Chips</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/snickers-varieties-and-lays-cappuccino-chips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/snickers-varieties-and-lays-cappuccino-chips/</guid>
      <description>To celebrate the recent one year anniversary of our father/son Tumblr site, TheVCubeSolver and I teamed up to review an assortment of Snickers bars we found at CVS. And as a special bonus, we take a look at the trendy new Lays Cappuccino potato chips.
Enjoy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kryptonite Kandy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kryptonite-kandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kryptonite-kandy/</guid>
      <description>Another bonus retro review! TheVCubeSolver hits up Popcorn Papa and takes a look at some very green rock candy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taki&#39;s, Cane Sugar Soda Pops</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</guid>
      <description>This is an older review from TheVCubeSolver and I very much inspired by the hijinks of Brian Hammons and the gang over at Review the World. In it we take a look at a couple of different varieties of Taki&amp;rsquo;s chips and some cane sugar soda pops we picked up at the local coffee shop.
Oh, and you&amp;rsquo;ll notice I&amp;rsquo;m calling myself &amp;ldquo;Meeks, the Pedestrian&amp;rdquo;. Cause we were trying to have code names or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Houston Winter Open</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/houston-winter-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2014 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/houston-winter-open/</guid>
      <description>Footage from the Houston Winter Open speedcubing competition.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zapps Mega Review Part Three</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zapps-mega-review-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 23:05:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zapps-mega-review-part-3/</guid>
      <description>The third and final installment of the big Zapp&amp;rsquo;s Potato Chip sampler review, representing my first donation to the blog. I&amp;rsquo;d go on to send a couple more &amp;ldquo;care packs&amp;rdquo; which would feature in a huge percentage of Brian&amp;rsquo;s output during 2014 and 2015, something of which I&amp;rsquo;m quite proud.
Highlights of this video include some of Brian&amp;rsquo;s prettier cinemagraphic work and Chris making a joke about his &amp;ldquo;bulge&amp;rdquo;.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</guid>
      <description>Back in the summer of 2013 TheVCubeSolver and I dropped by the local candy shop to review Blue Bunny&amp;rsquo;s Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes, a push-pop like product in three weird flavors. It turned out to be a complete and total sensory experience.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zapps Mega Review Part Two</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zapps-mega-review-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 22:47:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zapps-mega-review-part-2/</guid>
      <description>The second in Brian&amp;rsquo;s Zapp&amp;rsquo;s Potato Chip review trilogy, in which the boys puzzle over Voodoo flavoring and Nick gets sick on pickle chips.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zyka Indian Food Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zyka-indian-food-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zyka-indian-food-review/</guid>
      <description>I review some Indian food from my car.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zapps Mega Review Part One</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zapps-mega-review-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2014 22:28:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zapps-mega-review-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I got to know Brian in 2013 after becoming a fan of his blog, reviewtheworld.com. Toward the end of that year I sent him the first of what I would come to call &amp;ldquo;care packs&amp;rdquo; for the show — just donated items for potential review on the site. That particular pack was a huge sampler of Zapps potato chips, a Louisiana snack of which I am quite fond. It took about six months for him to feature the first video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get in the Trunk Part 3</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/get-in-the-trunk-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2013 22:16:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/get-in-the-trunk-part-3/</guid>
      <description>My first shout-out on Review the World was in this little vignette, now a classic in the RtW cinematic universe, in which &amp;ldquo;Toby&amp;rdquo; is the name of Chris&amp;rsquo;s ex-girlfriend.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>