<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Television on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</title>
    <link>https://tobyblog.com/categories/television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Television on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2013-2025 Toby Marks</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tobyblog.com/categories/television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Golden Girls, Really?</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190514-golden-girls-really/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20190514-golden-girls-really/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First off, this. Nostalgia community, we need to have a deep and confronting conversation. It’s time to stop pretending you like The Golden Girls. Nobody but your grandma liked The Golden Girls, and that’s exactly as it should be. Your unnatural determination to make The Golden Girls a “thing” amongst thirty-something &lt;em&gt;males&lt;/em&gt; has led to this abomination, and it’s time we as a society put an end to this madness.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Andy Griffith Show and the evolution of TV sitcoms</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20180424-rap-songs-mention-andy-griffith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 20:37:11 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/microposts/20180424-rap-songs-mention-andy-griffith/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Andy Griffith Show is one of those rare cultural phenomena that have spanned generations and left an indelible mark on American pop culture. Deputy Barney Fife consistently ranks among the top tier of American television characters on all polls, placing at number five in The &lt;a href=&#34;http://articles.chicagotribune.com/1995-12-06/features/9512060169_1_lucy-ricardo-ted-baxter-tv-characters&#34;&gt;Chicago Tribune&amp;rsquo;s list of the top 25&lt;/a&gt; of all time. (I would enthusiastically dispute that either Eddie Haskell or Ed Norton belong on that list above him.) Not only are the characters still beloved and recognizable more than fifty years on from their debut on the small screen, but the whole fictional world of Mayberry has transcended that medium to become a part of the national mythology — a kind of idyllic (and idealized) portrait of the last days of small town life in post-war America.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
