<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pop music on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/pop-music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pop music on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/pop-music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — Love Songs</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-love-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-love-songs/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time once again for one of my patented YouTube cover battles, and in typical fashion you pick the winner. Tonight&amp;rsquo;s theme is one of my favorite for YouTube covers — LOVE SONGS. I have my personal favorite, of course, but I won&amp;rsquo;t spoil it for you. Enjoy, and leave a comment to vote for the winner.
The first track is by Goga, a local (Dallas) wedding singer and one-man-band act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — Red Rubber Ball</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140724-cover-battle-red-rubber-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140724-cover-battle-red-rubber-ball/</guid>
      <description>I woke up this morning with this song stuck in my head, thinking about my dad and the good progress he&amp;rsquo;s making recovering from a triple bypass operation.
I probably thought of it because I noticed it was in the repertoire of local musician Bruce Wilder, who graced us at the coffee shop one evening with his guitar.
  Here are my three favorite YouTube covers of this 1966 song by Paul Simon and Bruce Woodley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baker Street</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140721-baker-street/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20140721-baker-street/</guid>
      <description>Love this song. Local musician Bruce Wilder was recently performing it solo at Firewheel Coffee, my office away from the office. Makes me want to sneak up behind him with a giant saxophone and start blaring away at the appropriate moments.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
