<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>horror on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/horror/</link>
    <description>Recent content in horror on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 13:41:27 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/horror/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Carrey in The Shining</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/jim-carrey-stars-in-the-shining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 13:41:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/jim-carrey-stars-in-the-shining/</guid>
      <description>Deepfake. I would have preferred this use his Ace Ventura voice, but I guess the AI isn&amp;rsquo;t up to that (yet).
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Sick</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-03-28-so-sick/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 22:46:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-03-28-so-sick/</guid>
      <description>Being sick on a trip is the worst. I&amp;rsquo;ve mostly been sleeping every spare moment I get. Managed to catch a pretty decent cheese ball of a movie, though. It was old school campy fun in the best way. Nicely captured the feel of old 80s schlock-horror movies like The Gate and Return of the Living Dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sfanthor! House of Wax</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/sfanthor-house-of-wax/</guid>
      <description>Here in North Texas the sun is shining. The weather is warming up. The world outside is getting brighter. The Texas wildflowers are already in bloom, thanks to a mild and soggy winter. In the woods, things are moving. The itchy season is upon us, and the window of opportunity for a lot of local geocaches is closing, as the casual players tend to steer clear of anything that might put them in the way of tall grass, poison ivy, or the dreaded tick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Hour - Best Haunt Ever!</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-dark-hour-best-haunt-ever/</guid>
      <description>I discovered The Dark Hour in March, at St. Patrick&#39;s Day of all times, and I fell in love. I don&#39;t have the skills to work there, but I think if I could just secretly sneak in and live there, I would. I&#39;d be like that weird guy from the movies who lives between the walls somehow, and you hear him rummaging around in the fridge at night. Just hope I don&#39;t get caught!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screening Phantasm With The Tall Man</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/screening-phantasm-with-the-tall-man/</guid>
      <description>From a respectful write-up on Texas Frightmare Weekend by Dread Central:
Can we stop calling Texas Frightmare Weekend a “regional con” now? The first reader I met this year was Aaron from Australia, who had flown all the way here to experience TFW as his FIRST con.
I met that guy! Twice. Sat right next to him at the special 35mm screening of Phantasm at the Alamo Draft House in Richardson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Visit to Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2015 14:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/a-visit-to-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Channard from Hellraiser II, in all his glory
  Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt is a boutique shop in Dallas specializing in horror and sci-fi collectibles, memorabilia, paraphernalia, and… well, you just gotta see it, folks. It&amp;rsquo;s an amazing place. I discovered them only recently after attending the St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Slay Weekend event at Dark Hour Haunted House in Plano. They were a sponsor of that particular show, so Dark Hour graciously gave them some floor space to sell a few wares after the show and otherwise promote the store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mask of the Red Death</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-mask-of-the-red-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2014 06:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-mask-of-the-red-death/</guid>
      <description>&#34;The &#39;Red Death&#39; had long devastated the country. No pestilence had ever been so fatal, or so hideous. Blood was its Avatar and its seal — the redness and the horror of blood. There were sharp pains, and sudden dizziness, and then profuse bleeding at the pores, with dissolution.&#34;&#34;With such precautions the courtiers might bid defiance to contagion. The external world could take care of itself.&#34;&#34;All these and security were within.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>