<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>covers on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/covers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in covers on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 23:07:28 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/covers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I Can&#39;t Get Over This Cover Album</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-20-bird-and-the-bee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 23:07:28 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2019-02-20-bird-and-the-bee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I discovered the The Bird and Bee this past December when I heard their rendition of &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/2018-12-21-my-favorite-christmas-songs/&#34;&gt;The Twelve Days of Christmas&lt;/a&gt; at a bar in Honolulu. That led me to this album, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been burning it up lately on drives and at work.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/V7rExwCkRYI&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s total ear candy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — The Great Pumpkin Waltz</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-the-great-pumpkin-waltz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-the-great-pumpkin-waltz/</guid>
      <description>We are officially in the &amp;ldquo;-BER months&amp;rdquo; now, a time of year that for my generation is indelibly stamped by the melancholy Peanuts cartoon soundtracks of Vince Guiraldi and his trio. Though the nostalgic quality of these tracks reaches fever pitch around Christmastime, we begin our seasonal contemplation with this wistful little tune, quickly supplanted in the Guiraldi lineup, but never quite forgotten. It remains one of my favorites, but I&amp;rsquo;ll only listen to it from the start of September through Halloween.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — Love Songs</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-love-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-love-songs/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s time once again for one of my patented YouTube cover battles, and in typical fashion you pick the winner. Tonight&amp;rsquo;s theme is one of my favorite for YouTube covers — LOVE SONGS. I have my personal favorite, of course, but I won&amp;rsquo;t spoil it for you. Enjoy, and leave a comment to vote for the winner. The first track is by Goga, a local (Dallas) wedding singer and one-man-band act.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Battle — Red Rubber Ball</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-red-rubber-ball/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cover-battle-red-rubber-ball/</guid>
      <description>I woke up this morning with this song stuck in my head, thinking about my dad and the good progress he&amp;rsquo;s making recovering from a triple bypass operation.
I probably thought of it because I noticed it was in the repertoire of local musician Bruce Wilder, who graced us at the coffee shop one evening with his guitar.
  Here are my three favorite YouTube covers of this 1966 song by Paul Simon and Bruce Woodley.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>