<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</title>
    <link>https://tobyblog.com/categories/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on ~ The Tobyblog 📝</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2024 (c) Toby Marks</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 10:59:53 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tobyblog.com/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Desert Tornado</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/tumbleweed-tornado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 10:59:53 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/tumbleweed-tornado/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I thought this was kind of neat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jim Carrey in The Shining</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/jim-carrey-stars-in-the-shining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 13:41:27 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/jim-carrey-stars-in-the-shining/</guid>
      <description>Deepfake. I would have preferred this use his Ace Ventura voice, but I guess the AI isn&amp;rsquo;t up to that (yet).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Subtle Subversion of Hating Nazis</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/the-subtle-subversion-of-nazi-hatred/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 09:50:49 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/the-subtle-subversion-of-nazi-hatred/</guid>
      <description>It’s not a contest but every generation has to confront its own evil because there is something deeply wrong with human beings.&#xA;The reason for the existence of shows like Hunters is the same reason why Godwin had to come up with his &amp;ldquo;Law.&amp;rdquo; And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to do with the laziness of screenwriters, though that does play into it. In the absence of religious faith Hitler and the Nazis have taken the place of the devil in our collective mythology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Windows of Our Isolation</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/windows-of-our-isolation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 09:49:49 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/windows-of-our-isolation/</guid>
      <description>Since the coronavirus started spreading, our little computer and phone cameras have become the windows of our isolation, looking into other people’s lives, catching glimpses of pets, children, and spouses in the background of video calls. I find these moments deeply humanizing; reminders that we’re not perfect work machines, just people trying to do the best we can. Our hair is messy, our faces poorly framed and lit. Sometimes we leave the mic on when we go to the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Expensive Font in the World</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/most-expensive-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 16:00:36 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/most-expensive-font/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s because it takes a lot of powerful tech to bend that slant backwards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isolate The Right Way in a Treehouse Hotel</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/treehouse-hotels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 09:34:35 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/treehouse-hotels/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re not waiting out the apocalypse in a treehouse hotel, you&amp;rsquo;re not doing it right. Most of these are in exotic spots around the world, but there happens to be one nearby in Eureka Springs! And very affordable, too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cleverest Life Hack</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/clever-life-hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:02:11 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/clever-life-hack/</guid>
      <description>Wait, just hear me out on this…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slayer, Striker, Shooter and the Rise of the Extreme Baby Boy Name</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/extreme-boys-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 15:35:40 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/extreme-boys-names/</guid>
      <description>In a recent Namerology article on the topic, she lists several of the burlier, more aggressive names that have been picking up steam: Angler, Camper, Tracker, Trapper, Catcher, Driver, Fielder, Racer, Sailor, Striker, Wheeler — deep breath — Breaker, Roper, Trotter, Wrangler — still going — Lancer, Shooter, Slayer, Soldier, Tracer, Trooper — wait, “Slayer”? — Blazer, Brewer, Charger, Dodger, Laker, Pacer, Packer, Raider, Ranger, Steeler, Warrior — kill me — Dreamer, Jester and — wait for it — Rocker.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Intelligence of Corvids</title>
      <link>https://tobyblog.com/posts/crows-are-pretty-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 14:26:52 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://tobyblog.com/posts/crows-are-pretty-smart/</guid>
      <description>Crows, in fact, might be like us not so much because they are clever (and so are we) but rather because they sometimes engage their cleverness simply for fun – and so do we.&#xA;What&amp;rsquo;s it like to be a crow? What do they make of us? Are animals capable of moral behavior? Having been a pet owner for many years I think this is true. I feel I&amp;rsquo;ve observed it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
