<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/categories/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 10:59:53 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Desert Tornado</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tumbleweed-tornado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 10:59:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/tumbleweed-tornado/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I thought this was kind of neat.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jim Carrey in The Shining</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/jim-carrey-stars-in-the-shining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 13:41:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/jim-carrey-stars-in-the-shining/</guid>
      <description>Deepfake. I would have preferred this use his Ace Ventura voice, but I guess the AI isn&amp;rsquo;t up to that (yet).
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Subtle Subversion of Hating Nazis</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-subtle-subversion-of-nazi-hatred/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 09:50:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-subtle-subversion-of-nazi-hatred/</guid>
      <description>It’s not a contest but every generation has to confront its own evil because there is something deeply wrong with human beings.
 The reason for the existence of shows like Hunters is the same reason why Godwin had to come up with his &amp;ldquo;Law.&amp;quot; And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to do with the laziness of screenwriters, though that does play into it. In the absence of religious faith Hitler and the Nazis have taken the place of the devil in our collective mythology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Windows of Our Isolation</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/windows-of-our-isolation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 09:49:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/windows-of-our-isolation/</guid>
      <description>Since the coronavirus started spreading, our little computer and phone cameras have become the windows of our isolation, looking into other people’s lives, catching glimpses of pets, children, and spouses in the background of video calls. I find these moments deeply humanizing; reminders that we’re not perfect work machines, just people trying to do the best we can. Our hair is messy, our faces poorly framed and lit. Sometimes we leave the mic on when we go to the bathroom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Expensive Font in the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/most-expensive-font/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 16:00:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/most-expensive-font/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s because it takes a lot of powerful tech to bend that slant backwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isolate The Right Way in a Treehouse Hotel</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/treehouse-hotels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 09:34:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/treehouse-hotels/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re not waiting out the apocalypse in a treehouse hotel, you&amp;rsquo;re not doing it right. Most of these are in exotic spots around the world, but there happens to be one nearby in Eureka Springs! And very affordable, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cleverest Life Hack</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/clever-life-hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:02:11 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/clever-life-hack/</guid>
      <description>Wait, just hear me out on this…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slayer, Striker, Shooter and the Rise of the Extreme Baby Boy Name</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/extreme-boys-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 15:35:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/extreme-boys-names/</guid>
      <description>In a recent Namerology article on the topic, she lists several of the burlier, more aggressive names that have been picking up steam: Angler, Camper, Tracker, Trapper, Catcher, Driver, Fielder, Racer, Sailor, Striker, Wheeler — deep breath — Breaker, Roper, Trotter, Wrangler — still going — Lancer, Shooter, Slayer, Soldier, Tracer, Trooper — wait, “Slayer”? — Blazer, Brewer, Charger, Dodger, Laker, Pacer, Packer, Raider, Ranger, Steeler, Warrior — kill me — Dreamer, Jester and — wait for it — Rocker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Intelligence of Corvids</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/crows-are-pretty-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 14:26:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/crows-are-pretty-smart/</guid>
      <description>Crows, in fact, might be like us not so much because they are clever (and so are we) but rather because they sometimes engage their cleverness simply for fun – and so do we.
 What&amp;rsquo;s it like to be a crow? What do they make of us? Are animals capable of moral behavior? Having been a pet owner for many years I think this is true. I feel I&amp;rsquo;ve observed it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fight For Baby Tinslee</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-fight-for-baby-tinslee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-fight-for-baby-tinslee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1573679128/img/2C1366D7-67E3-4A28-996C-A7B2474B672D_kalzqo.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I got to tag along recently to an impromptu press conference called at Cook Children&amp;rsquo;s Medical Center in Ft. Worth by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.texasrighttolife.com&#34;&gt;Texas Right to Life&lt;/a&gt; — you can &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.texasrighttolife.com/urgent-cook-childrens-to-pull-plug-on-9-month-baby/&#34;&gt;read about the unfortunate circumstances here&lt;/a&gt;. We were expecting Kassi to speak to the legal issues involved, but she wasn&amp;rsquo;t questioned at that time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slavoj Zizek on The Joker</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/zizek-on-joker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 18:03:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/zizek-on-joker/</guid>
      <description>He&amp;rsquo;s not a fan of the new Joker, though he greatly admires Nolan&amp;rsquo;s version.
 The truth is in your mask. The truth is in what you are doing.
 Interesting take.
 Paradoxically, a mask means I can be who I really am.
 His point, based in some psychological theory, is that our plain faces are the real masks; that in our normal lives we artificially conform ourselves because of social convention, expectations, etc; but that &amp;ldquo;our mask&amp;rdquo; allows us to break out of those restrictions, inviting the true self – the inner or even unconscious self – to emerge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hermione&#39;s Spiel</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/emma-watson-spiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 15:26:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/emma-watson-spiel/</guid>
      <description>She went on: “I never believed the whole ‘I’m happy single’ spiel. I was like, ‘This is totally spiel.’ It took me a long time, but I’m very happy [being single]. I call it being self-partnered.”
 The only story here is how much Emma Watson uses the Hollywood word spiel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A History of the Puffy Toilet Seat</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/puffy-toilet-seats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 11:16:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/puffy-toilet-seats/</guid>
      <description>I always considered those things the grossest of the gross. But did get me thinking about alternative &amp;ldquo;comfortable&amp;rdquo; materials. A gel toilet seat? Cushion of air? Water? Yeah, like a water bed — but instead it&amp;rsquo;s a toilet seat.
And if you don&amp;rsquo;t already follow the bro-science blog of Dollar Shave Club, you should. Way better than The Onion these days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COPS: Flushing Drugs Could Create “Meth-Gators”</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cops-flushing-drugs-could-create-meth-gators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/cops-flushing-drugs-could-create-meth-gators/</guid>
      <description>The Alabama Meth-Gators is my new favorite college football team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Ants Like Coffee?</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/ants-harvest-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 09:55:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/ants-harvest-coffee/</guid>
      <description>🐜❤️☕️
Ants are my favorite insect. That they have actually been observed to plant coffee seeds, live in and among the plants they grow, and actually harvest the beans floors me with wonder for these remarkable creatures that are so different from us, yet so much resemble us in our social behaviors. This is real agriculture; and we already know they practice ranching and husbandry behaviors, with aphids for example — &amp;ldquo;milking&amp;rdquo; them of the dew produced by their bodies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
