<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photolog on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/photolog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photolog on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:49:48 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/photolog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Halloween &amp; Hauntfest Convention</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-04-08-halloween-hauntfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 13:49:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018-04-08-halloween-hauntfest/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4339/36452811210_3a1f348349_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017, by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Toby Marks&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/36452811210/&#34; title=&#34;Halloween and Hauntfest 2017&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


Normally scheduled in late August, the &lt;a href=&#34;http://halloweenandhaunt.com/&#34; title=&#34;The Halloween &amp;amp; Hauntfest Show&#34;&gt;Halloween &amp;amp; Hauntfest show&lt;/a&gt; is appropriately billed as &amp;ldquo;a gateway event to the Halloween season.&amp;rdquo; To those of us who kick off our official celebrations with the start of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dinosaurdracula.com/&#34;&gt;Dinosaur Dracula&amp;rsquo;s Halloween Countdown&lt;/a&gt; on September 1, the timing hits that perfect sweet spot. The anticipation, that period of time I like to call &amp;ldquo;the run-up to the countdown&amp;rdquo;, starts to build throughout August, so that by the time this event rolls around Kassi and the kids and I are practically bursting with Halloween excitement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Year in Pictures — 2017 Edition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017-12-31-top-nine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017-12-31-top-nine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/2017-12-31-top-nine/top9.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of my favorite pictures from the past year. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/75738497@N00/sets/72157688929748362&#34;&gt;See the full set on Flickr.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smells Like Halloween at Yankee Candle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017-09-04-yankee-candle-halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 09:41:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017-09-04-yankee-candle-halloween/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

    &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4422/36040105263_67f5b87dbe_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Window advert&#34;&gt;
    &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Window advert, by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Toby Marks&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/36040105263/&#34; title=&#34;Window advert&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


What&amp;rsquo;s in a smell? The power to evoke. Memories. People. Places. And special times in our lives. Seasons long forgotten. All brought back in an instant the second a particular aroma hits our nostrils. It&amp;rsquo;s no wonder that scented candles, long thought domain of grandmas and boring little gift shops, have become respected among the nostalgia set in recent years. I read once that people don&amp;rsquo;t remember scents; that you remember the things associated with it or the strong feelings the scent creates, but the brain does not store memory of the scent itself. And now I find myself trying to remember what the woods smell like in autumn.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lights Out For Collector&#39;s Crypt</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lights-out-for-collectors-crypt/</guid>
      <description>#pic { display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; }   Do you remember Collector&amp;rsquo;s Crypt? I wrote about that place around this time last year. It&amp;rsquo;s closed now. I had a dream about it the other night, or rather its next incarnation, which was as a hybrid Christmas/Halloween store. I know the owners have an interest in Christmas things, so that detail is not too surprising. But in my dream, there was also a functional toilet over by the register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diana Levin&#39;s Pocket Watch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-levins-pocket-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/diana-levins-pocket-watch/</guid>
      <description>While in attendance at Texas Frightmare Weekend I picked up a small pocket watch as a souvenir for my daughter from the booth of Diana Levin. Check out her gallery on her website. Or better yet, if you like what you see you can buy something from her Etsy store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Year in Pictures</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-year-in-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-year-in-pictures/</guid>
      <description>Being a fan of post-Christmas year end wrap-ups, I decided to create a Flickr set highlighting some of the events and activities that filled our lives this year. These are not my best photos or even my favorites, but just a (largish) collection of pictures that capture the essence of 2014 for me. A little bit of countryside, a little bit of life at home. One or two guest appearances. Flowers and ponies and monsters and toys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Los Dias De Los Muertos at World Market</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 07:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/los-dias-de-los-muertos-at-world-market/</guid>
      <description>Already a great place to find exotic candies, foreign soda pop, and specialty food items at any time of the year (Brian Hammons, you know what I&amp;rsquo;m talking about), World Market really comes alive for Halloween. If you&amp;rsquo;ve got one in your area, get down there right now and check their selection. The stuff they carry is definitely outside of the Target/Big Lots/Dollar Store Halloween mold, but that&amp;rsquo;s not to say it&amp;rsquo;s super expensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween at Big Lots</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/halloween-at-big-lots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2014 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/halloween-at-big-lots/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, friends! It&amp;rsquo;s been a few days since my last update, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t been idle. Have you noticed how early the stores are stocking for Halloween this year? I blogged about my first sighting at At Home&amp;nbsp;(formerly Garden Ridge)&amp;nbsp;which was on July 1st, a full one month earlier than last year. (And if you&amp;rsquo;re interested, that was at a chain called Home Goods, where the theme of ravens &amp;amp; blackbirds predominated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yankee Candle Halloween Preview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 13:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/yankee-candle-halloween-preview/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yankee Candle had a special one-day preview of their upcoming Halloween 2014 collection, and we dropped in to get a look. Thanks to @PerkyJewels #FF for the tip-off!


Tragically, most of the &#34;Bonies&#34; decorations were sold out by the time we got there. We were told by staff that most of the merchandise was gone within the first half-hour of the store opening, so that should show you the amazing pent-up demand for Halloween this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wylie&#39;s Angel</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/wylies-angel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 23:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/wylies-angel/</guid>
      <description>I like geocaching for lots of reasons. I like to be outside. I like discovering new places. I like&amp;nbsp;walking and connecting with nature. But occasionally I learn something as well. Usually it&amp;rsquo;s just local historical trivia, or maybe a&amp;nbsp;geography&amp;nbsp;lesson. But sometimes the lesson is more personal, and as in this case, tragic.
The morning started out with a trip to the Trinity Trails in Wylie, Texas for some hiking and caching.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOUND OBJECTS: A PHOTOLOG OF GEOCACHING SWAGARTICLE I EVIL ZOMBIE CLOWN</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/found-objects-a-photolog-of-geocaching-swagarticle-i-evil-zombie-clown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2014 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/found-objects-a-photolog-of-geocaching-swagarticle-i-evil-zombie-clown/</guid>
      <description>I have no particular fear of clowns. I am not one of those people. But this thing gives me the creeps. Downright turns my stomach. 
I found it in an ammo can in a small copse of woods near the office, nestled among a collection of unremarkable trinkets. It&amp;rsquo;s only about an inch or so high, so it took me a second to realize that it carries in its left hand a severed human arm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>