<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dino Drac Funpack on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/dino-drac-funpack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dino Drac Funpack on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 19:09:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/dino-drac-funpack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Mega Fun Pack</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/super-mega-fun-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/super-mega-fun-pack/</guid>
      <description>The Super Mega Fun Pack geocache (GC5Z4X7) is a thinly-veiled tribute to Matt of dinosaurdracula.com and the amazing box of goodies that he puts together every month for his hordes of devoted fans. It&amp;rsquo;s only &amp;ldquo;veiled&amp;rdquo; at all because of the (understandable) policy of geocaching.com not to list any cache with references to commercial products. After going back and forth with them a bit about this, I relented and removed any overt references to Matt or his website, including changing the name of the cache from the original &amp;ldquo;The Dino Drac Fun Pack Geocache&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;Super Mega Fun Pack&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Dino Drac Funpack, Sep 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-sep-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-sep-2014/</guid>
      <description>September has arrived, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to open another funpack from Dinosaur Dracula!

Most of you may already recognize Dinosaur Dracula as the preeminent nostalgia blog on the web. (If not, you may recall its previous incarnation, X-Entertainment) Matt, the guy that runs the site, puts on quite a show every year for the Halloween season, and I must say 2014 is already off to a great start! Watching his videos and reading his reviews has become sort of a Halloween tradition in our family, something we look forward to every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Dino Drac Funpack, Aug 2014</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-aug-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2014 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/opening-the-dino-drac-funpack-aug-2014/</guid>
      <description>Most of you may already recognize&amp;nbsp;Dinosaur Dracula&amp;nbsp;as the preeminent nostalgia blog on the web. (If not, you may recall its previous incarnation,&amp;nbsp;X-Entertainment) Matt, the guy that runs the site, puts on quite a show every year for the Halloween season, and I must say 2014 is already off to a great start! Watching his videos and reading his reviews has become sort of a Halloween tradition in our family, something we look forward to every year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>