<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reviews on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/tags/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reviews on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/tags/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Three New Pasadena Restaurants </title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/three-new-pasadena-restaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/three-new-pasadena-restaurants/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1555717674/img/ABB60CD5-A457-4710-A103-8E22A15D25DC.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have decided that when presented with a choice between the familiar and the new, I am going to lean in favor of new experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cajun Treats</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/cajun-treats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 21:58:19 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/cajun-treats/</guid>
      <description>This video is something of a personal achievement, having been now just under two years in the making, and passing, as it does, yet another milestone in the revitalization of this little blog. Yeah, I know, that&amp;rsquo;s sort of a grandiose way to introduce a video where I discuss the merits of quail eggs and potato chips with friends and family, but there we are. It means something to me — hard to quantify — to be active on the site again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Libre</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-libre/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-libre/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1552629476/img/576933C9-5E92-4C23-B1AF-8B342EF82BDF.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weather was warmer today. I could feel spring in my bones. I get that way around this time of year. Maybe I was feeling a little homesick. Whatever the case, I&amp;rsquo;ve been craving Mexican food. I noticed this little while walking around during my lunch break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I was standing outside the door reading the posted menuboard, an older lady passing by said to me &amp;ldquo;Go in. You&amp;rsquo;ll like it. It&amp;rsquo;s really good.&amp;rdquo; I took that as a sign.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Times at the El Portal</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/el-portal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 22:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/el-portal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://res.cloudinary.com/tobyblog/image/upload/v1552625591/img/761E75E1-8A2E-4D98-9348-5951E7436215.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took a detour that night after my trip to the antique store. I passed along back streets, out of the way plazas, anywhere that looked like it might afford me new scenery. I stumbled across El Portal behind the headquarters of the Planetary Society, its aromas drawing my attention before I&amp;rsquo;d even rounded the corner to lay site on the place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Latte Beer and Ace Pumpkin Cider</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-11-24-pumpkin-latte-ace-pumpkin-cider/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 10:49:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/2017-11-24-pumpkin-latte-ace-pumpkin-cider/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-caption alignnone&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://farm5.staticflickr.com/4580/38604886832_7bc4b06488_z.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Coffee, Pumpkin Pie, and Pumpkin Latte Beer&#34;&gt;
  &lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-caption-text&#34;&gt;Coffee, Pumpkin Pie, and Pumpkin Latte Beer — Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/&#34;&gt;Tobyblog&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.flickr.com/photos/tobyjmarks/38604886832/&#34; title=&#34;Coffee, Pumpkin Pie, and Pumpkin Latte Beer&#34;&gt;Flickr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;


This year while out shopping for turkey and wine, I discovered a couple of very fallish, and very Thanksgiving-appropriate beverages I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share with you all. One is a new seasonal coffee brew from my favorite DFW brewery &lt;a href=&#34;http://martinhousebrewing.com/&#34;&gt;Martin House&lt;/a&gt;, and the other is a special cider I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in three years — &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/&#34;&gt;Ace&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/a&gt; own extraordinary Pumpkin Cider. Read on!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cauldron Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 19:53:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-10-29-cauldron-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Joined once again by nostalgia blogger and good friend Brian Hammons of reviewtheworld.com, Augie and I team up to complete our trilogy of Skittles reviews, this time looking at the legendary and rarely sighted Cauldron Skittles variety, now in its second year on store shelves. Does the candy itself live up to the promise of its bright orange bag? We find out, and the answer may just shock you. (It probably won&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brightside Skittles with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 15:21:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/2017-09-09-brightside-skittles/</guid>
      <description>Join me, Augie, and superpal Brian of Review the World for installment number two in this soon to be classic trilogy of Skittles candy reviews. This time we look at Brightside Skittles, the very flipside of the Darkside reviewed a couple of years back with Brian on his last visit to Dallas. A great theme for summer and sunny days, will Brightside warm your tummy as we slip into fall and all things pumpkin spice?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America Skittles Review with Brian</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 23:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/america-skittles-review/</guid>
      <description>Hello again, folks.
It has been a while now since I&amp;rsquo;ve been active on this site, but life has not held still for me and the family. Since the last time I posted anything of significance, quite a great deal has happened, actually, much of which was originally destined for publication here. Well, as it does, life got in the way, priorities shifted, my free time diminished, etc. etc. — and the gist of it all is that you folks were left unattended for many months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Review the World Episodes of 2015-2016</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/top-10-review-the-world-episodes-of-2015-2016/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again folks, that magical time between Christmas and New Year where thoughtful commentators like myself come out with their end of year retrospectives; and continuing a tradition I established a couple of years back on this site, I intend to give you my take on the best of my buddy Brian Hammons&amp;rsquo; output over on the internet&amp;rsquo;s most beloved nostalgia blog, ReviewTheWorld.com.
You can catch up on previous years&amp;rsquo; content by taking a look at my other lists:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bollywood Burrito</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-bollywood-burrito/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-bollywood-burrito/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-Sq3xak90kZg/V6zwoaw0I7I/AAAAAAAAC40/evK2MCidSAEDtEYEMePNyQVFAWYgzkF1QCLcB/s640/IMG_5441.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember Taco Naan, the Mexican-Indian hybrid restaurant &lt;a href=&#34;http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/&#34;&gt;I wrote about&lt;/a&gt; a long time back? I&amp;rsquo;m talking about the very same one my buddy &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reviewtheworld.com/2015/03/texas-taco-challenge-taco-naan-vs-fuel.html&#34;&gt;Brian featured&lt;/a&gt; on his second trip to the Big D, where he stacked up its offerings against the nationally renowned taco dive Fuel City. Well, they&amp;rsquo;re still around and busier and better than ever! The place is expanding like mad, doubling its interior floor space and hopefully renovating those dismal restrooms. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know because I&amp;rsquo;ve never had the courage to try them again. But you don&amp;rsquo;t go to Taco Naan to use the bathroom, man, so no worries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Czech Stop and Slovaceks</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-czech-stop-and-slovaceks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2016 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-czech-stop-and-slovaceks/</guid>
      <description>After a long hiatus, my front seat food review series is back! This time I feature some of the Waco area&amp;rsquo;s finest gas station Czech cuisine. If you&amp;rsquo;re ever in the area you should absolutely stop at one or both of these fine establishments. Such a treat.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Pineapple Cider &amp; Shannon Irish Red</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/ace-pineapple-cider-shannon-irish-red/</guid>
      <description>Beer is great year-round, but summer brings its own varieties. I noticed recently that hard ciders are becoming more popular. I had a chance to sample a new one from Ace, makers of an outstanding pumpkin cider that I am very much looking forward to having again this fall. Their pear cider, available in all seasons, merits a future review. But this one I had not seen before.
Indeed, it called out to me from the shelf with unabashed summery fruitiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tobyblog Thanksgiving Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-thanksgiving-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-thanksgiving-special/</guid>
      <description>After taking some time off to contemplate the overwhelming success of my Burger King poop tweet*, we now return to our regularly scheduled programming.
In truth October is always a busy month for us and I don&amp;rsquo;t have much spare time for blogging. This past Halloween was without a doubt the best yet, but I&amp;rsquo;ll save that retrospective for another day. For today we find ourselves at the end of November, as grand a month as any.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sprechers Root Beer Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2015 09:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/sprechers-root-beer-review/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating our third anniversary of Buddy Team reviews, TheVCubeSolver and I team up to tackle the legendary Sprechers Root Beer. It&amp;rsquo;s good stuff!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kranky Coffee</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kranky-coffee/</guid>
      <description>Straight off a Dollar Store shelf at the lovely Grapevine Mills Mall in Grapevine, Texas, and stocked just a few bins over from the storied Orchard Skittles, comes Kranky Candy, the coffee dusted confection you will soon come to know and love. Is it an afternoon snack? A breakfast substitute? Repurposed industrial by-product? You decide.
Joining me in his first proper appearance* on Tobyblog is my good friend Brian Hammons of ReviewTheWorld.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noshing Tacos with Review the World</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/noshing-tacos-with-review-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/noshing-tacos-with-review-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Once again we were proud to host buddy Brian Hammons of the food/candy/retro/life blog Review the World as he made his way down to Dallas for the big UFC 185 fight night. What a weekend! Among other things, I introduced Brian Hammons to some of the best tacos in the COUNTRY. Go see what resulted over on reviewtheworld.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Chix Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-chix-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/super-chix-review/</guid>
      <description>We have reached &#34;Peak Blogger&#34; in this society, folks. If the existence of Tobyblog was not proof of that already, take a look at the above picture. It was a cold, blustery Saturday afternoon and I was visiting nearby Arlington. It was around lunchtime and I had some time to kill, so I decided to walk over to the nearby strip mall and scope out the restaurants. There were a surprising number of cuisines on offer for such a small area, but this place caught my eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review the World Comes to Dallas</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2014 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/review-the-world-comes-to-dallas/</guid>
      <description>Those of you paying close attention&amp;nbsp;will remember that Tobyblog owes its existence to my good buddy Brian Hammons of the nostalgia blog&amp;nbsp;reviewtheworld.com. His site is a surprisingly deep personal catalog that is as much a call to action and personal philosophical movement as anything. Brian has been at this game for far longer than YouTube has been around, and has amassed an unparalleled amount of footage and articles documenting the greater part of his life, from high school hijinks to romances come and gone, to thirty-something introspections with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tobyblog Halloween Special</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-halloween-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/the-tobyblog-halloween-special/</guid>
      <description>I love Halloween. You do, too. This video is a tribute to that season, to every memory and every thrill. To cold autumn nights. To the warm glow of jack o&amp;rsquo; lanterns. To spooky stories and cozy evenings. To every bit of magic and adventure in our lives.
This is the story of Halloween 2013 as we experienced it; what has gone down in our lives and memories as THE BEST HALLOWEEN EVER.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liver and Gizzards Review, with Sriracha Whoopie Pies</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/liver-and-gizzards-review-with-sriracha-whoopie-pies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2014 15:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/liver-and-gizzards-review-with-sriracha-whoopie-pies/</guid>
      <description>My buddy Brian Hammons over at Review the World requested another video food review, so I though I&amp;rsquo;d introduce him to a down-home treat from my childhood. I hope you&amp;rsquo;re happy with the results. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna lie, this one is a bit of a deep dive; a little something for my hardcore devotees. That is, people that like watching me eat stuff in my car. And yes, I manage to add yet another stain to my car seat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snickers Varieties and Lays Cappuccino Chips</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/snickers-varieties-and-lays-cappuccino-chips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2014 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/snickers-varieties-and-lays-cappuccino-chips/</guid>
      <description>To celebrate the recent one year anniversary of our father/son Tumblr site, TheVCubeSolver and I teamed up to review an assortment of Snickers bars we found at CVS. And as a special bonus, we take a look at the trendy new Lays Cappuccino potato chips.
Enjoy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Food Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/new-orleans-food-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/new-orleans-food-review/</guid>
      <description>New Orleans is, of course, a city known for its food, home to some of the best chefs in the country. I was in town recently, so I figured I&amp;rsquo;d check out some of the local establishments and give you guys a virtual sight-tasting tour. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the hotel vending machine.


Hey, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten all day and I had a couple of hours to kill till my family showed up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Toe 2 Toe&#34; Review: Chili Cheese Fries</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2014 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/toe-2-toe-review-chili-cheese-fries/</guid>
      <description>THE CONTENDERS:
Melter&amp;rsquo;s (Irving)
melty burgers and loaded baked potatoes14 year old native Dallas establishment2 locations, downtown Dallas &amp;amp; Irvinglow key atmosphere with an emphasis on the food vs.Burger Fi (Garland)upscale burgers and hot dogsFlorida chain with scores of locations around the country50s/60s diner aestheticthick, home-cut fries and real angus beef
MELTERS 
Melters&amp;rsquo; chili cheese fries were the first and, so far, only thing I&amp;rsquo;ve had off of their menu, but I&amp;rsquo;m already impressed with the place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kryptonite Kandy</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kryptonite-kandy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/kryptonite-kandy/</guid>
      <description>Another bonus retro review! TheVCubeSolver hits up Popcorn Papa and takes a look at some very green rock candy.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taki&#39;s, Cane Sugar Soda Pops</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2014 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/takis-cane-sugar-soda-pops/</guid>
      <description>This is an older review from TheVCubeSolver and I very much inspired by the hijinks of Brian Hammons and the gang over at Review the World. In it we take a look at a couple of different varieties of Taki&amp;rsquo;s chips and some cane sugar soda pops we picked up at the local coffee shop.
Oh, and you&amp;rsquo;ll notice I&amp;rsquo;m calling myself &amp;ldquo;Meeks, the Pedestrian&amp;rdquo;. Cause we were trying to have code names or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taco Naan Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/taco-naan-review/</guid>
      <description>Go back, right now, and take a look at my Zyka India Food restaurant review. Notice anything suspicious about the Chicken 65? Take a closer look at those ingredients. 

Jalapenos. Onions. Cilantro. Sound familiar? 
If you&amp;rsquo;re from Texas or anywhere in the Southwest you would immediately associate that combination with Mexican or Tex-Mex cuisine. There are other similarities, too, like the general spiciness, the use of chilis, or the penchant for using circular flatbread at every meal to sandwich ingredients and sop up sauces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suncreek Park - More Than Meets The Eye</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/suncreek-park-more-than-meets-the-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/suncreek-park-more-than-meets-the-eye/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks ago my wife told me about a new park she had discovered while killing time between a couple of the kids&amp;rsquo; classes. 
While climbing an overpass she caught site of some paved trails just off the road that interested her enough to want to Google it later. The trails turned out to be part of Suncreek Park in Allen, Texas. The website claims Suncreek sports only four tenths of a mile of paved trails, so it&amp;rsquo;s not much for walking, hiking, or biking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/jolly-rancher-cool-tubes-review/</guid>
      <description>Back in the summer of 2013 TheVCubeSolver and I dropped by the local candy shop to review Blue Bunny&amp;rsquo;s Jolly Rancher Cool Tubes, a push-pop like product in three weird flavors. It turned out to be a complete and total sensory experience.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zyka Indian Food Review</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zyka-indian-food-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2014 23:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/videos/zyka-indian-food-review/</guid>
      <description>I review some Indian food from my car.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>