<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photoblog on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/categories/photoblog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photoblog on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 16:36:14 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/categories/photoblog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Year in Pictures — 2020 Edition</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-year-in-pictures-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 16:36:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/the-year-in-pictures-2020/</guid>
      <description>This year was different.
News of the virus in China had already begun to circulate late last year. The videos and stories coming out of Wuhan were quite terrifying. People being welded into their apartments to prevent them from leaving. Bodies being secretly cremated en masse by the authorities. Sick people being burned alive. You have to wonder now if any of that had any basis in reality. I have come to distrust the news, both mainstream and alternative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corned Beef and Cabbage</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/corned-beef-and-cabbage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/corned-beef-and-cabbage/</guid>
      <description>A traditional Irish dinner. Corned beef and cabbage and Saldo. (Well maybe not that last bit&amp;hellip;)
Yes, it’s a cheat during Great Lent. But it’s also a long established family tradition. And St. Patrick is a special patron of ours.
For dessert, s’mores over the stove, as we missed our chance for brownies today, and I neglected to hoard ice cream during the quarantine. No matter, they were delicious.
Happy St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make a Wish</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/make-a-wish/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 18:18:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/make-a-wish/</guid>
      <description>Go ahead, now&amp;rsquo;s your chance.
It&amp;rsquo;s the season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Year in Pictures — 2019 Edition</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20191230-the-year-in-pictures-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 16:21:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/20191230-the-year-in-pictures-2019/</guid>
      <description>You have unlocked bonus content!
Welcome to this retroactively inserted yearly retrospective. The date I am writing this is actually December 30, 2020. If you&amp;rsquo;ve found this page, that means you&amp;rsquo;ve stumbled upon some content that, while genuinely old, was not originally posted on this date. Greetings from the future! Or something. I suppose I could make some joke right now warning you to &amp;ldquo;turn back&amp;rdquo; from the dread year 2020, but that whole bit seems tired and depressing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
