<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photoblog on Tobyblog</title>
    <link>http://tobyblog.com/categories/photoblog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photoblog on Tobyblog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 15:33:44 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://tobyblog.com/categories/photoblog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Faces</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/faces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 15:33:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/faces/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/48578600051_4fc9c2cd49_b.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time does take its toll on the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do you see when you look into a funhouse mirror? Another &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; staring out at you beneath the surface of the glass? &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maybe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; you are really just one of a whole army of such &amp;ldquo;you&amp;quot;s, none knowing for sure what side of the glass he falls on. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maybe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; the &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo; you are now is just another picture frozen in time; something separate and distinct from all your past and future selves. Always dying, always being born; every thought and action carving its mark forever into the lines of your face and body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now imagine an app on your phone that would let you peer into that funhouse — would let you see those possibilities, those infinite &amp;ldquo;you&amp;quot;s that could have been. That &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;will&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; be?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, particularly those possibilities that involve you growing a beard, dying your hair, looking like a douchebag, or getting really old.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crow at the Grand Canyon</title>
      <link>http://tobyblog.com/posts/grand-canyon-crow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 17:32:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tobyblog.com/posts/grand-canyon-crow/</guid>
      <description>Who&amp;rsquo;s ready for fall?
You can count me in, though I&amp;rsquo;m not sure &amp;ldquo;ready&amp;rdquo; is the best word for it. Summer seemed to pass by so fast this year. Barely had time to really enjoy it, it seems, before it&amp;rsquo;s practically gone. They say this happens as you get older, but I suspect in my case it has more to do with a dearth of time spent outside this year, soaking up sun and heat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>